[
  {
    "Question": "How can government laws and regulations result in economic risk?",
    "A": "They can make businesses less safe.",
    "B": "They can reduce a business's profits.",
    "C": "They can protect consumers.",
    "D": "They can result in environmental problems.",
    "answer": "B: They can reduce a business's profits.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an important factor that affects the legal procedure:?",
    "A": "Larceny",
    "B": "Freedom",
    "C": "Misdemeanor",
    "D": "Jurisdiction",
    "answer": "D: Jurisdiction",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Tafoya Company has discovered that the Bremen Company illegally used Tafoya's trademark. To pursue a legal case for financial compensation, what should Tafoya's legal counsel do firs t?",
    "A": "Conduct an examination of discovery to interview all parties involved in the illega l use of the Tafoya trademark.",
    "B": "File a formal complaint to the court alleging the Bremen Company's illegal use of the Tafo ya trademark.",
    "C": "Issue a summons requiring the Bremen Company to respond to allegations of misusing the trademark.",
    "D": "Request that a pretrial conference date be set to clarify all the legal issues that will be di scussed",
    "answer": "B: File a formal complaint to the court alleging the Bremen Company's illegal use of the Tafo ya trademark.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements about the impact of law on business is accurate:?",
    "A": "Businesses are governed by law at the local, national, and international levels.",
    "B": "Businesses are not governed by criminal law because it only applies to individual s.",
    "C": "Businesses should focus on corporate laws enacted and enforced by their local government.",
    "D": "Businesses should focus on ethical rather than legal issues required by national la w.",
    "answer": "A: Businesses are governed by law at the local, national, and international levels.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Shawn is preparing for an interview with a local company. He knows that he should ask relevant questions about the job at the end of the interview. Which of the following will help him prepar e these questions:",
    "A": "Conducting research about the company prior to the interview",
    "B": "Relying on the interviewer to generate the questions",
    "C": "Asking his friends what questions they think he should ask",
    "D": "Finding background information about the interviewer's high school and asking him/her about",
    "answer": "A: Conducting research about the company prior to the interview",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Edith wants to organize the information in her persuasive paper in a clear, logical way that's easy for readers to understand. She starts by stating the dilemma at hand and then explains the answer that sh e believes will solve the dilemma. Which method of organizing information is Edith using?",
    "A": "Alphabetical",
    "B": "Problem/Solution",
    "C": "Deductive",
    "D": "Chronological",
    "answer": "B: Problem/Solution",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The part of a business letter that follows the inside address is the",
    "A": "body.",
    "B": "signature line.",
    "C": "dateline.",
    "D": "salutation.",
    "answer": "D: salutation.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for businesses to include logical evidence in a persuasive lette r?",
    "A": "To force the recipient to respond",
    "B": "To present interesting information",
    "C": "To explain the idea in strong language",
    "D": "To make the message more convincing",
    "answer": "D: To make the message more convincing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When analytical reports contain information that readers might disagree with, writers sho uld back their conclusions with?",
    "A": "enthusiastic statements.",
    "B": "technical statistics.",
    "C": "personal opinions.",
    "D": "logical arguments.",
    "answer": "D: logical arguments.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Every Friday, Odessa is supposed to remind employees to complete and sign their time sheets be fore going home for the weekend. What is the most appropriate channel for Odessa's reminder to employees?",
    "A": "Email",
    "B": "Fax",
    "C": "Phone",
    "D": "Letter",
    "answer": "A: Email",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your friend Maureen is nervous about an upcoming staff meeting at her company. Since y ou have a lot of experience attending and participating in meetings, she asks you for advice. You tell her that s he should be sure to",
    "A": "think about what she will say while others are speaking.",
    "B": "take the opportunity to bring up unrelated concerns she has.",
    "C": "keep quiet if she disagrees with someone else's point.",
    "D": "listen and look interested when someone is speakin g.",
    "answer": "D: listen and look interested when someone is speakin g.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who always keep their commitments to customers are building positive relatio nships with those customers by being",
    "A": "creative.",
    "B": "assertive.",
    "C": "dependable.",
    "D": "sociable.",
    "answer": "C: dependable.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Oliver is an American businessperson who will be traveling to Scotland to close a n important business deal. Does Oliver need to alter his communication style to adapt to the Scottish culture?",
    "A": "No. Scottish people speak English, so Oliver does not need to do anything special to prepare for the trip.",
    "B": "Yes. Scottish people tend to dislike Americans for many reasons, so Oliver needs to m ake sure he is behaving appropriately.",
    "C": "Yes. Oliver should do some research on Scottish culture so he doesn't do or say something offensive.",
    "D": "No. Western cultures tend to have similar cultural attitudes and practices, so Oliver does not",
    "answer": "C: Yes. Oliver should do some research on Scottish culture so he doesn't do or say something offensive.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does solving difficult-customer situations benefit you personally?",
    "A": "You will encounter difficult customers less frequently.",
    "B": "You gain valuable communication skills.",
    "C": "Your customers will be happier.",
    "D": "Your boss will automatically give you a raise.",
    "answer": "B: You gain valuable communication skills.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What role does utility play in the implementation of the marketing concept?",
    "A": "A payment method",
    "B": "A satisfaction gauge",
    "C": "A cost-saving tool",
    "D": "A delivery process",
    "answer": "B: A satisfaction gauge",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions describes proactive management:?",
    "A": "Encouraging individualism",
    "B": "Making only long-term plans",
    "C": "Planning in advance for change",
    "D": "Avoiding risk",
    "answer": "C: Planning in advance for change",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is not one of the four main idealized market structures used in trade theory:?",
    "A": "Monopolistic competition",
    "B": "Perfect competition",
    "C": "Monopoly",
    "D": "Perfect monopoly",
    "answer": "D: Perfect monopoly",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Government provides protection to business owners' property through the use of",
    "A": "consumer-protection laws.",
    "B": "minimum-wage laws.",
    "C": "safety standards.",
    "D": "zoning laws.",
    "answer": "D: zoning laws.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An individual with a higher income who pays a larger percentage of his/her income as taxes t han an individual with a lower income is in a __________ tax system.",
    "A": "flat",
    "B": "regressive",
    "C": "proportional",
    "D": "progressive",
    "answer": "D: progressive",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Limited commodities can cause",
    "A": "price stability.",
    "B": "cost-push inflation.",
    "C": "demand-pull inflation.",
    "D": "hyperinflation.",
    "answer": "B: cost-push inflation.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Some figures that are used to calculate the gross domestic product are",
    "A": "transfers.",
    "B": "forecasts.",
    "C": "estimates.",
    "D": "predictions.",
    "answer": "C: estimates.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When your self-concept is high, you usually believe that you are a(n) __________ pers on.?",
    "A": "aggressive",
    "B": "unimportant",
    "C": "witty",
    "D": "valuable",
    "answer": "D: valuable",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you make a mistake, the responsible thing to do is?",
    "A": "try to fix it before anyone finds out.",
    "B": "quit the project.",
    "C": "determine where to lay the blame.",
    "D": "admit it.",
    "answer": "D: admit it.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you are evaluated by your immediate supervisor, and s/he tells you of all the thi ngs you can do to improve your job performance, that is an example of?",
    "A": "harassment.",
    "B": "constructive criticism.",
    "C": "self-control.",
    "D": "interpersonal relationships.",
    "answer": "B: constructive criticism.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "People who receive a great deal of negative feedback may develop",
    "A": "self-importance.",
    "B": "enthusiasm.",
    "C": "optimism.",
    "D": "depression.",
    "answer": "D: depression.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who set realistic goals and standards for themselves often are able to control thei r",
    "A": "ability to advance.",
    "B": "level of stress.",
    "C": "work schedule.",
    "D": "group participation.",
    "answer": "B: level of stress.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maintaining a sense of humor can help you to be a good team member because it",
    "A": "keeps your emotions under control.",
    "B": "helps to ease any tension that arises.",
    "C": "improves your decision-making skills.",
    "D": "gives you more self-confidence.",
    "answer": "B: helps to ease any tension that arises.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does a goal differ from a vision?",
    "A": "There is no difference-the two are the same.",
    "B": "A goal could mean different things to different people.",
    "C": "A goal is abstract and indefinite.",
    "D": "A goal is concrete and measurable.",
    "answer": "D: A goal is concrete and measurable.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the most likely result when sexual harassment occurs in the workplace?",
    "A": "Good publicity for the business",
    "B": "Motivation for employees to work harder",
    "C": "An annoyance to all employees",
    "D": "A hostile work environment",
    "answer": "D: A hostile work environment",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following businesses is the best example of an entrepreneurial venture:?",
    "A": "A juice bar decides to purchase trucks to sell juice on location during special events.",
    "B": "A veterinarian invents and sells a device to prevent horse water troughs from freezi ng.",
    "C": "A pumpkin farm offers pumpkin carving and costume contests to create more interest.",
    "D": "A bakery creates a \"cretzel,\" a cross between a crescent and a pretzel, as a new produc t.",
    "answer": "B: A veterinarian invents and sells a device to prevent horse water troughs from freezi ng.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Finance charges are expressed as a(n)",
    "A": "annual percentage rate.",
    "B": "monthly percentage rate.",
    "C": "annual balance rate.",
    "D": "monthly balance rate.",
    "answer": "A: annual percentage rate.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is legally responsible for repaying a bank loan if the loan borrower fails to make p ayments as indicated in the loan contract?",
    "A": "Treasury Department",
    "B": "Credit union",
    "C": "Cosigner",
    "D": "Debt collectors",
    "answer": "C: Cosigner",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Fiona made a $500 donation to a local homeless shelter last year. When she prepares her pers onal income tax form, she can claim the donation as part of her",
    "A": "public property.",
    "B": "tax deductions.",
    "C": "living expenses.",
    "D": "discretionary income.",
    "answer": "B: tax deductions.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For financial information to be reliable, it must also be",
    "A": "understandable.",
    "B": "complete.",
    "C": "relevant.",
    "D": "biased.",
    "answer": "B: complete.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mr. Gates owns two successful businesses and would like to open a third. Which of the followi ng business activities should he consider first:",
    "A": "Marketing",
    "B": "Accounting",
    "C": "Production",
    "D": "Management",
    "answer": "B: Accounting",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a factor that might cause a business to adjust its budget figures:?",
    "A": "Sales procedures",
    "B": "Economic trends",
    "C": "Local elections",
    "D": "Operating policies",
    "answer": "B: Economic trends",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following airlines is most likely to be undervalued, based on their pri ce-to-cash flow ratios: Sky High Current Stock Price: $14. 36 Cash Flow per Share: $5.21 Smooth Flying Current Stock Price: $22.78 Cash Flow per Share: $4.12 Soar the Sky Current Stock Price: $18.50 Cash Flow per Share: $3.59 White Clouds Current Stock Price: $25.81 Cash Flow per Share: $6.94?",
    "A": "Smooth Flying",
    "B": "Sky High",
    "C": "Soar the Sky",
    "D": "White Clouds",
    "answer": "B: Sky High",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an indicator of strong organizational ethics?",
    "A": "Underperforming",
    "B": "Overpromising",
    "C": "High trust and mutual respect",
    "D": "Refusal to accept responsibility",
    "answer": "C: High trust and mutual respect",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an ethical issue that relates to knowledge management in the wor kplace:?",
    "A": "The sales manager of a manufacturing firm shares the firm's quarterly sales goals with the sa les staff.",
    "B": "A project leader requests that each member of his/her team provide a status report to the group.",
    "C": "The president of a small company asks her/his executive team for input regarding a business decision.",
    "D": "An employee deliberately doesn't share information with management that will help the company",
    "answer": "D: An employee deliberately doesn't share information with management that will help the company",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The FMT Company wants to implement a software program to capture and communicate tacit knowledge. Which of the following software applications is best suited to fulfill the co mpany's needs:",
    "A": "Recovery",
    "B": "Spreadsheet",
    "C": "Presentation",
    "D": "Groupware",
    "answer": "D: Groupware",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an action that threatens a company's ability to maintain its trade s ecrets:?",
    "A": "Process fragmentation",
    "B": "Systematic neutralizing",
    "C": "Copyright reform initiatives",
    "D": "Reverse engineering",
    "answer": "D: Reverse engineering",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sophia gathered members of the department together to discuss the ways in which the y perform their work and what they do to overcome pitfalls and challenges while performing their day-to-day tasks. While the members of the group shared their experiences and ideas, Sophia took notes and asked follo w-up questions. What technique is Sophia using to capture tacit knowledge?",
    "A": "Channeling discussion",
    "B": "Parliamentary procedure",
    "C": "Repetitious feedback",
    "D": "Critical interaction",
    "answer": "A: Channeling discussion",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about company goals:?",
    "A": "They can't be accomplished without employees' dedication.",
    "B": "They are the same at every company.",
    "C": "All company goals are general.",
    "D": "They are important only for new companies.",
    "answer": "A: They can't be accomplished without employees' dedication.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"Helsinki is the capital of Finland\" is an example of what type of information?",
    "A": "Unproven",
    "B": "Opinion",
    "C": "Criticism",
    "D": "Factual",
    "answer": "D: Factual",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "So the company can make wise business decisions, it is important for the company to effectiv ely manage its",
    "A": "markets.",
    "B": "ratings.",
    "C": "information.",
    "D": "demand.",
    "answer": "C: information.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "By searching the company's computer records, an employee obtained confidential information abo ut a well-known client, which s/he discussed with a friend. Eventually, the information was leaked to the media, which embarrassed the client and the business. What action could the company have tak en to prevent this unethical behavior?",
    "A": "Provide clients with information-tracking capabilities",
    "B": "Install anti-virus software to protect the computer network",
    "C": "Use computer passwords to limit access to certain data",
    "D": "Require the employee to submit his/her resignation",
    "answer": "C: Use computer passwords to limit access to certain data",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What technological component manages the computer's software and hardware?",
    "A": "Operating system",
    "B": "Power supply",
    "C": "Navigation key",
    "D": "Modem",
    "answer": "A: Operating system",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bobbi is searching the Internet for information about business licenses. Unfortunately, many of the search results are useless to her because they focus on drivers' licenses. What search terms shoul d Bobbi use to find information specifically about business licenses?",
    "A": "\"business license\" driver",
    "B": "+business +license",
    "C": "+business +license-driver",
    "D": "BUSINESS LICENSE",
    "answer": "C: +business +license-driver",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Holly, Cary, and Rick are working on a project together, even though they are geographically far away from each other. They use the Internet to work on documents together, share files, and communicate quickly and easily. What type of software are Holly, Cary, and Rick using?",
    "A": "Freeware",
    "B": "Shareware",
    "C": "Spyware",
    "D": "Groupware",
    "answer": "D: Groupware",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One limitation of project-management software is that it lacks the ability to",
    "A": "track resources.",
    "B": "generate reports.",
    "C": "sort data.",
    "D": "find input errors.",
    "answer": "D: find input errors.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When an existing customer's contact information changes, what should a company do?",
    "A": "Add the customer's record in the employee directory",
    "B": "Create a new record that contains the customer's changes",
    "C": "Update the customer's record in the company database",
    "D": "Enter the customer's contact information in a new database",
    "answer": "C: Update the customer's record in the company database",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Running out of inventory can result in",
    "A": "higher taxes.",
    "B": "lost sales.",
    "C": "higher productivity.",
    "D": "more satisfied customers.",
    "answer": "B: lost sales.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following facility components are inspected by authorized officials to ens ure that safety ordinances are met:?",
    "A": "Elevators",
    "B": "Photocopiers",
    "C": "Computer networks",
    "D": "Portable cameras",
    "answer": "A: Elevators",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important for businesses to provide employees with safety and health information and tr aining in order to",
    "A": "prevent accidents.",
    "B": "ensure greater profits.",
    "C": "increase employee morale.",
    "D": "control employee sick leave.",
    "answer": "A: prevent accidents.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following activities should be an employee's top priority:?",
    "A": "Making reservations at a local restaurant for a business luncheon that is going to be held in two weeks",
    "B": "Preparing a purchase order that needs to be faxed to the vendor in two days",
    "C": "Completing a status report that takes 45 minutes to prepare for a meeting that will occur in an hour",
    "D": "Photocopying a three-page document for a meeting with a customer that is scheduled to occur",
    "answer": "C: Completing a status report that takes 45 minutes to prepare for a meeting that will occur in an hour",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Robert forgot that he told Sabrina to update the price list, so he asked Todd to do it. Due to the lack of coordination among the team members, what is most likely to happen?",
    "A": "High efficiency",
    "B": "Duplicate work",
    "C": "Accurate calculations",
    "D": "Effective collaboration",
    "answer": "B: Duplicate work",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When proposing delegated tasks to her team, Becca asked for feedback so that she could?",
    "A": "establish openness.",
    "B": "promote her authority.",
    "C": "discourage over-reporting.",
    "D": "set expected outcomes.",
    "answer": "A: establish openness.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about projects:?",
    "A": "They are short-term undertakings.",
    "B": "They rely on traditional management structures.",
    "C": "They create goods, not services.",
    "D": "Their processes are more important than their result s.",
    "answer": "A: They are short-term undertakings.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is required of businesses to maintain positive, long-term relationships with their suppliers?",
    "A": "Rigid policies",
    "B": "Flexible lead times",
    "C": "Autocratic management",
    "D": "Ongoing communication",
    "answer": "D: Ongoing communication",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an item that most likely requires a retailer to place a special order with a manufacturer:?",
    "A": "Blinds for a nonstandard-size window",
    "B": "Windshield wipers for a 2008 Honda Accord",
    "C": "A cellphone charger for a popular smartphone",
    "D": "A color ink cartridge for a computer printer",
    "answer": "A: Blinds for a nonstandard-size window",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are examples of raw materials that a business might keep on hand for produc tion:?",
    "A": "Oil, grain, shoes, and household cleanser",
    "B": "Leather, bolts, stapler, and ore",
    "C": "Minerals, tables, leather, and paper",
    "D": "Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "answer": "D: Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the ILM Manufacturing Company orders large amounts of bolts and washers, the company's buyer asks its parts vendor for an additional five percent off the invoice total. This is an exam ple of a business negotiating",
    "A": "delivery terms.",
    "B": "a quantity discount.",
    "C": "service terms.",
    "D": "a cash rebate.",
    "answer": "B: a quantity discount.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Production processes that rely heavily on expensive equipment and materials are __________ processes.",
    "A": "intermittent",
    "B": "labor-intensive",
    "C": "standardized",
    "D": "capital-intensive",
    "answer": "D: capital-intensive",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following quality-control tools is a graphical representation of two v ariables that is used to determine cause and effect:?",
    "A": "Flow chart",
    "B": "Histogram",
    "C": "Check s heet",
    "D": "Scatter diagram",
    "answer": "D: Scatter diagram",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following best describes a goal of effective supply chain management:?",
    "A": "Managing customer relations",
    "B": "Reducing inventory",
    "C": "Storing marketing data",
    "D": "Planning promotional strategies",
    "answer": "B: Reducing inventory",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When employees review and analyze financial reports and income data from differ ent time frames, they are?",
    "A": "informing customers.",
    "B": "comparing data.",
    "C": "submitting evidence.",
    "D": "influencing others' opinions.",
    "answer": "B: comparing data.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Technology impacts just-in-time inventory management by",
    "A": "increasing warehouse storage costs.",
    "B": "eliminating the need for supplier relationships.",
    "C": "causing disruptions in the supply chain.",
    "D": "allowing inventory to be monitored regularly.",
    "answer": "D: allowing inventory to be monitored regularly.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a strategy to help manage risks in a global supply chain:?",
    "A": "Work with experienced partners abroad",
    "B": "Hire only local workers",
    "C": "Work only within the same time zone",
    "D": "Accept lower quality levels",
    "answer": "A: Work with experienced partners abroad",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To protect customer data such as credit card information, businesses should",
    "A": "use a shared server to store information.",
    "B": "accept payments in cash only.",
    "C": "require that all customers show an ID.",
    "D": "keep sensitive records encrypted.",
    "answer": "D: keep sensitive records encrypted.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you keep your workspace organized, you are less likely to?",
    "A": "misuse office equipment.",
    "B": "misplace important documents.",
    "C": "forget important phone numbers.",
    "D": "discard unnecessary paperwork.",
    "answer": "B: misplace important documents.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true of time management:?",
    "A": "It is a matter of common sense and just involves using a calendar.",
    "B": "It refers to how people use the 24 hours in their day.",
    "C": "It requires a significant amount of extra work.",
    "D": "It makes it more difficult for you to plan for the future.",
    "answer": "B: It refers to how people use the 24 hours in their day.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Even when times are tough for Caitlin's business venture, she tends to remain positive-she looks at the glass as half full rather than half empty. What characteristic of entrepreneurship is Caitlin exh ibiting?",
    "A": "Determination",
    "B": "Organization",
    "C": "Innovation",
    "D": "Optimism",
    "answer": "D: Optimism",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Department manager, small business manager, and regional manager are __________ positions.",
    "A": "supply chain management",
    "B": "business analytics",
    "C": "operations management",
    "D": "general management",
    "answer": "D: general management",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is often the first step in conducting a job search?",
    "A": "Identifying leads",
    "B": "Completing applications",
    "C": "Contacting employers",
    "D": "Scheduling interviews",
    "answer": "A: Identifying leads",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is it ever appropriate for an individual looking for a job to send a letter of application to a busine ss that has not advertised a job opening?",
    "A": "No, the business will discard the letter if it has no openings.",
    "B": "Yes, the worker should write to each business in the industry.",
    "C": "Yes, the worker can write if s/he has heard about a job opening.",
    "D": "No, a letter is used only in response to job advertisements.",
    "answer": "C: Yes, the worker can write if s/he has heard about a job opening.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To perform his job, Andrew works with a complex database program. Recently, a new version of the database program that he uses was released. The new program is more powerful, efficient, and user friendly. To learn how to use the program effectively, Andrew signed up to take a class at the communit y college. In this situation, Andrew is continuing his education so that he can",
    "A": "update his technical skills.",
    "B": "change his career path.",
    "C": "ensure his employability.",
    "D": "obtain professional licensure.",
    "answer": "A: update his technical skills.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary advantage of developing a work breakdown structure (WBS) to manage large projects?",
    "A": "Eliminates unexpected circumstances",
    "B": "Prevents the duplication of work",
    "C": "Reduces the need to set project milestones",
    "D": "Decreases the need to manage each task",
    "answer": "B: Prevents the duplication of work",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When team members disagree about the best way to complete an activity, the project manager m ay need to?",
    "A": "help resolve the conflict.",
    "B": "negotiate with external sources.",
    "C": "evaluate the reward system.",
    "D": "change the project scope.",
    "answer": "A: help resolve the conflict.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Releasing equipment, materials, and team members are tasks that are completed during the ___________ phase of a project.",
    "A": "planning",
    "B": "scheduling",
    "C": "closing",
    "D": "initiating",
    "answer": "C: closing",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The overall purpose of the Six Sigma quality-management framework is to satisfy custom ers and",
    "A": "identify needs.",
    "B": "simplify activities.",
    "C": "improve technology.",
    "D": "lower costs.",
    "answer": "D: lower costs.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What step in the continuous improvement process will indicate if quality is increas ing?",
    "A": "Documentation",
    "B": "Evaluation",
    "C": "Recommendation",
    "D": "Implementation",
    "answer": "B: Evaluation",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To reduce the risk of unauthorized access to confidential data, businesses use security soft ware to protect their",
    "A": "corporate policies.",
    "B": "intranet systems.",
    "C": "intercom systems.",
    "D": "spam email.",
    "answer": "B: intranet systems.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When businesses continuously monitor the laws and implement changes to remain in compli ance, they are?",
    "A": "interpreting contracts.",
    "B": "demonstrating negligence.",
    "C": "controlling their risks.",
    "D": "increasing their liabilities.",
    "answer": "C: controlling their risks.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When managers have the ability to understand how all of the functions of the company are interrelated, they possess?",
    "A": "innovative ideas.",
    "B": "interpersonal skills.",
    "C": "technical competence.",
    "D": "conceptual skills.",
    "answer": "D: conceptual skills.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What must occur before any management functions can be carried out?",
    "A": "Analyzing",
    "B": "Planning",
    "C": "Processing",
    "D": "Brainstorming",
    "answer": "B: Planning",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The organizing function of management is important to a business because it",
    "A": "defines workplace roles and relationships.",
    "B": "ensures efficient performance levels.",
    "C": "encourages creativity and problem solving.",
    "D": "motivates employees to achieve goals.",
    "answer": "A: defines workplace roles and relationships.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about human resources needs:?",
    "A": "They are harder to meet in high-tech industries.",
    "B": "They are always changing.",
    "C": "They are the same at every business.",
    "D": "There is no way to know when they will change.",
    "answer": "B: They are always changing.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What management function involves motivating and encouraging an employee?",
    "A": "Planning",
    "B": "Directing",
    "C": "Organizing",
    "D": "Recruiting",
    "answer": "B: Directing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Measuring the productivity of a business's employees is an example of",
    "A": "managerial control.",
    "B": "formal authority.",
    "C": "leadership style.",
    "D": "positional analysis.",
    "answer": "A: managerial control.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following employees would most likely be described as \"innovative\" by his/her supervisor:?",
    "A": "Elizabeth, because she gets frustrated when she needs to learn new skills",
    "B": "Madison, because she prefers to stick to traditional ideas and processes",
    "C": "Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "D": "Anthony, because he is usually quiet during brainstorming sessions",
    "answer": "C: Jake, because he is always willing to adapt to changes during a project",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jon sues his former employer for harassment. In what situation would the employer be likely to offer Jon a settlement?",
    "A": "The employer does not think it will be able to win the case.",
    "B": "The employer knows it will be able to win the case.",
    "C": "The employer wants the case to go to court.",
    "D": "Jon does not think he will be able to win the case.",
    "answer": "A: The employer does not think it will be able to win the case.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The litigation process begins when",
    "A": "the parties reach a settlement.",
    "B": "the defendant files an answer with the court.",
    "C": "the plaintiff files a complaint with the court.",
    "D": "an appeal is considered.",
    "answer": "C: the plaintiff files a complaint with the court.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a legitimate response for an employee to provide to a customer regarding an inquiry about product pricing:?",
    "A": "You'll need to contact the appropriate person to get the price.",
    "B": "I'm not sure what the pricing is.",
    "C": "If you can wait a moment, I'll check for the price in the computer.",
    "D": "I'm pretty sure that the item costs $39.65.",
    "answer": "C: If you can wait a moment, I'll check for the price in the computer.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "All calls coming into a business should end as pleasantly as possible in order to",
    "A": "leave a good last impression with callers.",
    "B": "make the best use of your time.",
    "C": "help you to get a good review.",
    "D": "provide callers with accurate information.",
    "answer": "A: leave a good last impression with callers.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel says to the audience, \"Now that you have some insight about the nature of the problem, I'll discuss the methodology that our firm used to conduct the research.\" This statement is an exam ple of a(n)",
    "A": "introduction.",
    "B": "transition.",
    "C": "gesture.",
    "D": "conclusion.",
    "answer": "B: transition.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are elements that appear in the heading of a memorandum:?",
    "A": "To, title, from, and date",
    "B": "To, from, date, and subject",
    "C": "Date, title, to, and company",
    "D": "Company, to, subject, and date",
    "answer": "B: To, from, date, and subject",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jessica must develop an analytical report that assesses the product opportunities for 18-to 34-year-old sports enthusiasts in the greater Seattle area. What type of analytical report is Jessica wr iting?",
    "A": "Market analysis",
    "B": "Troubleshooting",
    "C": "Justification",
    "D": "Feasibility",
    "answer": "A: Market analysis",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a purpose statement in a research report:?",
    "A": "In 2005, Sims Research surveyed 150,000 college professors.",
    "B": "In this study, we will examine the causes and effects of climate change.",
    "C": "The quality of soil may affect plant growth.",
    "D": "2,500 residents reported power outages during the ice storm.",
    "answer": "B: In this study, we will examine the causes and effects of climate change.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The purpose of participating in staff meetings usually is to",
    "A": "share information.",
    "B": "achieve a task.",
    "C": "conduct research.",
    "D": "develop a message.",
    "answer": "A: share information.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Customers tend to look at a business as a whole despite the number of __________ they experienc e.",
    "A": "feedback surveys",
    "B": "complaints",
    "C": "touch points",
    "D": "purchases",
    "answer": "C: touch points",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The overall category of resources that makes it possible for businesses to produce the goods and services that consumers want to buy is __________ resources.",
    "A": "economic",
    "B": "human",
    "C": "capital",
    "D": "natural",
    "answer": "A: economic",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Service businesses that use goods in order to perform their services usually do not transfer _____ _____ those goods to customers.",
    "A": "benefits from",
    "B": "usefulness of",
    "C": "ownership of",
    "D": "information about",
    "answer": "C: ownership of",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of opening a franchise:?",
    "A": "A well-known brand name",
    "B": "Paying royalties",
    "C": "Restrictions on products, prices, and location",
    "D": "Reliance on raw materials",
    "answer": "A: A well-known brand name",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason that a company would decide to offer its products in other c ountries:?",
    "A": "To subsidize developing countries",
    "B": "To sell obsolete, outdated products",
    "C": "To expand to new, untapped markets",
    "D": "To provide jobs to people in other countries",
    "answer": "C: To expand to new, untapped markets",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is vital to the successful operation of a private enterprise syst em:?",
    "A": "Competition",
    "B": "Mechanization",
    "C": "Production",
    "D": "Distribution",
    "answer": "A: Competition",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Government protects consumers by establishing",
    "A": "a measure of effectiveness in government.",
    "B": "requirements for product testing.",
    "C": "rules to generate competition.",
    "D": "laws to monitor the growth of business.",
    "answer": "B: requirements for product testing.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that inflation impacts businesses is by",
    "A": "increasing productivity.",
    "B": "decreasing free trade.",
    "C": "increasing prices.",
    "D": "decreasing labor costs.",
    "answer": "C: increasing prices.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following situations does a nation have a favorable balance of trade:",
    "A": "Exports of $3.5 million and imports of $3.1 million",
    "B": "Exports of $4.7 million and imports of $4.8 million",
    "C": "Exports of $2.4 million and cash flow of $2.9 million",
    "D": "Exports of $1.8 million and foreign aid of $1.5 million",
    "answer": "A: Exports of $3.5 million and imports of $3.1 million",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your interest and enthusiasm can help to create a sense of __________ within your work group.",
    "A": "cooperation",
    "B": "disagreement",
    "C": "security",
    "D": "conflict",
    "answer": "A: cooperation",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a possible consequence of taking too much initiative:?",
    "A": "Improving job performance",
    "B": "Causing hard feelings among employees",
    "C": "Higher ratings on job evaluations",
    "D": "Increased respect from others",
    "answer": "B: Causing hard feelings among employees",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Elias always listens to his friends instead of letting his mind wander or getting di stracted by his phone. Which trust-building technique is Elias demonstrating?",
    "A": "Taking responsibility for your mistakes",
    "B": "Communicating often and openly",
    "C": "Not sharing confidential information",
    "D": "Keeping your promises",
    "answer": "B: Communicating often and openly",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The main reason that employers offer criticism is so that workers can improve their",
    "A": "job performance.",
    "B": "ability to get along with others.",
    "C": "ability to accept feedback.",
    "D": "personal situations.",
    "answer": "A: job performance.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Valuing diversity means",
    "A": "acknowledging differences as problems.",
    "B": "ignoring differences.",
    "C": "minimizing differences.",
    "D": "acknowledging differences as assets.",
    "answer": "D: acknowledging differences as assets.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Norman overheard Gina tell a coworker that the company's operations manager is going to be fired. Should Norman tell the operations manager about the conversation?",
    "A": "No. Because if Norman believes that the gossip isn't true, he should confront Gina.",
    "B": "No. Gina is gossiping about something that may or may not be true.",
    "C": "Yes. The operations manager needs to start looking for another job.",
    "D": "Yes. If the operations manager is Norman's boss, Norman should warn him/her about the",
    "answer": "B: No. Gina is gossiping about something that may or may not be true.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following do individuals usually need to be able to persuade others:?",
    "A": "Flexibility",
    "B": "Credibility",
    "C": "Creativity",
    "D": "Responsibility",
    "answer": "B: Credibility",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In a consensus-building group, the facilitator is the person who",
    "A": "keeps the discussion on track.",
    "B": "is in charge of the group.",
    "C": "takes notes.",
    "D": "makes sure everyone has equal time to speak.",
    "answer": "A: keeps the discussion on track.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Motivation can be anything that drives a person to pursue a(n)",
    "A": "raise at work.",
    "B": "certain outcome.",
    "C": "achievement award.",
    "D": "promotion.",
    "answer": "B: certain outcome.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tayari communicates openly, even when it's difficult. She demonstrates",
    "A": "transparency.",
    "B": "fairness.",
    "C": "viability.",
    "D": "accountability.",
    "answer": "A: transparency.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following people would make the best entrepreneur:?",
    "A": "A risk-averse person who wants to work 9 to 5",
    "B": "A person who lacks self-confidence",
    "C": "A risk-taker who has a strong work ethic",
    "D": "A person who often works so hard she makes herself sick",
    "answer": "C: A risk-taker who has a strong work ethic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If individuals are not self-employed, which of the following is a type of earned incom e they might receive:",
    "A": "Child support income",
    "B": "Vacation pay",
    "C": "Interest and dividends",
    "D": "Trust disbursements",
    "answer": "B: Vacation pay",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What source of credit offers its members small loans, installment credit, and low interest rates?",
    "A": "Commercial banks",
    "B": "Sales finance companies",
    "C": "Credit unions",
    "D": "Savings and loan associations",
    "answer": "C: Credit unions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Caitlin has three credit cards. She receives her credit card statement for one of the cards and has to decide how to pay the $500 she spent with that card. To pay the least for use of the credit, she sho uld pay with __________ and make the __________ payment.",
    "A": "cash; full",
    "B": "cash; minimum",
    "C": "another card; full",
    "D": "another card; minimum",
    "answer": "A: cash; full",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While George is unable to work because of a back injury, he receives a check every week for 60% of hi s usual salary. George's check is a benefit of his __________ insurance.",
    "A": "cash-value",
    "B": "disability",
    "C": "liability",
    "D": "bodily injury",
    "answer": "B: disability",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is usually responsible for analyzing a business's income statement?",
    "A": "Customers",
    "B": "Managers",
    "C": "Cashiers",
    "D": "Bookkeepers",
    "answer": "B: Managers",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nico knows he would never do anything unethical, but he is sure that all of his coworkers are tempte d at one point or another. Nico is demonstrating",
    "A": "loss aversion.",
    "B": "short-term gratification.",
    "C": "framing.",
    "D": "over-optimism and overconfidence.",
    "answer": "D: over-optimism and overconfidence.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If the cash from operating activities is consistently greater than the company's net income, the compan y's net earnings are of a(n) __________ quality.",
    "A": "high",
    "B": "low",
    "C": "moderate",
    "D": "excessive",
    "answer": "A: high",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "True or false: Companies without an HR department do not participate in HR management activities.",
    "A": "False; in companies without HR departments, all employees participate in HR management activities.",
    "B": "True; smaller companies have no need for HR management.",
    "C": "True; only HR managers can complete these activities.",
    "D": "False; in companies without HR departments, other managers and supervisors participate in HR",
    "answer": "D: False; in companies without HR departments, other managers and supervisors participate in HR",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the foundation of knowledge management?",
    "A": "An unresolved conflict or problem",
    "B": "An intangible product to mark et",
    "C": "A place to store unrelated data",
    "D": "A willingness to share expertise",
    "answer": "D: A willingness to share expertise",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To have effective knowledge-management processes, businesses need their employees to have a (n) __________ attitude.",
    "A": "argumentative",
    "B": "cautious",
    "C": "transparent",
    "D": "curious",
    "answer": "C: transparent",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The laddering technique is used to capture and change categories of",
    "A": "horizontal communication.",
    "B": "hierarchical information.",
    "C": "meaningless data.",
    "D": "redundant knowledge.",
    "answer": "B: hierarchical information.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your company had total sales of $5 billion last year, while your industry as a whole s old $50 billion. Your company's sales divided by total industry sales equals 10 percent, or your",
    "A": "efficiency.",
    "B": "market share.",
    "C": "ethics.",
    "D": "brand value.",
    "answer": "B: market share.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lamar Enterprises is using a trademark that looks very similar to the Seward Company's trademark. To prevent Lamar from continuing to use the trademark, Seward can take legal action by",
    "A": "filing an infringement lawsuit against Lamar.",
    "B": "charging Lamar with obstruction of justice.",
    "C": "requiring Lamar to pay a licensing fee.",
    "D": "obtaining an arrest warrant.",
    "answer": "A: filing an infringement lawsuit against Lamar.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do businesses often develop to be able to store and analyze data for the purpose of making business decisions?",
    "A": "Information systems",
    "B": "Operating procedures",
    "C": "Survey methods",
    "D": "Management policies",
    "answer": "A: Information systems",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The capability of combining graphics, text, animation, and sound is a unique characteristic of __________ software programs.",
    "A": "communication",
    "B": "presentation",
    "C": "numeric",
    "D": "electronic",
    "answer": "B: presentation",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jamal wants to purchase software for his small business that allows him to create text d ocuments, prepare presentations, maintain a customer database, and develop numerical charts. What type of software would best meet Jamal's needs?",
    "A": "Word processing",
    "B": "Integrated",
    "C": "Spreadsheet",
    "D": "Trajectory",
    "answer": "B: Integrated",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of data analysis suggests a future course of action:?",
    "A": "Prescriptive analytics",
    "B": "Predictive analytics",
    "C": "Descriptive analytics",
    "D": "Instructive analytics",
    "answer": "A: Prescriptive analytics",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an accurate description of business records:?",
    "A": "Documents containing company information",
    "B": "Events involving sales employees",
    "C": "Reports about retail theft",
    "D": "Accounts of customer loyalty",
    "answer": "A: Documents containing company information",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an economic factor that affects business trends:?",
    "A": "The business cycle",
    "B": "Lifestyle changes",
    "C": "An aging population",
    "D": "Emergence of social media",
    "answer": "A: The business cycle",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following may happen if a business cuts costs:?",
    "A": "It may pay fewer taxes.",
    "B": "It may improve product quality.",
    "C": "It may boost its community involvement.",
    "D": "It may hire more employees.",
    "answer": "A: It may pay fewer taxes.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) increased requirements for food allergen awareness for all food workers, how would a restaurant's operations likely be affected?",
    "A": "Increased margins and sales",
    "B": "Faster food service",
    "C": "Increased training time and costs",
    "D": "Higher employee retention",
    "answer": "C: Increased training time and costs",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses can help to prevent accidents in the workplace by",
    "A": "controlling human error.",
    "B": "establishing safety guidelines.",
    "C": "purchasing insurance.",
    "D": "buying only accident-proof equipment.",
    "answer": "B: establishing safety guidelines.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The purpose of depositing large bills in drop boxes upon receipt is to prevent",
    "A": "burglary.",
    "B": "fraud.",
    "C": "robbery.",
    "D": "pilferage.",
    "answer": "C: robbery.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations should be an employee's top priority:?",
    "A": "Preparing a simple report that is due in one week",
    "B": "Returning an urgent telephone call from an important customer",
    "C": "Faxing a purchase order that a vendor needs by tomorrow afternoon",
    "D": "Reading an online newsletter about industry trends",
    "answer": "B: Returning an urgent telephone call from an important customer",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What must be determined before work can be coordinated effectively among team members?",
    "A": "Customer-satisfaction levels",
    "B": "Technical changes",
    "C": "The necessary tasks",
    "D": "The employees' requirements",
    "answer": "C: The necessary tasks",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determining a project's feasibility, developing a statement of work (SoW), creating SM ART objectives, and developing a project charter occur during the __________ stage of project management.",
    "A": "initiation",
    "B": "planning",
    "C": "execution",
    "D": "closure",
    "answer": "A: initiation",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the best example of the types of resources it takes to complete a project successfully:?",
    "A": "Encouragement",
    "B": "Food",
    "C": "Materials",
    "D": "Energy",
    "answer": "C: Materials",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an important question that a business should ask when select ing a vendor:?",
    "A": "What is our business's target market?",
    "B": "What computer program does the vendor use for its project management processes?",
    "C": "Does the vendor have the resources to consistently meet our business's needs?",
    "D": "What are our business's strengths and weaknesses?",
    "answer": "C: Does the vendor have the resources to consistently meet our business's needs?",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is required to maintain favorable relationships with vendors?",
    "A": "Ongoing cooperation",
    "B": "Limited communication",
    "C": "Occasional interaction",
    "D": "Full disclosure",
    "answer": "A: Ongoing cooperation",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Colbert Company ships 19 cases of model number 328 bolts to SOA Manufacturing Company ever y other week. This is an example of a(n) __________ purchase order.",
    "A": "seasonal",
    "B": "advance",
    "C": "standing",
    "D": "open",
    "answer": "C: standing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a raw material that a business might inventory for pr oduction use:?",
    "A": "Chair",
    "B": "Toothpaste",
    "C": "Stapler",
    "D": "Wood",
    "answer": "D: Wood",
    "topic": "Supply Chain Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Simpson Company is negotiating discount terms with Cornwell Manufacturing, a prospectiv e vendor. During the negotiation, Cornwell states that it is willing to offer Simpson a six-percent d iscount on orders over $50,000. Although Simpson would rather have an eight-percent discount, it agrees to the te rms, hoping to obtain something it wants later in the negotiation. This is an example of a",
    "A": "concession.",
    "B": "withdrawal.",
    "C": "plea.",
    "D": "position.",
    "answer": "A: concession.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that employees can help to control a business's expenses is by",
    "A": "rotating stock daily.",
    "B": "arriving at work on time.",
    "C": "overlooking thefts.",
    "D": "handling products casually.",
    "answer": "B: arriving at work on time.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To remain competitive in the marketplace, a company implements processes to identify its inter nal strengths and weaknesses and its external opportunities and threats. What type of business analysi s is the company conducting?",
    "A": "Resource allocation",
    "B": "Financial leverage",
    "C": "PERT",
    "D": "SWOT",
    "answer": "D: SWOT",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Online shipment tracking is one example of __________ affecting supply chain management.",
    "A": "globalization",
    "B": "technology",
    "C": "an economic downturn",
    "D": "production changes",
    "answer": "B: technology",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Supply chain networks are often",
    "A": "unimportant.",
    "B": "eliminated.",
    "C": "redesigned.",
    "D": "unprofitable.",
    "answer": "C: redesigned.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One possible downside to choosing overseas suppliers is",
    "A": "increased delivery times.",
    "B": "increased costs.",
    "C": "a simpler supply chain.",
    "D": "increased taxes.",
    "answer": "A: increased delivery times.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one way that employees can help their companies protect digital assets?",
    "A": "Send out emails to update everyone on security policy changes.",
    "B": "Share passwords with everyone in the company.",
    "C": "Download documents from unevaluated websites.",
    "D": "Follow company policies about giving out personal information.",
    "answer": "D: Follow company policies about giving out personal information.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lack of exercise, sleep, and adequate relaxation are factors that are likely to have a direct eff ect on an individual's ability to",
    "A": "socialize with coworkers.",
    "B": "enter training programs.",
    "C": "perform job expectations.",
    "D": "learn of new opportunities.",
    "answer": "C: perform job expectations.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important to develop a personal plan of action for goals because",
    "A": "a plan guarantees success.",
    "B": "goals cannot be achieved without a written plan.",
    "C": "a plan helps you to achieve your goals.",
    "D": "you can share the plan with others.",
    "answer": "C: a plan helps you to achieve your goals.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Creativity is an important skill to use in",
    "A": "calculus.",
    "B": "ethics.",
    "C": "problem solving.",
    "D": "accounting.",
    "answer": "C: problem solving.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following employees has an operations management career:?",
    "A": "Samuel manages his company's call center.",
    "B": "Kylie is a district manager.",
    "C": "Wyatt is in charge of recruiting employees.",
    "D": "Valerie trains her company's new employees.",
    "answer": "A: Samuel manages his company's call center.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Virgil is looking to gain work experience in graphic design, but he has not been able to secure a part-or full-time position with a company. He decides to bid on jobs online that will pay him a small wage per project he completes. Virgil is __________ to gain valuable work experience.",
    "A": "freelancing",
    "B": "volunteering",
    "C": "interning",
    "D": "being an apprentice",
    "answer": "A: freelancing",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which component of the project's statement of work (SoW) would the following message most l ikely appear: \"Due to the limited amount of time allocated to complete the study, the survey sample size m ay need to be reduced.\"",
    "A": "Deliverables",
    "B": "Purpose",
    "C": "Benefits",
    "D": "Constraints",
    "answer": "D: Constraints",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Trevor needs to determine the procedures that he needs to follow for a specific project work activity. Trevor can locate that information in the",
    "A": "work breakdown structure dictionary.",
    "B": "project's statement of work.",
    "C": "network diagram.",
    "D": "production schedule.",
    "answer": "A: work breakdown structure dictionary.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the primary activity performed during the execution pha se of a project:?",
    "A": "Producing",
    "B": "Forecasting",
    "C": "Financing",
    "D": "Arbitrating",
    "answer": "A: Producing",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jane said, \"Troy, I think you are on the right track. Let's make the modification that you sugge sted, but do it before you enter the phase 2D data in the computer system.\" What project-management activity is Jane performing?",
    "A": "Resolving conflict",
    "B": "Providing feedback",
    "C": "Encouraging teamwork",
    "D": "Assessing skills",
    "answer": "B: Providing feedback",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Six Sigma framework of quality management takes a disciplined approach to continuou sly providing better quality and",
    "A": "changing intermediaries.",
    "B": "assessing competitors.",
    "C": "lowering costs.",
    "D": "increasing visibility.",
    "answer": "C: lowering costs.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Although governments and businesses used computers in limited ways for several decades, the development and widespread use of desktop computers emerged in the 1980s in both homes and businesses, drastically changing the way people and businesses interact. What type of i mprovement does this situation exemplify?",
    "A": "Breakthrough",
    "B": "Incremental",
    "C": "Compli ant",
    "D": "Supplemental",
    "answer": "A: Breakthrough",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an ethical issue resulting from internal risks:?",
    "A": "Boycotting the use of an insurance company that has a reputation for not correcting its mistakes",
    "B": "Revealing discounted expenses",
    "C": "Selecting an insurance company that considers paying fines a cost of doing business",
    "D": "Providing incomplete data for audits",
    "answer": "D: Providing incomplete data for audits",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a risk-management application that alerts the appropriate personnel when an unauthorized source has tried to access the business's computer network:?",
    "A": "Organic scoreboard",
    "B": "Automated notification",
    "C": "Genetic algorithm",
    "D": "Forensic accounting",
    "answer": "B: Automated notification",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An automobile manufacturer in Country A purchases parts from a factory in Country B. When Country B suffers a massive earthquake, the automobile manufacturer is forced to put production on hold until it can find another factory to supply the parts. What type of risk does this situation illustrate?",
    "A": "Political",
    "B": "Employee",
    "C": "Environmental",
    "D": "Health and safety",
    "answer": "C: Environmental",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do top-level managers usually receive high salaries?",
    "A": "Their decisions affect the entire company.",
    "B": "They are required to attend a great many meetings.",
    "C": "They have more experience than others in the company.",
    "D": "Their responsibilities involve hands-on supervision.",
    "answer": "A: Their decisions affect the entire company.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Serena is determining the specific activities needed to carry out a year-long adverti sing campaign. Serena is engaged in __________ planning.",
    "A": "tactical",
    "B": "strategic",
    "C": "contingency",
    "D": "long-term",
    "answer": "A: tactical",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The primary purpose of the organizing function of management is to provide",
    "A": "leverage.",
    "B": "structure.",
    "C": "insight.",
    "D": "motivation.",
    "answer": "B: structure.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Melanie is showing a group of new employees how to perform work-related tasks. What s taffing activity is Melanie performing?",
    "A": "Appraising",
    "B": "Recruiting",
    "C": "Interviewing",
    "D": "Training",
    "answer": "D: Training",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kate says, \"I am very pleased with your progress on the project, Devon. Take the rest of the day of f, and we'll talk about the next phase of the project tomorrow.\" What directing activity is Kate performi ng?",
    "A": "Motivating an employee",
    "B": "Establishing a schedule",
    "C": "Delegating responsibility",
    "D": "Training a worker",
    "answer": "A: Motivating an employee",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the three primary characteristics of an effective control system in a business?",
    "A": "Responsive, flexible, and transferable",
    "B": "Suitable, understandable, and timely",
    "C": "Relevant, intangible, and rigid",
    "D": "Rigid, economical, and reactionary",
    "answer": "B: Suitable, understandable, and timely",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Change management occurs in a cycle because",
    "A": "organizations always need to change.",
    "B": "organizations push for unnecessary change.",
    "C": "change is harmful for most companies.",
    "D": "change is difficult to implement.",
    "answer": "A: organizations always need to change.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When entering into a contract with another business, an agent is the party that represents the?",
    "A": "consultant.",
    "B": "defendant.",
    "C": "opposition.",
    "D": "principal.",
    "answer": "D: principal.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The person who files a lawsuit is the",
    "A": "plaintiff.",
    "B": "defendant.",
    "C": "lawyer.",
    "D": "judge.",
    "answer": "A: plaintiff.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why might parties choose to use mediation to solve a dispute?",
    "A": "To avoid going to court",
    "B": "To spend more money",
    "C": "To do less work",
    "D": "To get a less personal result",
    "answer": "A: To avoid going to court",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sasha's science teacher is explaining lab directions to the class. They'll be pe rforming a complicated experiment with many steps that will take about a week. The next day, Sasha tries to remem ber a step of the directions, but she can't. Which step of following oral directions should Sasha have foll owed?",
    "A": "Eliminate distractions",
    "B": "Take notes",
    "C": "Make eye contact",
    "D": "Acknowledge directions verbally or nonverbally",
    "answer": "B: Take notes",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"This is an exciting new opportunity for you,\" says Jane's boss. Which of the follo wing nonverbal cues would appropriately reinforce that message?",
    "A": "Focusing eyes on the computer",
    "B": "Slouching",
    "C": "Smiling",
    "D": "Looking out the window",
    "answer": "C: Smiling",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jolie is working in a group in her business class. If she wants to contribute to her group's d iscussion in a meaningful way, what should she do?",
    "A": "Summarize what's been discussed in the conversation",
    "B": "Let someone know right away if his/her idea is bad or unrealistic",
    "C": "Wait for other people to lead the conversation when it gets silent",
    "D": "Ask questions as a way of judging someone else's suggestion",
    "answer": "A: Summarize what's been discussed in the conversation",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the three main purposes of oral presentations?",
    "A": "To inform, inspire, and entertain",
    "B": "To inform, persuade, and entertain",
    "C": "To inform, persuade, and instruct",
    "D": "To interview, debate, and entertain",
    "answer": "B: To inform, persuade, and entertain",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Aaron prepared a detailed report for his supervisor that described several issues that Aaron's work group has been experiencing with a long-term project. Aaron described the most difficult or challenging i ssues in the beginning of the report and ended the report with the least important points. How did Aaron organize the information in the report?",
    "A": "Priority sequence",
    "B": "Alphabetical by category",
    "C": "Simple to complex",
    "D": "Chronological order",
    "answer": "A: Priority sequence",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jacob is determining the writing style to use for an analytical report. If most readers are likel y to support the report's content, Jacob should format the report for a(n) __________ audience.",
    "A": "receptive",
    "B": "indecisive",
    "C": "argumentative",
    "D": "intellectual",
    "answer": "A: receptive",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the last component of a research report:?",
    "A": "Recommendations",
    "B": "Purpose of the study",
    "C": "Background information",
    "D": "Methodology",
    "answer": "A: Recommendations",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Phoebe is the manager of a small company. One of her employees has been showing up late an d missing work frequently. What channel of communication should Phoebe use to discuss thi s issue with him?",
    "A": "A company-wide memo",
    "B": "An email message",
    "C": "Face-to-face conversation",
    "D": "A video conference",
    "answer": "C: Face-to-face conversation",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When participating in a project-status meeting, it is important for a participant to?",
    "A": "be prepared to provide an updat e.",
    "B": "monopolize the conversation.",
    "C": "provide information about new company policies.",
    "D": "take notes for the group.",
    "answer": "A: be prepared to provide an updat e.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Today, customer relationship management is considered an important tool in",
    "A": "commercial investing.",
    "B": "business decision-making.",
    "C": "hiring new employees.",
    "D": "establishing connections with vendors.",
    "answer": "B: business decision-making.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an economic service:?",
    "A": "Eyeglasses",
    "B": "Bottle of perfume",
    "C": "Baseball bat",
    "D": "Ticket to football game",
    "answer": "D: Ticket to football game",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are examples of capital goods:?",
    "A": "Trucks, drum scanners, and minerals",
    "B": "Bull dozers, photocopiers, and roads",
    "C": "Tractors, laborers, and cranes",
    "D": "Refineries, iron ore, and computers",
    "answer": "B: Bull dozers, photocopiers, and roads",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason that businesses use a matrix organizational design is to",
    "A": "share human resources.",
    "B": "improve employee productivity.",
    "C": "segment areas of expertise.",
    "D": "standardize business tasks.",
    "answer": "A: share human resources.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a government regulation that affects a business's worki ng conditions:?",
    "A": "Zoning laws",
    "B": "Food inspection",
    "C": "Minimum wage",
    "D": "Price supports",
    "answer": "C: Minimum wage",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an item that is subject to an excise tax:?",
    "A": "Prescription medication",
    "B": "Carton of eggs",
    "C": "Ski boat",
    "D": "Business computer",
    "answer": "C: Ski boat",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about gross domestic product (GDP):?",
    "A": "Improved use of resources increases the GDP.",
    "B": "The underground economy overstates the GDP.",
    "C": "It is easy to measure the GDP accurately.",
    "D": "A decrease in GDP results in a higher standard of living.",
    "answer": "A: Improved use of resources increases the GDP.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following illustrates the impact of a country's history on world trade:?",
    "A": "Countries with widely different religious beliefs have difficulty establishing trust.",
    "B": "Countries that have engaged in war conflicts have difficulty establishing trust.",
    "C": "Countries speaking different languages have difficulty understanding each other.",
    "D": "Countries that are adjacent to each other have more opportunities for conflict.",
    "answer": "B: Countries that have engaged in war conflicts have difficulty establishing trust.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One good way to raise your level of self-esteem when it has dropped is to",
    "A": "discuss your feelings with someone you trust.",
    "B": "withdraw from activities for a while.",
    "C": "reanalyze all your past mistakes.",
    "D": "keep your feelings to yourself.",
    "answer": "A: discuss your feelings with someone you trust.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Workers can demonstrate their honesty and integrity by giving a fair amount of ___________ for their pay.",
    "A": "worry",
    "B": "concern",
    "C": "effort",
    "D": "loyalty",
    "answer": "C: effort",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For two hours a day, Jacob shuts his office door to prevent interruptions, does not check email, and does not accept incoming phone calls. This enables Jacob to focus on his most important tasks. What technique is Jacob using to help him manage his work commitments effectively?",
    "A": "Eliminating the use of technological tools",
    "B": "Delegating his workload",
    "C": "Controlling environmental distractions",
    "D": "Developing a detailed \"to-do\" list",
    "answer": "C: Controlling environmental distractions",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does having a sense of humor help you maintain a positive attitude?",
    "A": "It encourages you to give your appearance the attention it deserves.",
    "B": "If you hang out with positive people, you'll be positive as well.",
    "C": "It is easier to maintain a positive attitude when you're healthy.",
    "D": "It keeps you from taking yourself too seriously.",
    "answer": "D: It keeps you from taking yourself too seriously.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When people make you angry or upset, you may be able to maintain your self-control if you?",
    "A": "frown to indicate your displeasure.",
    "B": "use language to vent your anger.",
    "C": "adopt a defensive attitude.",
    "D": "make an effort to remain calm.",
    "answer": "D: make an effort to remain calm.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an internal source of feedback:?",
    "A": "Teachers",
    "B": "Yourself",
    "C": "Friends",
    "D": "Employers",
    "answer": "B: Yourself",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of violating a coworker's privacy in the workplace:?",
    "A": "Thomas changed the wording on Carrie's report with her approval.",
    "B": "Ruby saw that her coworkers were having a serious discussion, so she walked away.",
    "C": "Joe needed a pen, so he opened Ali's desk drawer to look for one while she was away.",
    "D": "Paige sent a personal email from her work computer to her friend Alan.",
    "answer": "C: Joe needed a pen, so he opened Ali's desk drawer to look for one while she was away.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about secondary dimensions of diversity:?",
    "A": "They are mental aptitudes.",
    "B": "They are physical traits.",
    "C": "They are determined by a person's subculture.",
    "D": "They can change over time.",
    "answer": "D: They can change over time.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During a staff meeting, Matthew says, \"In closing, I want to congratulate Shelby, who has been instrumental in landing the Feldman account. This account has the potential to greatly impac t our company's sales.\" Matthew is motivating an employee by",
    "A": "providing her with a monetary reward.",
    "B": "acknowledging her efforts.",
    "C": "giving her new job responsibilities.",
    "D": "supporting her ideas.",
    "answer": "B: acknowledging her efforts.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Frank has a good understanding of his own emotions. What component of emotional intell igence does Frank demonstrate?",
    "A": "Social management",
    "B": "Self-management",
    "C": "Social awareness",
    "D": "Self-awareness",
    "answer": "D: Self-awareness",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Collaborative relationships with colleagues from other departments are beneficial to the busine ss because they often",
    "A": "support highly competitive attitudes.",
    "B": "prevent workplace conflict.",
    "C": "generate innovative ideas.",
    "D": "facilitate independent behavior.",
    "answer": "C: generate innovative ideas.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "John recently expanded his business into another country to reach more of his target market. He was initially thrilled with his company's profits following the expansion-until he converted the money back to his domestic currency. At that point, he realized that the company made much less than he origina lly thought. What risk involved with international business did John experienc e?",
    "A": "International trade agreement changes",
    "B": "Foreign exchange rate fluctuations",
    "C": "Political unrest in foreign countries",
    "D": "The cost of international unionized labor",
    "answer": "B: Foreign exchange rate fluctuations",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of a checking account:?",
    "A": "Overdraft protection",
    "B": "Direct payroll deposit",
    "C": "Account balance requirement",
    "D": "Online transaction options",
    "answer": "C: Account balance requirement",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Incorrect information on an individual's credit report may hinder his/her ability to",
    "A": "earn interest on stock holdings.",
    "B": "withdraw money from a savings account.",
    "C": "pay monthly credit card balances.",
    "D": "obtain a bank loan.",
    "answer": "D: obtain a bank loan.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do businesses transfer risk?",
    "A": "Screen employee s",
    "B": "Implement security measures",
    "C": "Check for hazards",
    "D": "Obtain insurance",
    "answer": "D: Obtain insurance",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Emma is reviewing the sales budget in relation to the actual sales generated for a set time f rame. How is Emma using financial information in this situation?",
    "A": "To compare estimated performance with actual performance",
    "B": "To establish new quality standards and benchmarks",
    "C": "To identify external economic trends",
    "D": "To analyze the impact of aging accounts",
    "answer": "A: To compare estimated performance with actual performance",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When preparing her company's budget, Tatiana's manager told her that the company would be merging with another company. To maintain her ethics, Tatiana should?",
    "A": "report this information to the SEC.",
    "B": "make sure the merger benefits the public interest.",
    "C": "maintain her independence.",
    "D": "keep this information confidential.",
    "answer": "D: keep this information confidential.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are listed as long-term assets on a balance sheet:?",
    "A": "Capital equipment, mortgage, and inventory",
    "B": "Land, cash, and mortgage",
    "C": "Vehicles, insurance, and accounts payable",
    "D": "Buildings, vehicles, and capital equipment",
    "answer": "D: Buildings, vehicles, and capital equipment",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to a company's most recent statement of cash flows, its cash flow from operations for the mos t recent year was $1,375,400. The net cash used by investing was an outlay of $690,000. The net c ash spent on financing was $140,300. What was the company's free cash flow?",
    "A": "$686,400",
    "B": "$549,700",
    "C": "$545,100",
    "D": "$830,300",
    "answer": "C: $545,100",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following business trends affects human resources management:?",
    "A": "Lack of new technology",
    "B": "Costs of business going down",
    "C": "No restructuring",
    "D": "Globalization",
    "answer": "D: Globalization",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of receiving tacit knowledge:?",
    "A": "\"Shadowing\" a person in your desired career",
    "B": "Reading a history textbook",
    "C": "Listening to an instructor's lecture",
    "D": "Following a recipe",
    "answer": "A: \"Shadowing\" a person in your desired career",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bailey knows that she has more knowledge about digital marketing than anyone else on her team. She is reluctant to share her knowledge because she wants to give herself an advantage. This is an exampl e of how",
    "A": "sharing knowledge builds stronger relationships.",
    "B": "it is impossible to get ahead in your career if you share knowledge.",
    "C": "knowledge management prevents unethical behavior.",
    "D": "self-interest can prevent effective knowledge management.",
    "answer": "D: self-interest can prevent effective knowledge management.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Corsica Steel Mill has developed a new process to reduce the time it takes to complete a phase of production. To legally protect this new process from unauthorized use, the company should obtain a",
    "A": "trade name.",
    "B": "copyright.",
    "C": "trademark.",
    "D": "patent.",
    "answer": "D: patent.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following factors has the greatest effect on a consumer's buying behavior:?",
    "A": "Cultural influences",
    "B": "Situational influences",
    "C": "Individual influences",
    "D": "Social influences",
    "answer": "A: Cultural influences",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an ethical dilemma related to an employee providing information i n the workplace:?",
    "A": "A customer asks Kate to mail a complete product catalog and a comprehensive price list to his/her business.",
    "B": "Bob's new employer asks him to share confidential information about product-devel opment processes that his previous employer uses.",
    "C": "Melinda and two of her coworkers talk about their plans to work overtime next weekend.",
    "D": "Steven advises a customer that Simpson Electronics does not provide personal information to",
    "answer": "B: Bob's new employer asks him to share confidential information about product-devel opment processes that his previous employer uses.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Any business storing customers' personal banking account information is legally requir ed to",
    "A": "maintain the confidentiality of the stored information.",
    "B": "share the information with its competitors.",
    "C": "provide the information to the government for tax purposes.",
    "D": "provide affiliated banks access to the information.",
    "answer": "A: maintain the confidentiality of the stored information.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What technological component manages the computer's software and hardware?",
    "A": "Navigation key",
    "B": "Power supply",
    "C": "Operating system",
    "D": "Modem",
    "answer": "C: Operating system",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic common to all integrated software packages:?",
    "A": "Performs interrelated functions",
    "B": "Calculates break-even points",
    "C": "Requires minimal training",
    "D": "Includes forecasting tools",
    "answer": "A: Performs interrelated functions",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which component of project-management software helps project managers determine the length of time that a series of interdependent tasks will take to complete under various circumstances:?",
    "A": "Demonstration",
    "B": "Critical path",
    "C": "Presentation",
    "D": "Linear",
    "answer": "B: Critical path",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maxton Mart is being pressured by its vendors to pay for inventory it purchased more than 30 da ys ago. However, Maxton Mart has not received its accounts receivable from customers. What busine ss record has Maxton Mart failed to monitor successfully?",
    "A": "Balance sheet",
    "B": "Income statement",
    "C": "Cash flow",
    "D": "Open to buy",
    "answer": "C: Cash flow",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The owner of a business facility that has hazardous electrical wiring is likely to be fined for violating",
    "A": "affirmative-action initiatives.",
    "B": "federal trade laws.",
    "C": "local building codes.",
    "D": "electronic communication regulations.",
    "answer": "C: local building codes.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of employee pilferage:?",
    "A": "Hacking into a competitor's computer network to obtain trade secrets",
    "B": "Changing the amount specified on a check you prepare for the company with authorization",
    "C": "Installing personally owned software on your workplace computer",
    "D": "Padding an expense account",
    "answer": "D: Padding an expense account",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lily is the last employee to leave the building today. To reduce the risk of theft, Lily s hould __________ before she __________.",
    "A": "set the security alarm; locks the doors",
    "B": "turn off the lights; sets the security alarm",
    "C": "turn on the surveillance camera; adjusts the thermostat",
    "D": "adjust the thermostat; turns on the surveillance camera",
    "answer": "A: set the security alarm; locks the doors",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the most important factor to consider when prioritizing work tasks:?",
    "A": "Enjoyment of tasks",
    "B": "Due dates of tasks",
    "C": "Coworkers' opinions",
    "D": "Employee's aptitude",
    "answer": "B: Due dates of tasks",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When delegating work to their employees, managers should make sure to clearly articulate their?",
    "A": "preference for quantity of work over quality.",
    "B": "rules and consequences for breaking them.",
    "C": "punishment for staff that fail to meet the deadline.",
    "D": "desired outcomes for the project.",
    "answer": "D: desired outcomes for the project.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What the project will and will not include is called the?",
    "A": "plan.",
    "B": "scope.",
    "C": "risk.",
    "D": "quality.",
    "answer": "B: scope.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determining which tasks need to be performed and when they need to be completed is an im portant aspect of project",
    "A": "planning.",
    "B": "initiating.",
    "C": "executing.",
    "D": "closing.",
    "answer": "A: planning.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following do purchasing personnel try to obtain, along with the lowest possibl e price:?",
    "A": "Security",
    "B": "Loyalty",
    "C": "Quality",
    "D": "Publicity",
    "answer": "C: Quality",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When companies work with their vendors to develop mutually beneficial business arrangements, they are more likely to?",
    "A": "double their profit margins.",
    "B": "maintain long-term relationships.",
    "C": "experience vertical conflict.",
    "D": "experience horizontal conflict.",
    "answer": "B: maintain long-term relationships.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is most likely to happen if a purchaser negotiates lower prices for raw materials?",
    "A": "The company will be limited in which type of materials can be purchased.",
    "B": "The company will be able to purchase more materials and increase production.",
    "C": "Increases in productivity will lead to higher costs.",
    "D": "Communication processes will be improved.",
    "answer": "B: The company will be able to purchase more materials and increase production.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is a business most likely to place a straight reorder with a vendor?",
    "A": "To replenish its regularly-stocked items",
    "B": "To accommodate customers' unique requests",
    "C": "To order seasonal merchandise",
    "D": "To change the quantities of items that it routinely orders",
    "answer": "A: To replenish its regularly-stocked items",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why does a business keep stock on hand for resale?",
    "A": "So it can buy raw materials",
    "B": "So it can produce manufactured goods",
    "C": "To use it in business operations",
    "D": "To sell it to end users",
    "answer": "D: To sell it to end users",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should businesses do before negotiating with vendors?",
    "A": "Make minor concessions",
    "B": "Implement aggressive tactics",
    "C": "Assess vendors' strengths and weaknesses",
    "D": "Adopt a win-lose attitude",
    "answer": "C: Assess vendors' strengths and weaknesses",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Acceptance sampling is a part of statistical quality control that involves",
    "A": "identifying the cause of quality problems.",
    "B": "filling out control charts.",
    "C": "determining whether to approve or reject an entire batch of products.",
    "D": "painting a picture with descriptive statistics.",
    "answer": "C: determining whether to approve or reject an entire batch of products.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mitchell is reviewing internal data and proposals from several agencies to determine the b est course of action for implementing a major advertising campaign for his company. What is Mitchell analyzing?",
    "A": "Financial status",
    "B": "Operating schedule",
    "C": "Promotional needs",
    "D": "Human resources",
    "answer": "C: Promotional needs",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An Internet and cable provider is considering whether to implement a new process that would requir e its customer service agents to work the phone lines for 24 hours a day instead of the previous 12 hours a day. What type of factor will most likely impact the design of this new process?",
    "A": "Environmental",
    "B": "Regulatory",
    "C": "Technological",
    "D": "Human",
    "answer": "D: Human",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Supply chain networks encompass the flow and movement of __________ among __________.",
    "A": "classified information; protest groups",
    "B": "employees and customers; governments",
    "C": "government officials; Fortune 500 companies",
    "D": "materials and information; organizations",
    "answer": "D: materials and information; organizations",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An American car manufacturer exports many of its automobiles to Asia. A recent delivery to Chi na was detained at Chinese customs due to a miscommunication between the English-speaking barge op erator and the Mandarin-speaking shipyard receiver. This is an example of which of the following global supply chain issues:",
    "A": "Cultural conflicts",
    "B": "Accountability and compliance",
    "C": "Time zone differences",
    "D": "Language barriers",
    "answer": "D: Language barriers",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a company hold employees accountable for protecting digital assets?",
    "A": "Encryption software",
    "B": "An effective laptop security policy",
    "C": "Project management software",
    "D": "Background checks",
    "answer": "B: An effective laptop security policy",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Riley is working with a design firm on a promotional campaign. The designer gives her a USB drive with some possible layouts to review. To ensure she is protecting the customer data on her computer, Riley should",
    "A": "fire the design firm.",
    "B": "refuse to open the files.",
    "C": "delete customer information before opening it.",
    "D": "scan the drive for viruses before opening it.",
    "answer": "D: scan the drive for viruses before opening it.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When it gets noisy in her workspace, Olivia puts on her headphones and listens to soft m usic while she works. What principle of time management is Olivia following?",
    "A": "Dividing large projects into smaller parts",
    "B": "Knowing how she works best",
    "C": "Making the most of her down time",
    "D": "Focusing on personal goals rather than work tasks",
    "answer": "B: Knowing how she works best",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee who is meeting his/her employer's expe ctations:?",
    "A": "Tom spends the first half hour of the workday chatting with Kate.",
    "B": "Allison focuses on her work tasks so she can meet her deadlines.",
    "C": "Rachel sends a text message to her roommate during a meeting.",
    "D": "Calvin tells a customer about his issues with a difficult coworker.",
    "answer": "B: Allison focuses on her work tasks so she can meet her deadlines.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cameron supervises the transportation, storage, and handling of his company's products. Which type of business management and administration career does Cameron have?",
    "A": "Office management",
    "B": "Business analytics",
    "C": "Supply chain management",
    "D": "Human resources management",
    "answer": "C: Supply chain management",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What would be the best response to write on a job application form for the reason that you left your last job if you quit because you felt your supervisor was unfair?",
    "A": "Unable to get along with supervisor",
    "B": "Left for a better job",
    "C": "Unfair supervisor",
    "D": "Unpleasant working environment",
    "answer": "B: Left for a better job",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An organization's product goals often involve setting standards for",
    "A": "the variety of its goods and services.",
    "B": "behavior in the workplace.",
    "C": "expenses and income.",
    "D": "the target market's expectations.",
    "answer": "A: the variety of its goods and services.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the sequential order of a project's work breakdown structure:?",
    "A": "Subtask, task, and work assignment",
    "B": "Work assignment, task, and subtask",
    "C": "Task, subtask, and work assignment",
    "D": "Work assignment, subtask, and task",
    "answer": "B: Work assignment, task, and subtask",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a primary responsibility of the project manager during the execution phase of a project:?",
    "A": "Developing a list of work tasks",
    "B": "Assembling a steering committee",
    "C": "Keeping the project on track",
    "D": "Acquiring project supplies and equipment",
    "answer": "C: Keeping the project on track",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a project manager motivating a project team:?",
    "A": "Zoey sends an email requesting each team member provide her with a weekly ac tivity report.",
    "B": "Marcus tells Thomas that he might work more efficiently if he performed one task before another one.",
    "C": "Ryan advises Samantha that she will need to perform additional duties while Maggi e is on vacation.",
    "D": "Tamara recognizes how hard her team is working, so she provides lunch for the team members.",
    "answer": "D: Tamara recognizes how hard her team is working, so she provides lunch for the team members.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After providing the stakeholders with the project deliverables, Lisa analyzed and documented the project's actual results with the initial project goals. What did Lisa do?",
    "A": "Prepare a lessons-learned report",
    "B": "Conduct a post-implementation review",
    "C": "Develop a project-issues log",
    "D": "Compose final delivery instructions",
    "answer": "B: Conduct a post-implementation review",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a potential benefit of implementing continuous quality im provement processes:?",
    "A": "Decreased demand",
    "B": "Lower productivity",
    "C": "Increased revenue",
    "D": "Higher costs",
    "answer": "C: Increased revenue",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Using computer-data backup procedures on a regular basis reduces a company's level of risk becau se the process",
    "A": "detects noncompliance issues.",
    "B": "prevents hackers from accessing the computer system.",
    "C": "saves information when computer failures occur.",
    "D": "allows employees to use many applications.",
    "answer": "C: saves information when computer failures occur.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What can a business do if it is exposed to risks that commercial insurance companies do not co ver?",
    "A": "Establish a risk-management committee",
    "B": "Acquire a professional associati on",
    "C": "Create a trade union",
    "D": "Form a captive insurance company",
    "answer": "D: Form a captive insurance company",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following levels of managers spend most of their time staffing, directing, and co ntrolling the day-to-day activities of the business:?",
    "A": "Mid-level",
    "B": "First-line",
    "C": "Executive",
    "D": "Regional",
    "answer": "B: First-line",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an advantage of managerial planning?",
    "A": "Reduces uncertainty",
    "B": "Eliminates errors",
    "C": "Decreases the need to delegate work",
    "D": "Lessens the need to monitor employees",
    "answer": "A: Reduces uncertainty",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What management function is responsible for coordinating resources in ways that maximi ze efficiency?",
    "A": "Organizing",
    "B": "Staffing",
    "C": "Directing",
    "D": "Controlling",
    "answer": "A: Organizing",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which task in the staffing process ensures that employees are knowledgeable and productive?",
    "A": "Determining need",
    "B": "Recruiting",
    "C": "Training and developing",
    "D": "Developing compensation plans",
    "answer": "C: Training and developing",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What occurs during the first stage of the change-management life cycle?",
    "A": "Organizations carry out a strategic plan for implementing desired change.",
    "B": "Organizations engage in dialogue to determine how to best implement change.",
    "C": "Organizations agree on a strategic plan for implementing the desired change.",
    "D": "Organizations identify and communicate the need for change to employees.",
    "answer": "D: Organizations identify and communicate the need for change to employees.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jon sues his former employer for harassment. In what situation would the employer be likely to offer Jon a settlement?",
    "A": "The employer wants the case to go to court.",
    "B": "The employer knows it will be able to win the case.",
    "C": "The employer does not think it will be able to win the case.",
    "D": "Jon does not think he will be able to win the case.",
    "answer": "C: The employer does not think it will be able to win the case.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following words most accurately describes arbitration:?",
    "A": "Private",
    "B": "Nonconsensual",
    "C": "Biased",
    "D": "Temporary",
    "answer": "A: Private",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To be reimbursed for business expenses, Luke must obtain and complete an expense-reimbursement form, attach the original transaction receipts to the completed form, and submit the documentation to his manager for approval. What is Luke doing?",
    "A": "Following company procedures",
    "B": "Developing company policies",
    "C": "Evaluating company feedback",
    "D": "Assessing company guidelines",
    "answer": "A: Following company procedures",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To use oral communication effectively, you need to",
    "A": "pronounce your words correctly.",
    "B": "impress your listeners.",
    "C": "know your listeners.",
    "D": "distract your listeners' attention.",
    "answer": "A: pronounce your words correctly.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is typically the primary purpose of an introduction during a presentation:?",
    "A": "To share a funny story",
    "B": "To provide supporting details",
    "C": "To summarize the talk",
    "D": "To gain the audience's attention",
    "answer": "D: To gain the audience's attention",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a key to effective note-taking?",
    "A": "Active listening",
    "B": "Capturing details",
    "C": "Creative thinking",
    "D": "Using an outline",
    "answer": "A: Active listening",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a guideline for writing clear instructions for your coworkers:?",
    "A": "Write complex, lengthy statements.",
    "B": "Write from your supervisor's perspective.",
    "C": "Understand the process you are explaining.",
    "D": "Confine the instructions to one page.",
    "answer": "C: Understand the process you are explaining.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The opening sentences of an effective business letter should",
    "A": "avoid specific details.",
    "B": "be completely impersonal.",
    "C": "be formal.",
    "D": "go right to the point.",
    "answer": "D: go right to the point.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When developing an analytical report about a problem that the business is facing, the writer should conclude the report by?",
    "A": "defining the issue.",
    "B": "describing the research techniques.",
    "C": "recommending solutions.",
    "D": "providing crucial background information.",
    "answer": "C: recommending solutions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Liam wrote and submitted a report to management describing relationships between actions and the probable results of those actions. What type of research report has Liam written?",
    "A": "Cause and effect",
    "B": "Interpretive",
    "C": "Jury of executive opinion",
    "D": "Argumentative",
    "answer": "A: Cause and effect",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While Mark is presenting his status report during a staff meeting, Danielle has a question about something he says. What should Danielle do?",
    "A": "Ask the question after Mark has finished speaking",
    "B": "Wait until the next meeting to ask her question",
    "C": "Interrupt Mark so she can ask her question right away",
    "D": "Wait to see if another participant has the same question",
    "answer": "A: Ask the question after Mark has finished speaking",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business strives to make every customer experience a positive one, it is remembering its?",
    "A": "history.",
    "B": "internal customers.",
    "C": "competition.",
    "D": "touchpoints.",
    "answer": "D: touchpoints.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would be the most likely cause of customer complaints:?",
    "A": "Product quality",
    "B": "Institutional ads",
    "C": "Extended hours",
    "D": "Price reductions",
    "answer": "A: Product quality",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a capital good:?",
    "A": "A delivery truck",
    "B": "Iron ore",
    "C": "A truck driver",
    "D": "Weather conditions",
    "answer": "A: A delivery truck",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Telford Pharmaceutical Company is concer ned that proposed regulatory changes may negatively impact its research and development initiatives, profitability, long-term growth, and the well-being of patients who may benefit from using its products. What can the company do to influence legislation a nd protect its interests?",
    "A": "Hire an estate attorney",
    "B": "Veto the legislation",
    "C": "Engage in lobbying efforts",
    "D": "Sign a warrant",
    "answer": "C: Engage in lobbying efforts",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the disadvantages of private enterprise is",
    "A": "unequal distribution of income.",
    "B": "limited government control.",
    "C": "pricing system.",
    "D": "competition.",
    "answer": "A: unequal distribution of income.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During an economic recession, the best way for consumers to help expand the economy is by",
    "A": "saving money.",
    "B": "spending money.",
    "C": "earning money.",
    "D": "collecting money.",
    "answer": "B: spending money.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The category of GDP called gross private domestic investment includes",
    "A": "all purchases of capital goods.",
    "B": "all exports of goods and services.",
    "C": "purchases made by private individuals.",
    "D": "inventories held over from previous years.",
    "answer": "A: all purchases of capital goods.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An American businessperson in London was offered a \"cuppa\" by the company's receptionist. The businessperson did not know that the receptionist was offering a cup of tea. This is an example of",
    "A": "a language barrier.",
    "B": "a business subculture.",
    "C": "being uneducated.",
    "D": "economic differences.",
    "answer": "A: a language barrier.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following behaviors matches with the value of kindness:?",
    "A": "Always telling the truth",
    "B": "Encouraging others who are sad",
    "C": "Getting a job promotion",
    "D": "Avoiding difficult tasks",
    "answer": "B: Encouraging others who are sad",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding initiative:?",
    "A": "People with initiative must usually be prodded into doing things.",
    "B": "Possessing initiative is unimportant in business occupations.",
    "C": "Increased initiative usually brings increased job responsibility.",
    "D": "Initiative should be demonstrated only at your place of employment.",
    "answer": "C: Increased initiative usually brings increased job responsibility.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one of the main reasons that employees behave unethically?",
    "A": "To become managers",
    "B": "To create positive customer relations",
    "C": "To do what everyone else does",
    "D": "To obtain publicity",
    "answer": "C: To do what everyone else does",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ian is planning a picnic even though it's cloudy because he doesn't think it is likely to rain. Ian has likely considered the __________ of rain.",
    "A": "probability",
    "B": "forecast",
    "C": "magnitude",
    "D": "severity",
    "answer": "A: probability",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To take responsibility for your decisions and actions, it's important to build your self-confidence and",
    "A": "work portfolio.",
    "B": "grades.",
    "C": "self-esteem.",
    "D": "physical fitness.",
    "answer": "C: self-esteem.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do positive people enjoy good personal relationships?",
    "A": "They are kind and considerate.",
    "B": "They're usually in a bad mood.",
    "C": "They usually put themselves first.",
    "D": "They typically have good personal-hygiene habits.",
    "answer": "A: They are kind and considerate.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jeremy listened to his friend Mike's description of a problem Mike recently had at work and said, \"It's easy to see why you are so upset.\" What empathetic trait does Jeremy have?",
    "A": "Understanding",
    "B": "Honesty",
    "C": "Sharing",
    "D": "Open-mindedness",
    "answer": "A: Understanding",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Organizing your sock drawer, throwing a party, and building a bookshelf are examples of",
    "A": "projec ts.",
    "B": "goals.",
    "C": "product ideas.",
    "D": "planning methods.",
    "answer": "A: projec ts.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a leader takes ownership of a problem, makes sure it is fixed, and takes steps to prevent it from happening again, s/he is demonstrating",
    "A": "flexibility.",
    "B": "adaptability.",
    "C": "responsibility.",
    "D": "social awareness.",
    "answer": "C: responsibility.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following examples describes an ethical leader practicing persistence and patience:?",
    "A": "A team captain yells at her teammates to motivate them.",
    "B": "Marie encourages her team not to take shortcuts to achieve results.",
    "C": "Your teacher always grades and returns tests on time.",
    "D": "Jalen spends time giving back to organizations in his community.",
    "answer": "B: Marie encourages her team not to take shortcuts to achieve results.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The main reason why people lose their jobs is that the y",
    "A": "take too many days off work.",
    "B": "complain about the unsatisfactory pay.",
    "C": "do not get along with their coworkers.",
    "D": "are not able to perform all job tasks.",
    "answer": "C: do not get along with their coworkers.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important to be honest about the time commitment when interviewing potential empl oyees for a new business because",
    "A": "entrepreneurs shouldn't hire employees with busy personal lives.",
    "B": "employees who are overburdened are unlikely to stay with the company.",
    "C": "being honest should weed out the people who aren't dedicated to the job.",
    "D": "employees are not legally allowed to work more than 40 hours/week.",
    "answer": "B: employees who are overburdened are unlikely to stay with the company.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For an investment to yield positive results at the end of the investment period, the earnings should",
    "A": "be accrued on a debt security.",
    "B": "grow by at least 10%.",
    "C": "exceed the rate of inflation.",
    "D": "be documented appropriately.",
    "answer": "C: exceed the rate of inflation.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When making a budget for next year, Antonio allocated money for his college tuition, his apartment, and food. What is another financial need that he should include in his budget?",
    "A": "Fitness classes",
    "B": "Tickets for sporting events",
    "C": "Apartment decorations",
    "D": "Transportation",
    "answer": "D: Transportation",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you do not keep up with the balance of your checking account, you might",
    "A": "challenge the bank's authority.",
    "B": "have your identity stolen.",
    "C": "prevent fraudulent charges.",
    "D": "incur fees and penalties.",
    "answer": "D: incur fees and penalties.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To avoid accumulating unmanageable debt, you should",
    "A": "purchase expensive items using credit.",
    "B": "avoid buying anything except necessities.",
    "C": "pay your credit card balance in full.",
    "D": "spend your monthly paycheck immediat ely.",
    "answer": "C: pay your credit card balance in full.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Accountants are legally required to follow established guidelines when preparing financial documents to ensure that the information presented is",
    "A": "clear and consistent.",
    "B": "transparent and subjective.",
    "C": "subjective and consistent.",
    "D": "adjusted and clear.",
    "answer": "A: clear and consistent.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of money is recorded in the cash receipts column of a cash flow statement?",
    "A": "Credit",
    "B": "Cost of goods",
    "C": "Collected",
    "D": "Expenses",
    "answer": "C: Collected",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to the statement of cash flows in a company's annual report, its cash flow from operations last year was $5,260,300 and its capital expenditures were $980,200. What was the company's free cash flow?",
    "A": "$1,863,391",
    "B": "$4,280,100",
    "C": "$5,397,164",
    "D": "$6,240,500",
    "answer": "B: $4,280,100",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who often helps orient new employees by answering their routine questi ons during their first few days on the job?",
    "A": "Top-level managers",
    "B": "Coworkers",
    "C": "Recruiters",
    "D": "Human resources staff",
    "answer": "B: Coworkers",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because knowledge is so valuable, it needs to be",
    "A": "managed.",
    "B": "unrestricted.",
    "C": "delegated.",
    "D": "prohibited.",
    "answer": "A: managed.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As part of it s knowledge-management program, a business uses a special computer application to help detect and record unexpected issues that occur during the production process. This program allows many staff members to obtain and share information to resolve the probl em quickly. This is an example of a business effectively using",
    "A": "mind-mapping software.",
    "B": "incident-management software.",
    "C": "a public domain database.",
    "D": "an accounting database.",
    "answer": "B: incident-management software.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ralph hosts a video conference about a trade show he recently attended. Which of the following knowledge management processes is Ralph practicing:",
    "A": "Refinement",
    "B": "Acquisition",
    "C": "Creation",
    "D": "Sharing",
    "answer": "D: Sharing",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which function of marketing determines how much gross profit a business will make on a good or service?",
    "A": "Risk management",
    "B": "Channel management",
    "C": "Promotion",
    "D": "Pricing",
    "answer": "D: Pricing",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way for businesses to obtain needed information efficiently is to",
    "A": "read a book.",
    "B": "schedule an interview.",
    "C": "access a database.",
    "D": "contact a competitor.",
    "answer": "C: access a database.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a trend in information management:?",
    "A": "Fewer electronic documents",
    "B": "Increased use of outsourcing",
    "C": "Decreased competition",
    "D": "Less incoming information",
    "answer": "B: Increased use of outsourcing",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monitors, keyboards, and hard drives are examples of computer",
    "A": "servers.",
    "B": "hardware.",
    "C": "dashboards.",
    "D": "standards.",
    "answer": "B: hardware.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Adian is conducting online research for a marketing project at work. What web-based tool will help Adian save and organize the websites that contain the relevant information he needs for his final report?",
    "A": "Personal intranet connection",
    "B": "Notebook with color-coded dividers",
    "C": "Word-processing memo template",
    "D": "Browser bookmarking applications",
    "answer": "D: Browser bookmarking applications",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of employees using groupware computer applications:?",
    "A": "Dan, Kara, and Simon review their departments' budgets, which are saved as different computer-spreadsheets files.",
    "B": "Craig, Tessa, and Lily use presentation software to guide a group discussion about their research project.",
    "C": "Kelli, Juan, and Phil can access and make changes to the company production schedule from their home computers.",
    "D": "Michelle, Jeff, and Aubrey use the same desktop-publishing program to create advertisements",
    "answer": "C: Kelli, Juan, and Phil can access and make changes to the company production schedule from their home computers.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following strategies can help make data change easier:?",
    "A": "Rolling out data changes during a busy time of year",
    "B": "Ignoring errors during implementation",
    "C": "Informing staff that data changes will continually occur",
    "D": "Communicating the benefits of the data change",
    "answer": "D: Communicating the benefits of the data change",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "By maintaining customer records, a business can determine the",
    "A": "needs and product preferences of its customers.",
    "B": "goals and motivation of its major competitors.",
    "C": "performance levels of its marketing staff.",
    "D": "productivity levels of its operational efforts.",
    "answer": "A: needs and product preferences of its customers.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often monitor internal inventory records to obtain the information needed to",
    "A": "organize new displays.",
    "B": "plan special sales.",
    "C": "evaluate vendors.",
    "D": "create safety rules.",
    "answer": "B: plan special sales.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To maintain a hazard-free work environment, local regulations might require businesses to undergo",
    "A": "security analyses.",
    "B": "accounting audits.",
    "C": "safety inspections.",
    "D": "ethics training.",
    "answer": "C: safety inspections.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important in project planning to build in a safety net, or padding, when identifying resources?",
    "A": "To plan for the unexpected",
    "B": "To find substitutes",
    "C": "To try to cut corners",
    "D": "To obtain financial support",
    "answer": "A: To plan for the unexpected",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When managing projects, which of the following is an important activity:?",
    "A": "Changing objectives",
    "B": "Tracking deadlines",
    "C": "Following directions",
    "D": "Obeying orders",
    "answer": "B: Tracking deadlines",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the probable outcome when a producer purchases inferior parts for its products to cut costs?",
    "A": "Customer dis satisfaction and increased business",
    "B": "Customer satisfaction and repeat business",
    "C": "Customer goodwill and loss of business",
    "D": "Customer dissatisfaction and loss of business",
    "answer": "D: Customer dissatisfaction and loss of business",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When developing a request for quotation (RFQ) for prospective vendors, a business should always include?",
    "A": "prices and a purchase order.",
    "B": "specifications and deadlines.",
    "C": "guidelines and discounts.",
    "D": "statistics and a checklist.",
    "answer": "B: specifications and deadlines.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What attitude would be most likely to support long-term relationships between businesses and their suppliers?",
    "A": "Reflective",
    "B": "Creative",
    "C": "Influential",
    "D": "Collaborative",
    "answer": "D: Collaborative",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the Frederick Company has space limitations in its warehouse, it needs to have a shelving unit custom-made. What type of order is the Frederick Company likely to place with the shelving manufacturer?",
    "A": "Special",
    "B": "Open",
    "C": "Blanket",
    "D": "Reorder",
    "answer": "A: Special",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are examples of raw materials that a business might keep on hand for production:?",
    "A": "Minerals, tables, leather, and paper",
    "B": "Leather, bolts, stapler, and ore",
    "C": "Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "D": "Oil, grain, shoes, and household cleanser",
    "answer": "C: Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before a business begins negotiating with a vendor, it carefully plans the specific points or terms that it is willing to give up that will benefit the vendor. What is the business planning?",
    "A": "Desired shipping terms",
    "B": "The vendor's purchasing power",
    "C": "Targeted discount rates",
    "D": "Its concession strategy",
    "answer": "D: Its concession strategy",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do most businesses use some type of quality-control method at work?",
    "A": "To organize employees",
    "B": "To minimize errors",
    "C": "To attract vendors",
    "D": "To guarantee safety",
    "answer": "B: To minimize errors",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following expenses should Charlene categorize as a fixed cost:?",
    "A": "Commissions",
    "B": "Delivery charges",
    "C": "Cost of goods sold",
    "D": "Rent",
    "answer": "D: Rent",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an activity that falls under supply chain management:?",
    "A": "Building relationships with vendors",
    "B": "Creating advertising campaigns",
    "C": "Forecasting sales",
    "D": "Hiring new employees",
    "answer": "A: Building relationships with vendors",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a key aspect of risk managem ent:?",
    "A": "Setting product prices",
    "B": "Preparing operational budgets",
    "C": "Determining appropriate advertising media",
    "D": "Staying in compliance with laws and regulations",
    "answer": "D: Staying in compliance with laws and regulations",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does process thinking help organizations?",
    "A": "Assists them in separating work between departments",
    "B": "Enables them to find out who to blame for issues",
    "C": "Helps them avoid documenting workflow",
    "D": "Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "answer": "D: Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its business processes is",
    "A": "desire for growth.",
    "B": "competition.",
    "C": "low employee morale.",
    "D": "high operating costs.",
    "answer": "B: competition.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Online shipment tracking is one example of __________ affecting supply chain management.",
    "A": "technology",
    "B": "globalization",
    "C": "economic downturns",
    "D": "production changes",
    "answer": "A: technology",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for companies to make inventories of their digital information?",
    "A": "So that the information is readily accessible when it is needed",
    "B": "Because most employees don't use their computers wisely",
    "C": "To prevent unethical IT professionals from stealing company data",
    "D": "So that the company can keep tabs on what employees are doing online",
    "answer": "A: So that the information is readily accessible when it is needed",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements about protecting digital customer data is true:?",
    "A": "A company's protection of data has little impact on the customer's perception of the company.",
    "B": "Protecting digital customer data is a responsibility of the IT department.",
    "C": "Data protection strategies should be reevaluated often.",
    "D": "Protecting digital customer data is only necessary for large businesses.",
    "answer": "C: Data protection strategies should be reevaluated often.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a good way for an employee to make sure that all essential tasks are completed each day:?",
    "A": "Prioritize tasks",
    "B": "Complete routine tasks first",
    "C": "Seek help from coworkers",
    "D": "Work as fast as possible",
    "answer": "A: Prioritize tasks",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would be a short-term financial goal:?",
    "A": "Getting a promotion within five years",
    "B": "Starting your own business",
    "C": "Walking a mile every day",
    "D": "Saving enough to buy a c oncert ticket",
    "answer": "D: Saving enough to buy a c oncert ticket",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Emilio works in office management. Which of the following would likely be one of his job responsibilities:",
    "A": "Packaging and distributing warehouse orders",
    "B": "Helping his office run faster and more efficiently",
    "C": "Helping customers decide how to invest their money",
    "D": "Creating a marketing plan for a new product",
    "answer": "B: Helping his office run faster and more efficiently",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of personal information that should be included in a r\u00e9sum\u00e9:?",
    "A": "Year of graduation",
    "B": "Telephone number",
    "C": "Rate of pay",
    "D": "Names of parents",
    "answer": "B: Telephone number",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ABC Corp. shu ts down its office for a few days each winter to protect its employees from any weather-related accidents. This is an example of a rule related to",
    "A": "health and safety.",
    "B": "discrimination.",
    "C": "conflicts of interest.",
    "D": "insubordination.",
    "answer": "A: health and safety.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Prater Corporation wants to expand its market share by 6% next year. What type of goal has the company set?",
    "A": "Financial",
    "B": "Ideological",
    "C": "Organizational",
    "D": "Input",
    "answer": "C: Organizational",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What question should the purpose statement of a project's statement of work (SOW) answer?",
    "A": "What materials do we need to do this project?",
    "B": "What is this project going to produce?",
    "C": "Why are we doing this project?",
    "D": "Who will carry out this project?",
    "answer": "C: Why are we doing this project?",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Alicia is creating a resource that includes entries for each component of how her project will be organized and run, including definitions, deliverables, associated activities, and milestones. Alicia is making a",
    "A": "resource breakdown structure.",
    "B": "scope statement.",
    "C": "work breakdown structure dictionary.",
    "D": "project charter.",
    "answer": "C: work breakdown structure dictionary.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a project manager delegating responsibility to a project team member:?",
    "A": "Stan asks Joanna and Tom for suggestions to improve process efficiency.",
    "B": "Bill tells Peter that he needs to remember to include a cover sheet with his TPS report.",
    "C": "Nina advises Milton that he is responsible for preparing the team's weekly status report.",
    "D": "Anne determines that Bob has the desired organizational skills to be on the project team.",
    "answer": "C: Nina advises Milton that he is responsible for preparing the team's weekly status report.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before closing a project, the project manager, team, and stakeholders must agree that the",
    "A": "objectives have been achieved.",
    "B": "resources have been used efficiently.",
    "C": "project has stayed within budget.",
    "D": "members are ready to resume their regular duties.",
    "answer": "A: objectives have been achieved.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Six Sigma is a popular quality-management",
    "A": "requirement.",
    "B": "questionnaire.",
    "C": "methodology.",
    "D": "technique.",
    "answer": "C: methodology.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the potential benefit to a business that continuously takes action to improve the quality of it s goods and services?",
    "A": "Increased product options",
    "B": "Higher demand",
    "C": "Increased premiums",
    "D": "Higher costs",
    "answer": "B: Higher demand",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a company's leaders encourage ethical behavior in risk management?",
    "A": "Act ethically themselves",
    "B": "Hire risk managers",
    "C": "Discourage risk-taking",
    "D": "Involve middle managers",
    "answer": "A: Act ethically themselves",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Wellston Industries wants to compare a current business situation with a target situation. Which of the following tools will help Wellston obtain the information that it wants:",
    "A": "Critical path study",
    "B": "Mind map",
    "C": "Decision tree",
    "D": "Gap analysis",
    "answer": "D: Gap analysis",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An automobile manufacturer in Country A purchases parts from a factory in Country B. When Country B suffers a massive earthquake, the automobile manufacturer is forced to put produ ction on hold until it can find another factory to supply the parts. What type of risk does this situation illustrate?",
    "A": "Health and safety",
    "B": "Employee",
    "C": "Political",
    "D": "Environmental",
    "answer": "D: Environmental",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about managers:?",
    "A": "Managers allow employees to set the organizational standards.",
    "B": "Managers must be able to do their employees' jobs.",
    "C": "Managers decide how to use the business's resources.",
    "D": "Managers usually train the employees to do the work.",
    "answer": "C: Managers decide how to use the business's resources.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Managers need to form relationships with employees and understand human behavior. This is an example of which characteristic of directing?",
    "A": "Continuous",
    "B": "Executive",
    "C": "Creative",
    "D": "People-focused",
    "answer": "D: People-focused",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of managerial control would a company use to measure the financial success of various products, territories, customer groups, distribution channels, and order sizes?",
    "A": "Annual plan C. Strategic",
    "B": "Profitability D. Efficiency 99. Every month, a technology company has all-staff meetings in which employees team up and brainstorm new ideas together. Many of these ideas lead to innovative new products. This is an example of how __________ helps organizations innovate and change. A. customer service",
    "C": "collaboration B. training",
    "D": "resilience",
    "answer": "B: Profitability D. Efficiency 99. Every month, a technology company has all-staff meetings in which employees team up and brainstorm new ideas together. Many of these ideas lead to innovative new products. This is an example of how __________ helps organizations innovate and change. A. customer service",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Many organizational changes fail because",
    "A": "managers give their employees too much time to adjust to changes.",
    "B": "big changes cannot be executed throughout entire companies.",
    "C": "most people are resistant to change.",
    "D": "companies do not properly execute the change-management lifecycle.",
    "answer": "D: companies do not properly execute the change-management lifecycle.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Creditors are required to inform consumers about __________ before offering them a credit product.",
    "A": "their credit scores C. the state of the economy",
    "B": "fees and penalties D. the company's history 3. One of the most common reasons why a defendant may choose to settle a legal dispute out of cour t is to A. earn the respect of a jury.",
    "C": "turn the ordeal into a public spectacle. B. prove the defendant's innocence.",
    "D": "avoid the high costs of going to trial.",
    "answer": "B: fees and penalties D. the company's history 3. One of the most common reasons why a defendant may choose to settle a legal dispute out of cour t is to A. earn the respect of a jury.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following steps in the civil litigation process typically comes first:?",
    "A": "Pleadings C. Trial",
    "B": "Discovery D. Appeal 5. What should you do first when someone gives you a set of written instructions to follow? A. Read the instructions in their entirety. B. Comprehend what the instructions are telling you.",
    "C": "Reference the instructions when you get stuck.",
    "D": "Skim the instructions for a general overview.",
    "answer": "A: Pleadings C. Trial",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An accounts receivable employee monitors delinquent accounts by placing them into three folders-30 days past due, 60 days past due, and 90 days past due. How has the employee organized the information?",
    "A": "Name C. Location",
    "B": "Invoice number D. Time 9. Which of the following message closings is the most appropriate to use for a businessperson who is sending formal email correspondence: A. Affectionately",
    "C": "Greetings B. THX",
    "D": "Regards",
    "answer": "D: Regards",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mitchell is writing an email to a company asking for some information that he needs to complete a research project. What is the most effective way to close the message?",
    "A": "I wish you the bes t of luck. C. I appreciate your help with this issue.",
    "B": "I need this information ASAP. D. I apologize for the inconvenience. 11. In a detailed document, Rachel explains the possible implications of implementing a cooperative advertising program for her employer's major customers. In this situation, Rachel developed a A. request for proposal.",
    "C": "sales analysis. B. troubleshooting proposal.",
    "D": "feasibility report.",
    "answer": "C: sales analysis. B. troubleshooting proposal.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements would be placed in the introductory section of a research report:?",
    "A": "Based on the previously stated findings, it is recommended that the XYZ Company revise its operating budget.",
    "B": "The purpose of this study is to determine why sales have been decreasing for three consecutive quarters.",
    "C": "The survey c onsisted of 250,600 respondents from the northern region of the country.",
    "D": "The statistics indicate that the business is losing up to 15% of its market share to new",
    "answer": "B: The purpose of this study is to determine why sales have been decreasing for three consecutive quarters.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which type of communication is being used when a salesperson sends a m essage to the store manager?",
    "A": "Lateral C. Upward",
    "B": "Downward D. Diagonal 14. What might result if a business fails to maintain positive customer/client relations? A. Decrease in sales",
    "C": "Loss of advertisers B. Reduction in assets",
    "D": "Lowering of goals",
    "answer": "C: Loss of advertisers B. Reduction in assets",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding data integrity and security:?",
    "A": "It can be helpful to hire a data security specialist.",
    "B": "Businesses are not allowed to sell customer information.",
    "C": "Data security programs are strictly monitored by the government.",
    "D": "All businesses have similar data security needs.",
    "answer": "A: It can be helpful to hire a data security specialist.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Items that are used to produce goods and services are",
    "A": "unlimited resources. C. competing wants.",
    "B": "noneconomic resources. D. economic resources. 17. Which of the following are results, or outputs, of the production activities of a business: A. Goods or services",
    "C": "Raw materials B. Capital resources",
    "D": "Means of production",
    "answer": "D: Means of production",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the biggest barriers that separates countries/regions is",
    "A": "brain drain. C. methods of travel.",
    "B": "technology. D. language. 19. To develop new products that accommodate changing markets, a business should A. review its profit margins on a continuous basis. B. adopt a laissez-faire organizational structure.",
    "C": "develop licensi ng programs with business partners.",
    "D": "implement innovative management practices.",
    "answer": "D: implement innovative management practices.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Leonardo's is considering opening a second location in a nearby city. The owners are concerned with the competition they might face from a business that is not quite like theirs, but also competes for scarce consumer dollars. What form of competition are they facing?",
    "A": "Indirect C. Direct",
    "B": "Price D. Nonprice 21. Increased export trade might result in an increase in A. sales taxes.",
    "C": "inflationary trends. B. employment opportunities.",
    "D": "interest rates.",
    "answer": "A: Indirect C. Direct",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the difference between a visa and a passport?",
    "A": "A passport is a supplement to a visa.",
    "B": "A visa is a supplement to a passport.",
    "C": "Visas are for business; passports are for leisure.",
    "D": "Passports are for business; visas are for leisure.",
    "answer": "B: A visa is a supplement to a passport.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an accurate way of describing someone with emotional intelligence:?",
    "A": "A person who ignores his/her emotions",
    "B": "A person who becomes emotional very easily",
    "C": "A person who recognizes and manages emotions",
    "D": "A person who has a high IQ",
    "answer": "C: A person who recognizes and manages emotions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You have just had an experience that greatly reduced your level of self-esteem. Which of the following is a constructive action to take:",
    "A": "Wish it hadn't happened. C. Forget about it.",
    "B": "Blame someone else for what happened. D. Analyze what happened. 25. Which of the following is a characteristic of self-confidence: A. Willing to take positive risks",
    "C": "Dismissing compliments B. Having a suspicious attitude",
    "D": "Critic izing others' ideas",
    "answer": "D: Critic izing others' ideas",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you are considering the possible consequences of each decision you could make, you are",
    "A": "focusing on creativity. C. assessing risk.",
    "B": "staying calm. D. practicing mindfulness. 27. An example of a social change would be a change in A. highway speed limits.",
    "C": "interest rates. B. hair and clothing styles.",
    "D": "product-safety standards.",
    "answer": "C: interest rates. B. hair and clothing styles.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a basic belief that you must have so you can start to be assertive:?",
    "A": "You should always respond to the needs of others.",
    "B": "You have the right to try to force your ideas on others.",
    "C": "Your thoughts, feelings, ideas, and opinions are important.",
    "D": "Your needs come first in all situations.",
    "answer": "C: Your thoughts, feelings, ideas, and opinions are important.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your boss tells employees not to use their phones in front of cust omers, but s/he is constantly texting and checking social media. Your boss is ineffective at modeling ethical behavior because s/he isn't",
    "A": "providing feedback. C. making ethics relevant to employees.",
    "B": "being consistent. D. communicating clearly and openly. 30. Which of the following best describes what it means to have a vision: A. Encouraging others to achieve their dreams B. Setting clear objectives that you want to achieve",
    "C": "Being clear-minded and focused at all tim es",
    "D": "Having a mental picture of the ideal future",
    "answer": "B: being consistent. D. communicating clearly and openly. 30. Which of the following best describes what it means to have a vision: A. Encouraging others to achieve their dreams B. Setting clear objectives that you want to achieve",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sarah works in a large corporation and has daily contact with many different types of people from a variety of backgrounds. What is one technique that she can use in order to treat all of these peop le with respect?",
    "A": "Stereotype coworkers C. React defensively",
    "B": "Discuss controversial topics D. Use empathy and tact 32. Conflicting viewpoints at work can lead to A. increased creativity.",
    "C": "more discrimination. B. heightened aggression.",
    "D": "decreased productivity.",
    "answer": "D: decreased productivity.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Integrity means acting with",
    "A": "humility. C. leadership skills.",
    "B": "honesty. D. a sense of humor. 34. Entrepreneurs who hold themselves to high moral standards from the very beginning A. set the bar low for other companies.",
    "C": "set their businesses up for success. B. are destined to go bankrupt.",
    "D": "are unlikely to make a profit.",
    "answer": "B: honesty. D. a sense of humor. 34. Entrepreneurs who hold themselves to high moral standards from the very beginning A. set the bar low for other companies.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a name for a medium of exchange accepted and backed by the government as payment for goods and services:?",
    "A": "Certific ates of deposit C. Money market accounts",
    "B": "Credit cards D. Currency 36. By developing a personal budget, individuals will be able to review their A. bank statements.",
    "C": "investment plans. B. insurance policy coverage.",
    "D": "spending patterns.",
    "answer": "D: spending patterns.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determining your personal net worth means finding out how much money you would have if you",
    "A": "sold all of your assets and paid off all your debts.",
    "B": "paid all of your debts and purchased more assets.",
    "C": "earned twice as much money as you made this year.",
    "D": "sold all of your assets and took on more debts.",
    "answer": "A: sold all of your assets and paid off all your debts.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why should you pay your credit card bill in full each month?",
    "A": "When you pay in full, annual fees don't apply.",
    "B": "When you pay in full, you can avoid accumulating interest.",
    "C": "When you pay in full, finance charges are applied.",
    "D": "When you pay in full, your credit score will go down over time.",
    "answer": "B: When you pay in full, you can avoid accumulating interest.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To protect yourself against identity theft, you should",
    "A": "write down all of your important passwords on paper.",
    "B": "throw away credit card receipts in public trash cans.",
    "C": "maintain at least six different credit cards in your name.",
    "D": "avoid providing sensitive information via telephone.",
    "answer": "D: avoid providing sensitive information via telephone.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to be a consequence for a business that neglects its financial information:?",
    "A": "A business might exceed its budget. C. The target market might not be reached.",
    "B": "Salespeople might not be prepared. D. Competitors will perform better. 41. Effective budgets should always be A. inflexible.",
    "C": "evaluated. B. optimistic.",
    "D": "secretive.",
    "answer": "A: A business might exceed its budget. C. The target market might not be reached.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to a company's most recent statement of cash flows, its cash flow from operations for the most recent year was $1,375,400. The net cash used by investing was an outlay of $690,000. The net cash spent on financ ing was $140,300. What was the company's free cash flow?",
    "A": "$549,700 C. $686,400",
    "B": "$545,100 D. $830,300 43. Making employment information available to job seekers in many locations at the same time is one way that computer technology impacts A. business development.",
    "C": "corporate communications. B. human resources management.",
    "D": "organizational decision-making.",
    "answer": "B: $545,100 D. $830,300 43. Making employment information available to job seekers in many locations at the same time is one way that computer technology impacts A. business development.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One tool that businesses can use to allow employees and customers to share knowledge through their websites is by posting",
    "A": "message boards. C. bots.",
    "B": "meta tags. D. interesting content. 47. Which of the following is an action that a business can take to capture tacit knowledge from its employees: A. Conducting personal interviews",
    "C": "Developing a competitive analysis B. Holding customer focus groups",
    "D": "Obtaining statistical reports from the Internet",
    "answer": "A: message boards. C. bots.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "At an exhibit, an employee helps customers make selections of new items that appeal to them. Which function of marketing is the salesperson performing?",
    "A": "Pricing C. Selling",
    "B": "Promotion D. Distribution 49. \"Helsinki is the capital of Finland\" is an example of what type of information? A. Criticism",
    "C": "Factual B. Opinion",
    "D": "Unproven",
    "answer": "C: Factual B. Opinion",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way for a person to verify the reliability of an online article's information is by",
    "A": "comparing the information with other articles about the topic.",
    "B": "evaluating the author's writing style.",
    "C": "gathering internal reports from the company's database.",
    "D": "asking others for their opinions.",
    "answer": "A: comparing the information with other articles about the topic.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is responsible for information management?",
    "A": "The information management department C. An information technology manager",
    "B": "Everyone in the organization D. The chief executive officer 52. If a business wants to send a mailing to customers in specific geographic regions, it should set the database q uery to sort its customer information by A. name.",
    "C": "state. B. sales volume.",
    "D": "street number.",
    "answer": "B: Everyone in the organization D. The chief executive officer 52. If a business wants to send a mailing to customers in specific geographic regions, it should set the database q uery to sort its customer information by A. name.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What spreadsheet function enables Audrey to reorganize sales data in one column so the dollar values appear in descending order?",
    "A": "AutoSum C. Merge",
    "B": "Sort and filter D. Find and select 54. To streamline its information systems, the Mason Company wants to purchase a computer program that performs a variety of related functions, such as accounts payable, accounts receivable, and general ledger applications. The Mason Company should purchase a(n) __________ computer package. A. integrated software",
    "C": "engineering design B. marketing intelligence",
    "D": "customer identification",
    "answer": "B: Sort and filter D. Find and select 54. To streamline its information systems, the Mason Company wants to purchase a computer program that performs a variety of related functions, such as accounts payable, accounts receivable, and general ledger applications. The Mason Company should purchase a(n) __________ computer package. A. integrated software",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a project-management software application that duplicates the project database and enables project managers to evaluate potential changes to the project plan and assess \"what if\" scenarios:?",
    "A": "Transaction processing C. Encryption",
    "B": "Test environment D. Digital scanning 56. A company wants to know how to better advertise to specific segments of customers, so it groups its customer data based on their incomes. This company is using the __________ method of data mining. A. decision tree",
    "C": "neural networks B. clustering",
    "D": "huddling",
    "answer": "B: Test environment D. Digital scanning 56. A company wants to know how to better advertise to specific segments of customers, so it groups its customer data based on their incomes. This company is using the __________ method of data mining. A. decision tree",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The local government fined Lenny's Grille because there were 75 more patrons in the facility at one time than legally permitted. In this situation, the business violated a",
    "A": "traffic ordinance. C. maximum capacity code.",
    "B": "federal property law. D. construction permit. 60. A company trained you for five days on how to run a high-speed printing press. Now you are working by yourself, but you have forgotten a step in the process although the machine seems to be operating correctly. What should you do? A. Ask for help.",
    "C": "Skip that step. B. Stop the press.",
    "D": "Continue working.",
    "answer": "C: Skip that step. B. Stop the press.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of security problem is most frightening to a business's employees?",
    "A": "Robbery C. Burglary",
    "B": "Fraud D. Shoplifting 62. How can you make sure your project plan is realistic and thorough? A. Use to-do lists.",
    "C": "Create a budget. B. Identify project stakeholders.",
    "D": "Obtain feedback from your team.",
    "answer": "A: Robbery C. Burglary",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is a project's scope determined?",
    "A": "Before the planning stage begins C. At the beginning of the planning stage",
    "B": "In the middle of the planning stage D. At the end of the planning stage 64. A standard purchase order should include product specifications, quantities, prices, and what else? A. The invoice code",
    "C": "Shipping requirements B. Location of buyer's customer",
    "D": "Credit references",
    "answer": "C: Shipping requirements B. Location of buyer's customer",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "All-purpose flour is an impor tant ingredient in a variety of baked goods. What type of inventory would all-purpose flour be for a bakery?",
    "A": "Packing material C. Finished good",
    "B": "Work in progress D. Raw material 66. Which of the following is a non-price issue that a business might negotiate with a vendor when purchasing expensive, complex equipment: A. Post-sale service",
    "C": "Volume reductions B. Payment terms",
    "D": "Compensation",
    "answer": "D: Compensation",
    "topic": "Supply Chain Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The practices of not relying on inspection to achieve quality and lowering costs by working with just one supplier are part of which quality control technique?",
    "A": "Continuous improvement C. Lean operations",
    "B": "Six Sigma D. Total quality management 68. When combined, which costs equal all of the expenses incurred by a company? A. Salaries and rent",
    "C": "Direct labor and materials B. Overhead and direct costs",
    "D": "Products and services costs",
    "answer": "D: Products and services costs",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business analyst is finished working on a project, s/he should then?",
    "A": "attempt to understand the existing processes that are in place.",
    "B": "determine t he primary stakeholders related to the project.",
    "C": "evaluate the effectiveness of the project's solutions.",
    "D": "clarify the project's primary business objectives.",
    "answer": "C: evaluate the effectiveness of the project's solutions.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before assigning a new project to her employees, Joanna establishes the steps that her staff needs to take to complete the project. Joanna is utilizing",
    "A": "human resource planning. C. agile project management.",
    "B": "business process thinking. D. change management. 71. A business process design should seek to achieve simplicity because complex designs A. require documentation.",
    "C": "result in more errors. B. must be validated.",
    "D": "cannot be automated.",
    "answer": "B: business process thinking. D. change management. 71. A business process design should seek to achieve simplicity because complex designs A. require documentation.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Premiere Office Supplies used to make enough revenue through existing customer reorders, but lately, many customers have begun order ing from YourOffice, a new retailer. Therefore, Premiere Office Supplies had to change its sales process to increase revenue due to",
    "A": "growth. C. technology.",
    "B": "competition. D. regulation. 73. Akua is in charge of supervising the entire process of getting products into the marketplace, otherwise known as the flow of goods. Akua's job title is most likely A. chief financial officer.",
    "C": "supply chain manager. B. line supervisor.",
    "D": "inventory manager.",
    "answer": "B: competition. D. regulation. 73. Akua is in charge of supervising the entire process of getting products into the marketplace, otherwise known as the flow of goods. Akua's job title is most likely A. chief financial officer.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The use of technology in supply chain management often results in",
    "A": "increased efficiency. C. decreased efficiency.",
    "B": "improved budgeting. D. more human error. 75. Supply chain networks are often A. eliminated.",
    "C": "unimportant. B. redesigned.",
    "D": "unprofitable.",
    "answer": "A: increased efficiency. C. decreased efficiency.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One possible downside to choosing overseas suppliers is",
    "A": "increased costs. C. a simpler supply chain.",
    "B": "increased delivery times. D. increased taxes. 77. How can a company hold employees accountable for protecting digital assets? A. Background checks",
    "C": "Project management software B. Encryption software",
    "D": "An effective laptop security policy",
    "answer": "B: increased delivery times. D. increased taxes. 77. How can a company hold employees accountable for protecting digital assets? A. Background checks",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As a specific outcome you intend to work toward, a goal is a(n)",
    "A": "target. C. performance.",
    "B": "skill. D. evaluation. 79. Employees who have supervisory responsibilities for part or all of the business work in A. business information management.",
    "C": "securities and investments. B. general management.",
    "D": "merchandising.",
    "answer": "A: target. C. performance.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Human resources management, operations management, and administrative services are all employment opportunities within",
    "A": "secretarial and managerial services. C. human affairs and counseling services.",
    "B": "financial and banking services management. D. business management and administration. 81. Employers promote employees who have shown that they are reliable, trustworthy, and A. competent.",
    "C": "interesting. B. dependent.",
    "D": "aggressive.",
    "answer": "D: aggressive.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Social media policies are especially important in today's modern world because",
    "A": "the Internet can only harm a company's reputation.",
    "B": "employees can't be trusted with technology.",
    "C": "negative comments can spread quickly online.",
    "D": "companies rely on social media to communicate.",
    "answer": "C: negative comments can spread quickly online.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding the chain of command is true:?",
    "A": "It's okay to ask for help fr om someone below you in the chain of command, rather than asking your boss.",
    "B": "You should always report to the person with the most expertise on the topic you need help with.",
    "C": "If you know your boss can't help you with something, you shouldn't bother as king him/her.",
    "D": "It's typically inappropriate to report to anyone else in the chain of command besides your direct supervisor.",
    "answer": "D: It's typically inappropriate to report to anyone else in the chain of command besides your direct supervisor.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Deidra was developing the statement of work (SOW) for a complex construction project, she included a statement that describes the things that the project will and won't include. This statement is defining the project?",
    "A": "constraints. C. risks.",
    "B": "outcome. D. scope. 85. Which of the following is a true statement about the work breakdown structure (WBS) in project management: A. The project manager should require team members to approve the WBS. B. The project scope remains the same after making changes to the WBS.",
    "C": "Each work package should take between eight and 80 hours to complete.",
    "D": "Team members develop the WBS dictionary after they carry out their work tasks.",
    "answer": "D: Team members develop the WBS dictionary after they carry out their work tasks.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When executing a project, the project manager must often?",
    "A": "develop a project charter. C. form a steering committee.",
    "B": "update the project plan. D. revise stakeholder requirements. 87. What should project managers do to ensure that team members will perform their designated tasks efficiently? A. Correct the team members' mistakes for them B. Ask team members if they like their assignments",
    "C": "Communicate their roles and responsibilities to them",
    "D": "Provide a team evaluation form",
    "answer": "B: update the project plan. D. revise stakeholder requirements. 87. What should project managers do to ensure that team members will perform their designated tasks efficiently? A. Correct the team members' mistakes for them B. Ask team members if they like their assignments",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following pieces of information are included in the \"lessons-learned\" document when closing a project:?",
    "A": "Statement of work, successes, and failures",
    "B": "Costs, suggestions for improvement, and project charter",
    "C": "Successes, failures, and suggestions for improvement",
    "D": "Project charter, successes, and failures",
    "answer": "C: Successes, failures, and suggestions for improvement",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An organization-wide system that businesses use to ensure that products meet quality s tandards is known as quality",
    "A": "management. C. assurance.",
    "B": "control. D. improvement. 90. Which of the following statements is true about the Six Sigma quality management framework: A. It can be effective without establishing incremental benchmarks. B. It focuses on increasing employee job satisfaction.",
    "C": "It emphasizes lowering costs more than improving quality.",
    "D": "It involves change throughout the entire organization.",
    "answer": "C: It emphasizes lowering costs more than improving quality.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do ethics relate to risk management?",
    "A": "The best form of business et hics is risk management.",
    "B": "Risk management is all about the ethical treatment of customers.",
    "C": "Risk management is insurance for lapses in business ethics.",
    "D": "The best form of risk management is adherence to business ethics.",
    "answer": "D: The best form of risk management is adherence to business ethics.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Using appropriate sof tware to protect confidential data that are stored on a company's computer systems is an important part of managing",
    "A": "physical safety risks. C. security risks.",
    "B": "natural disasters. D. environmental hazards. 93. Which of the following is the type of action that a business is taking when it continuously monitors the laws that affect its operations for the purpose of minimizing risk: A. Preventative",
    "C": "Reactive B. Corrective",
    "D": "Remedial",
    "answer": "C: Reactive B. Corrective",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following questions should effective managerial planning answer:?",
    "A": "How will we monitor the work effort? C. Did we accomplish our goals?",
    "B": "Who will do the work? D. What do we want to do? 95. Success Unlimited Corporation has a detailed structure that determines job roles. Therefore, all employees know exactly what they are supposed to be doing and feel confident and satisfied in their positions. This is an example of how A. organizational structure leads to cooperation. B. it is important to know who is in charge.",
    "C": "managerial organizatio n leads to a sense of security.",
    "D": "companies that grow quickly are more organized.",
    "answer": "D: companies that grow quickly are more organized.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a manager is directing, s/he is?",
    "A": "initiating action. C. identifying resources.",
    "B": "setting goals. D. evaluating feedback. 97. A customer contacts a manager regarding a billing error. After confirming the discrepancy, the manager asks an employee to void the existing invoice and create a new invoice with the correct information. What type of control is the manager using in this situation? A. Feedforwar d",
    "C": "Concurrent B. Feedback",
    "D": "Coercive",
    "answer": "A: initiating action. C. identifying resources.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Company executives decided to add a new product line to the company's mix. The company would benefit from",
    "A": "adjusting its budget. C. change management.",
    "B": "hiring new employees. D. ethics training. 99. Andy presents his idea for restructuring his company to the board of directors. In which stage of the change-management lifecycle is Andy? A. Review and authorize",
    "C": "Implementation B. Identify need for change",
    "D": "Close",
    "answer": "C: Implementation B. Identify need for change",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of corporation may be owned by just a few people and does not offer its shares for sale to the general public?",
    "A": "Franchise C. \"C\"",
    "B": "Private D. Limited 3. Jon sues his former employer for harassment. In what situation would the employer be likely to offer Jon a settlement? A. The employer wants the case to go to court. B. The employer knows it will be able to win the case.",
    "C": "The employer does not think it will be able to win the case.",
    "D": "Jon does not think he will be able to win the c ase.",
    "answer": "B: Private D. Limited 3. Jon sues his former employer for harassment. In what situation would the employer be likely to offer Jon a settlement? A. The employer wants the case to go to court. B. The employer knows it will be able to win the case.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first part of the litigation process?",
    "A": "Filing a motion to dismiss C. Investigating the complaint",
    "B": "Appearing in court D. Appealing the decision 5. The implementation of digital warehouse management systems is an example of how technology can impact __________ management. A. financial",
    "C": "supply chain B. human resource",
    "D": "employee",
    "answer": "C: supply chain B. human resource",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You can most effectively follow written directions by",
    "A": "reading the directions while you are distracted.",
    "B": "completing steps in the order written.",
    "C": "following steps in any order you choose.",
    "D": "completing the first step without reading the others.",
    "answer": "B: completing steps in the order written.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While attending a presentation, Jimmy indicates to the speaker that he would like to ask a question. Before stating his question, Jimmy briefly sums up the speaker's lecture. Which communication technique is Jimmy using?",
    "A": "Gestures C. Probing",
    "B": "Nonverbal D. Paraphrasing 8. Individuals who can defend their ideas objectively usually are able to provide o thers with A. personal opinions.",
    "C": "logical evidence. B. emotional information.",
    "D": "unrelated statistics.",
    "answer": "D: unrelated statistics.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The technological innovation that has had the greatest impact on modern businesses is",
    "A": "electronic databases. C. the internet.",
    "B": "improved computer hardware. D. virtual training. 10. Which of the following statements regarding executive summaries is true: A. Your executive summary should be approximately one-fourth to one-third as long as your entire report. B. You should sequence the m ain ideas of your executive summary in the same order that they appear in your full report.",
    "C": "You should always write your executive summary before writing the body and appendices of your report.",
    "D": "You should use jargon, technical language, abbreviatio ns, and slang frequently throughout your",
    "answer": "C: You should always write your executive summary before writing the body and appendices of your report.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jacob is determining the writing style to use for an analytical report. If most readers are likely to support the report's content, Jacob should format the report for a(n) __________ audience.",
    "A": "argumentative C. receptive",
    "B": "indecisive D. intellectual Test 1247 BUSINESS MANAGEMENT AND ADMINISTRATION CLUSTER EXAM 2 12. Which of the following is the last component of a research report: A. Purpose of the study",
    "C": "Background information B. Recommendations",
    "D": "Methodology",
    "answer": "C: Background information B. Recommendations",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the bes t way to show empathy to a customer who received poor service and mentioned it to you?",
    "A": "Ask them to complete a satisfaction survey.",
    "B": "Give the customer a credit on their account.",
    "C": "Listen, apologize, and thank them for sharing.",
    "D": "Promise them that it will never happen again.",
    "answer": "C: Listen, apologize, and thank them for sharing.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of customer would make the following statement: \"I just don't know how these items got into my pocket.\"?",
    "A": "Dishonest C. Disagreeable",
    "B": "Suspicious D. Domineering/Superior 15. What economic activity is necess ary for consumption to occur? A. Opportunity",
    "C": "Financing B. Production",
    "D": "Management",
    "answer": "A: Dishonest C. Disagreeable",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When demand for an item exceeds supply, the price will usually?",
    "A": "decrease. C. remain the same.",
    "B": "increase. D. be discounted. 17. Brynn manages employees wh o are new on the job and need quite a bit of supervision. Therefore, she can only supervise a few employees at once. Brynn's span of control is A. open.",
    "C": "wide. B. narrow.",
    "D": "tight.",
    "answer": "B: increase. D. be discounted. 17. Brynn manages employees wh o are new on the job and need quite a bit of supervision. Therefore, she can only supervise a few employees at once. Brynn's span of control is A. open.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Improved efficiency in the workplace usually increases",
    "A": "productivity. C. labor costs.",
    "B": "selling prices. D. unemployment. 19. Consumer spending is likely to decrease when A. a federal income tax increase is implemented. B. interest rates decrease substantially.",
    "C": "the production of goods and services in creases.",
    "D": "unemployment levels decrease for at least a year.",
    "answer": "A: productivity. C. labor costs.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Over the past few decades, a country has undergone a huge amount of economic development. This type of economic growth will most likely coincide with the country",
    "A": "opting out of trading with other countries. C. participating more in world trade.",
    "B": "participating less in world trade. D. maintaining the same level of trade. 21. Before you make a decision, you consider how your actions will affect your employer, coworkers, customers, and community. You are showing __________ responsibility. A. social",
    "C": "legal B. personal",
    "D": "ethical",
    "answer": "C: legal B. personal",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Involving employees in the decision-making process leading up to a planned change is one way to help them become __________ the change.",
    "A": "rebellio us against C. resistant to",
    "B": "receptive to D. reluctant about 23. While making a presentation to a customer, Kip used complex terms that the customer didn't understand. In this situation, effective communication was hindered due to A. the use of jargon.",
    "C": "the customer's emotional intelligence. B. Kip's personal appearance.",
    "D": "ongoing interruptions.",
    "answer": "B: receptive to D. reluctant about 23. While making a presentation to a customer, Kip used complex terms that the customer didn't understand. In this situation, effective communication was hindered due to A. the use of jargon.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is true of trust:?",
    "A": "It creates weaker relationships. C. It exists among customers, not coworkers.",
    "B": "It is only necessary at home or school. D. It is essential for success in the workplace. 25. When confronting another person about a conflict, it is important to avoid A. being objective.",
    "C": "using \"I\" statements. B. using \"you\" statements.",
    "D": "listen ing to feedback.",
    "answer": "D: listen ing to feedback.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Alyssa strives to come up with unique ideas, approaches, and solutions for her work group. What leadership characteristic does she demonstrate?",
    "A": "Authenticity C. Passion for people",
    "B": "Creativity D. Integrity 27. If you always act ethically no matter what the situation is, you are A. being consistent.",
    "C": "providing feedback. B. communicating clearly.",
    "D": "following the rules.",
    "answer": "B: Creativity D. Integrity 27. If you always act ethically no matter what the situation is, you are A. being consistent.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Trish learned that her company was switching to a new computer software program, she accept ed the change and worked overtime to become familiar with the new program. Trish exhibited __________ behavior.?",
    "A": "irresponsible C. passive",
    "B": "stubborn D. adaptable 29. A characteristic of democratic managers is that they generally A. explain the rea sons behind procedures.",
    "C": "encourage creative ways of doing things. B. rely solely upon their own judgment.",
    "D": "give very specific orders and instructions.",
    "answer": "D: give very specific orders and instructions.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one reason that it is easier than ever for small businesses to engage in internatio nal trade?",
    "A": "Technological advances C. Language barriers",
    "B": "Decreasing international middle class D. Increased regulation 31. Which of the following is a type of credit card that can be used to make purchases from a variety of participating businesses: A. Retail store",
    "C": "Hotel B. Bank",
    "D": "Petroleum",
    "answer": "A: Technological advances C. Language barriers",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chandra wants to develop a personal budget. What is the first step she should take?",
    "A": "Establishing her goals C. Determining regular expenditures",
    "B": "Estimating her income D. Allocating in come 33. If Diedra wants to open a savings account to save money for her dream vacation, she should place her money in a deposit-taking institution, such as a(n) A. investment bank or mortgage company.",
    "C": "commercial bank or credit union. B. savings an d loan bank or investment bank.",
    "D": "mortgage company or credit union.",
    "answer": "A: Establishing her goals C. Determining regular expenditures",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you are trying to create a personal budget, which of the following pieces of financial information is relevant to your purpose:",
    "A": "A sample budget found online C. Your employe r's assets and liabilities",
    "B": "A record of your monthly income D. Your best friend's cell phone bill 35. Checks, receipts, invoices, and purchase orders are examples of A. financial statements.",
    "C": "source documents. B. department ledgers.",
    "D": "accountin g standards.",
    "answer": "B: A record of your monthly income D. Your best friend's cell phone bill 35. Checks, receipts, invoices, and purchase orders are examples of A. financial statements.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the relationship between ethics and decision-making?",
    "A": "Ethical principles often conflict with the right decision.",
    "B": "Ethics make decision-making difficult.",
    "C": "Ethics are a framework for good decision-making.",
    "D": "Decision-makin g helps form ethical principles.",
    "answer": "C: Ethics are a framework for good decision-making.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to the statement of cash flows in a company's annual report, its cash flow from operations last year was $5,260,300 and its capital expenditures were $980,200. What was the company's free cash flow?",
    "A": "$4,280,100 C. $5,397,164",
    "B": "$1,863,391 D. $6,240,500 38. A human resources manager is reviewing job applications for a marketing position to select which candidates to call for an interview. What process is the human resources manager performing? A. Negotiating",
    "C": "Prospecting B. Onboarding",
    "D": "Screening",
    "answer": "A: $4,280,100 C. $5,397,164",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Knowledge is __________ information.",
    "A": "the raw, unprocessed form of C. understanding how to use",
    "B": "less important and useful than D. more tangible and identifiable than 40. Which of the following is an ethical issue that relates to knowledge management in the workplace: A. The president of a small company asks their executive team for input regarding a business decision. B. A project leader requests that each member of their team provide a status report to the group.",
    "C": "An employee deliberately doesn't share information with management that will he lp the company meet its goals.",
    "D": "The sales manager of a manufacturing firm shares the firm's quarterly sales goals with the sales",
    "answer": "C: An employee deliberately doesn't share information with management that will he lp the company meet its goals.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When selecting and implementing technological tools for an organization's knowledge management system, a primary factor to consider is?",
    "A": "accessibility. C. retention rates.",
    "B": "creativity. D. product marketability. 42. A business might ask its empl oyees to sign a nondisclosure agreement to A. protect its trade secrets.",
    "C": "ensure its employees' privacy. B. avoid discrimination lawsuits.",
    "D": "prevent copyright infringement.",
    "answer": "A: accessibility. C. retention rates.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Morgan Health Supply Company wants to expand its product line this year. It uses its budget surplus to invest in new products rather than to remodel its offices. What po sitive action is the company demonstrating?",
    "A": "Provide excellent customer service",
    "B": "Align strategies and activities with goals",
    "C": "Demonstrate corporate responsibility",
    "D": "Utilize touchpoints to reinforce company image",
    "answer": "B: Align strategies and activities with goals",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should you include in a persuasive message to support your statements?",
    "A": "Logical evidence C. Simple language",
    "B": "Educated guess D. Personal opinion 47. When creating and posting information to a website, one of the most important considerations is the A. shopping cart.",
    "C": "domain name. B. search engine.",
    "D": "home page.",
    "answer": "A: Logical evidence C. Simple language",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following strategies can help make data change easier:?",
    "A": "Ignoring errors during implementation",
    "B": "Communicating the benefits of the data change",
    "C": "Informing staff that data changes will continually occur",
    "D": "Rolling out data changes during a busy time of year",
    "answer": "B: Communicating the benefits of the data change",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a factor that relates to the government category of an envi ronmental scan:?",
    "A": "Stage of the business cycle C. Import/Export regulations",
    "B": "Religious affiliation D. Advances in technology 52. During the busy tourist season, a coastal surf shop sold 398 beach balls in June, 924 beach balls in July, and 537 bea ch balls in August. This information reveals that A. the supply of beach balls declined in June by 4%. B. more tourists purchased beach balls in July than June and August combined.",
    "C": "beach-ball production rates increased in August.",
    "D": "the demand for be ach balls peaked during July.",
    "answer": "C: beach-ball production rates increased in August.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following facility components are inspected by authorized officials to ensure that safety ordinances are met:?",
    "A": "Elevators C. Computer networks",
    "B": "Photocopiers D. Portable cameras 54. When a customer or an employee is involved in a minor accident on the business's premises, an employee of the business should immediately A. report the accident to a supervisor or manager. B. offer to take the person home.",
    "C": "help the injured person move to a quiet are a.",
    "D": "call the local medical emergency number.",
    "answer": "A: Elevators C. Computer networks",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important in proj ect planning to build in a safety net, or padding, when identifying resources?",
    "A": "To try to cut corners C. To plan for the unexpected",
    "B": "To find substitutes D. To obtain financial support 59. To maintain positive, ongoing relationships with vendors, a business should A. embrace a team-oriented mindset.",
    "C": "adopt an indifferent outlook. B. develop complex contracts.",
    "D": "focus on its own interests.",
    "answer": "C: adopt an indifferent outlook. B. develop complex contracts.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When is a business most likely to place a straight rebuy with a vendor?",
    "A": "To change the quantitie s of items that it routinely orders",
    "B": "To accommodate customers' unique requests",
    "C": "To order seasonal merchandise",
    "D": "To replenish its regularly stocked items",
    "answer": "D: To replenish its regularly stocked items",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should an electronics store do when they learn that the new iPhone is expected to be more popular than ever?",
    "A": "Build up anticipatory inventory C. Use just-in-time inventory",
    "B": "Lower the price of the iPhone D. Get rid of raw materials 62. Determine if the following statement is true or false: The primary purpose of quality-control measures is to evaluate employee efficiency levels. A. False; businesses also use quality-control measures to evaluate products, processes, and other business functions. B. False; the primary purpose of quality-control measures is to evaluate the degree of excellence of goods and services.",
    "C": "True; businesses must evaluate their employees' performance to ensure that they are producing high-quality goods and services.",
    "D": "True; employees perform the work, so they are responsible for developing and implemen ting",
    "answer": "A: Build up anticipatory inventory C. Use just-in-time inventory",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the benefits of setting goals that will help you in your relationships with others is that setting goals",
    "A": "gives you a way to measure your progress. C. helps you stay on task.",
    "B": "helps you understand yourself. D. raises your level of self-esteem. 64. Kate is a consultant who specializes in helping companies discover and implement positive solutions to problems in their business processes. Kate's work could best be described as A. financial counseling.",
    "C": "marketing research. B. public relations.",
    "D": "business analysis.",
    "answer": "B: helps you understand yourself. D. raises your level of self-esteem. 64. Kate is a consultant who specializes in helping companies discover and implement positive solutions to problems in their business processes. Kate's work could best be described as A. financial counseling.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To reduce risks associated with unethical business activities, a company should clearly communicate its",
    "A": "code of conduct to all employees.",
    "B": "terms-of-sale policies to executive man agers.",
    "C": "product requirements to its primary distributors.",
    "D": "dividend payment schedule to suppliers.",
    "answer": "A: code of conduct to all employees.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Supply chain networks encompass the flow and movement of __________ among __________.",
    "A": "classified information; protest groups C. government officials; Fortune 500 companies",
    "B": "employees and customers; governments D. materials and information; organizations 71. Longer supply lines resulting from globalization will m ost likely increase __________ for suppliers. A. visibility",
    "C": "product quality B. speed",
    "D": "risk",
    "answer": "D: risk",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one way that employees can help their companies protect digital assets?",
    "A": "Share passwords with everyone in the company",
    "B": "Follow company policies about giving out personal information",
    "C": "Download documents from unevaluated websites",
    "D": "Send out emails to update everyone on security policy changes",
    "answer": "B: Follow company policies about giving out personal information",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To protect customer data such as credit card information, businesses sho uld",
    "A": "use a shared server to store information. C. require that all customers show an ID.",
    "B": "accept payments in cash only. D. keep sensitive records encrypted. 74. Which of the following is an advantage of a supply chain's ability to adjust internal inventory levels: A. It develops better supplier relationships. B. It no longer needs to monitor inventory levels.",
    "C": "It significantly reduces transportation costs.",
    "D": "It can respond to changes in the marketplace.",
    "answer": "D: It can respond to changes in the marketplace.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Even when times are tough for C aitlin's business venture, she tends to remain positive-she looks at the glass as half full rather than half empty. What characteristic of entrepreneurship is Caitlin exhibiting?",
    "A": "Determination C. Innovation",
    "B": "Organization D. Optimism 76. Which of the following employees has a supply chain management career: A. Saeed interviews potential employees.",
    "C": "Ian is in charge of employee benefits. B. Rose orients new employees.",
    "D": "Lena is in charge of demand forecasting.",
    "answer": "D: Lena is in charge of demand forecasting.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of information can be included in an interview follow-up letter?",
    "A": "Explanation of salary expectations C. Detailed description of education",
    "B": "Chronological review of employment D. Brief reminder of qualifications 78. Brandon, an accountant, wants to expand his professional network and stay up to date in his industry. However, he doesn't have time to commit to attending events on a weekly basis. Which of the following resources would best help Brandon achieve these goals: A. Classes/Seminars",
    "C": "A professional as sociation B. Trade journals/periodicals",
    "D": "A social group outside of work",
    "answer": "D: A social group outside of work",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Caroline explains the company's rules of conduct to a new employee, she should also explain?",
    "A": "when the rules were implemented. C. who developed the rules.",
    "B": "the spe cific reasons for having all the rules. D. the consequences of breaking the rules. 80. In which of the following documents does the project manager clearly define the project's terms and conditions for stakeholders: A. Statement of work",
    "C": "The project audit B. Team agenda",
    "D": "Project schedule",
    "answer": "D: Project schedule",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Change management occurs in a cycle because",
    "A": "organizations always need to change. C. change is harmful for most companies.",
    "B": "organizations push for unnecessary change. D. change is difficult to imple ment. Test 1247 BUSINESS MANAGEMENT AND ADMINISTRATION CLUSTER EXAM 8 82. Reviewing activity status reports helps a project manager A. develop specifications.",
    "C": "determine project scope. B. create barriers.",
    "D": "control the project.",
    "answer": "A: organizations always need to change. C. change is harmful for most companies.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a project manager delegating respon sibility to a project team member:?",
    "A": "Stan asks Joanna and Tom for suggestions to improve process efficiency.",
    "B": "Bill tells Peter that he needs to remember to include a cover sheet with his TPS report.",
    "C": "Nina advises Milton that he is responsible for pr eparing the team's weekly status report.",
    "D": "Anne determines that Bob has the desired organizational skills to be on the project team.",
    "answer": "C: Nina advises Milton that he is responsible for pr eparing the team's weekly status report.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ABC Builders is two months behind schedule on the mall it is building. Management has decided to \"crash\" the project. Which of the following is an example of \"crashing\" a project:",
    "A": "Extend the completion date by two months",
    "B": "Stop the project and allow another company to finish it",
    "C": "Start installing lights now instead of waiting until the painting is complete",
    "D": "Hire 10 additional construction workers",
    "answer": "D: Hire 10 additional construction workers",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the primary purpose of developing a post-implementation review during the closure phase of a project?",
    "A": "To archive all project documentation",
    "B": "To document necessary changes for future projects",
    "C": "To formally release all resources from the project",
    "D": "To determine if the deliverables achieved project goals",
    "answer": "D: To determine if the deliverables achieved project goals",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The cost of employing product inspectors is a(n) __________ cost.",
    "A": "internal failure C. appraisal",
    "B": "prevention D. external failu re 87. Identifying and eliminating defects that cause variations in quality is the primary goal of A. acceptance sampling.",
    "C": "behavior modeling. B. Six Sigma.",
    "D": "\"Big Q.\"",
    "answer": "C: behavior modeling. B. Six Sigma.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What step in the Plan-Do-Check-Act (PDCA) continuous improvement techniq ue involves analyzing the results of a small-scale change to determine if the change was effective?",
    "A": "Do C. Act",
    "B": "Check D. Plan 89. Before beginning a new project, a manager who uses business process thinking would most likely A. examine the fina ncial implications of the project to make sure it will be profitable. B. explain to employees the end result that the manager wants to achieve from the project.",
    "C": "create a list of things that employees should avoid doing during the project.",
    "D": "determine the steps that employees need to follow to complete the project.",
    "answer": "B: Check D. Plan 89. Before beginning a new project, a manager who uses business process thinking would most likely A. examine the fina ncial implications of the project to make sure it will be profitable. B. explain to employees the end result that the manager wants to achieve from the project.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a company uses computer software to assess the risk levels associated with alternative actions in a variety of business situations, it is conducting?",
    "A": "qualitative resea rch. C. top-down forecasting.",
    "B": "a product feasibility study. D. what-if planning. 91. When a business actively takes steps to ensure that it is complying with safety standards, its goal is to reduce A. property disputes.",
    "C": "fraudulent activity. B. social responsibility.",
    "D": "liability exposure.",
    "answer": "D: liability exposure.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the first step of effective managerial planning:?",
    "A": "Establish criteria to evaluate strategies",
    "B": "Evaluate the quality of various processes",
    "C": "Develop procedures for activity implementation",
    "D": "Use a systematic approach to establish objectives",
    "answer": "D: Use a systematic approach to establish objectives",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Under what circumstances would a company adopt a matrix organizational structure?",
    "A": "It has offices in several cities. C. It frequently uses cross-functional teams.",
    "B": "It has mostly inexperienced employees. D. It has fewer than 50 employees. 96. What directing activity involves rewarding employees with positive feedback and monetary incentives? A. Coordinating",
    "C": "Motivating B. Supervising",
    "D": "Producing",
    "answer": "C: Motivating B. Supervising",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The p rimary way that managers control employees is by",
    "A": "making sure employees are doing what they are supposed to be doing.",
    "B": "interacting with customers to see how employees are doing.",
    "C": "controlling the level of work-life balance that employees enjoy.",
    "D": "monitoring how the company's public relations team is performing.",
    "answer": "A: making sure employees are doing what they are supposed to be doing.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Every month, a technology company has all-staff meetings in which employees team up and brainstorm new ideas together. Many of these ideas lead to innovative new products. This is an example of how __________ helps organizations innovate and change.",
    "A": "collaboration C. customer service",
    "B": "training D. resilience 99. What does it mean to obtain sponsorship within the organization during the change management process? A. Earning th e support of other companies in the industry B. Obtaining funding for the change from an external sponsor",
    "C": "Gaining acceptance of the change from company stockholders",
    "D": "Securing the approval and involvement of senior executives",
    "answer": "A: collaboration C. customer service",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The importance of following legal procedure is to provide each party with",
    "A": "specific duties.",
    "B": "unique rights.",
    "C": "due process.",
    "D": "formal requests.",
    "answer": "C: due process.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason that someone might want to settle a legal case:?",
    "A": "To avoid a judge's approval",
    "B": "To have a lengthy trial",
    "C": "To damage someone's reputation",
    "D": "To avoid a costly trial",
    "answer": "D: To avoid a costly trial",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step of the litigation process?",
    "A": "The defendant answers a complaint.",
    "B": "The plaintiff answers a complaint.",
    "C": "The plaintiff files a complaint.",
    "D": "The defendant files a complaint.",
    "answer": "C: The plaintiff files a complaint.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why might parties choose to use mediation to solve a dispute?",
    "A": "To do less work",
    "B": "To spend more money",
    "C": "To avoid going to court",
    "D": "To get a less personal result",
    "answer": "C: To avoid going to court",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following steps should be completed first when preparing a written communication:?",
    "A": "Organizing the information to be presented in the communication",
    "B": "Determining the major purpose of the communication",
    "C": "Editing the communicatio n to make sure it is clear",
    "D": "Selecting the details that should be included in the communication",
    "answer": "B: Determining the major purpose of the communication",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In oral presentations, a closing method used specifically for getting the audience to do something is",
    "A": "making an appeal for action.",
    "B": "making a comparison.",
    "C": "using humor.",
    "D": "using a quotation.",
    "answer": "A: making an appeal for action.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Edith wants to organize the information in her persuasive paper in a clear, logical way that's easy for readers to understand. She starts by stating the dilemma at hand and then explains the answer that she believes will solve the dilemma. Which method of organizing information is Edith using?",
    "A": "Deductive",
    "B": "Chronological",
    "C": "Problem/Solution",
    "D": "Alphabetical",
    "answer": "C: Problem/Solution",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rosa is writing a business letter to Alex Smith, whom she has never met. Which of the following salutations should Rosa use:",
    "A": "To Whom It May Concern:",
    "B": "Dear Mr. Smith:",
    "C": "Dear Alex:",
    "D": "Dear Alex Smith:",
    "answer": "D: Dear Alex Smith:",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One goal of analytical reports is to",
    "A": "report progress.",
    "B": "assess opportunities.",
    "C": "criticize decisions.",
    "D": "request funding.",
    "answer": "B: assess opportunities.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which component of a research report should the writer place the following statement: \"Based on our findings, we believe that it is imperative that PNJ Corporation make the necessary adjustments.\"",
    "A": "Assumptions",
    "B": "Recommendations",
    "C": "Methodology",
    "D": "Analyses",
    "answer": "B: Recommendations",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How should an employee handle a situation in which a disagreeable customer is making a loud complaint?",
    "A": "Remain calm and try to identify the real problem",
    "B": "Interrupt the customer and tell them to be quiet",
    "C": "Ask the customer to come back when they are calmer",
    "D": "Tell the customer they don't need to yell",
    "answer": "A: Remain calm and try to identify the real problem",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would be classified as a service complaint:?",
    "A": "Defective item",
    "B": "Late delivery",
    "C": "Empathetic behavior",
    "D": "Wrong size",
    "answer": "B: Late delivery",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Selling goods and locating potential customers are included in which of the following categories of business activities:",
    "A": "Financial analysis",
    "B": "Operations management",
    "C": "Marketing",
    "D": "Strategic management",
    "answer": "C: Marketing",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of tax do many local governments levy to pay for public schools and community parks?",
    "A": "Estate",
    "B": "Excise",
    "C": "Income",
    "D": "Property",
    "answer": "D: Property",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In 2019, a pair of running shoes cost $55. In 2020, that same pair of running shoes cost $65. Assuming that nothing else changed except the price of the shoes, this example most likely demonstrates",
    "A": "trend shifts.",
    "B": "advertising power.",
    "C": "deflation.",
    "D": "inflation.",
    "answer": "D: inflation.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An internal factor that affects the business environment is",
    "A": "exchange rates.",
    "B": "economic expansion.",
    "C": "job reorganization.",
    "D": "competition.",
    "answer": "C: job reorganization.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of increased financial risk for a company with poor business ethics:?",
    "A": "Increased productivity",
    "B": "Decreased company value",
    "C": "Decreased labor costs",
    "D": "Increased sales",
    "answer": "B: Decreased company value",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first thing you need to do when you want to persuade others to take a certain course of action?",
    "A": "Understand your audience",
    "B": "State your case",
    "C": "Communicate clearly",
    "D": "Express a need or want",
    "answer": "A: Understand your audience",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following coaching characteristics means that you are willing to admit your mistakes:?",
    "A": "Patience",
    "B": "Dependability",
    "C": "Humility",
    "D": "Approachability",
    "answer": "C: Humility",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Many people enjoy being given responsibility because it",
    "A": "makes them feel valuable and respected.",
    "B": "guarantees that they'll get a promotion.",
    "C": "allows them to do less work than before.",
    "D": "ensures that they will never lose their job.",
    "answer": "A: makes them feel valuable and respected.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a personal vision:?",
    "A": "I will learn how to effectively manage my personal finances.",
    "B": "I will earn an associate degree in business administration.",
    "C": "I will complete my first 5K race in under 30 minutes.",
    "D": "I will share my love of food with others by being a chef.",
    "answer": "D: I will share my love of food with others by being a chef.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Evaluating the magnitude of a risk can be done by considering its",
    "A": "chance.",
    "B": "severity.",
    "C": "probability.",
    "D": "possible threat.",
    "answer": "B: severity.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Simon is a chef, and he has just gotten a special request to make a dish that he's never made before. However, Simon thinks about similar dishes he has made and uses that knowledge to guide him. This is an example of",
    "A": "listening to gut instincts.",
    "B": "shifting to other perspectives.",
    "C": "learning from the past.",
    "D": "asking questions.",
    "answer": "C: learning from the past.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Taking online quizzes and/or looking at a comprehensive list of values can help you",
    "A": "find gaps between values and behavior.",
    "B": "determine what your values are.",
    "C": "match behaviors with values.",
    "D": "find ways to critique others' values.",
    "answer": "B: determine what your values are.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Entrepreneurs who act ethically are less likely to",
    "A": "make a profit long term.",
    "B": "preserve the environment.",
    "C": "enjoy support from suppliers.",
    "D": "harm their customers.",
    "answer": "D: harm their customers.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Choosing to buy an item at the checkout counter is often an example of",
    "A": "smart shopping.",
    "B": "impulsive spending.",
    "C": "financial self-control.",
    "D": "poor use of credit.",
    "answer": "B: impulsive spending.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rebecca recently terminated her relationship with a financial-services provider. The financial planner misled Rebecca about her financial status so that she would continue to pay for their services. This example demonstrates the importance of selecting a f inancial-services provider who is",
    "A": "open-minded.",
    "B": "competent.",
    "C": "diligent.",
    "D": "objective.",
    "answer": "D: objective.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of investment involves several people pooling their money to purchase stocks and bonds?",
    "A": "Elective",
    "B": "Secure",
    "C": "Mutual funds",
    "D": "Money market accounts",
    "answer": "C: Mutual funds",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of insurance provides financial support to loved ones in the event of your death?",
    "A": "Renter's insurance",
    "B": "Disability insurance",
    "C": "Health insurance",
    "D": "Life insurance",
    "answer": "D: Life insurance",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a finance professional demonstrating transparency:?",
    "A": "Evan regularly attends professional development seminars.",
    "B": "Jess makes sure to complete all of her work on time.",
    "C": "Carmen keeps financial information private.",
    "D": "Darren speaks up when he sees errors in a financial model.",
    "answer": "D: Darren speaks up when he sees errors in a financial model.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When filling out a check, which of the following is written in the \"pay to the order of\" area:?",
    "A": "Name of person or business receiving the funds",
    "B": "The total check amount spelled out in words",
    "C": "Name of bank institution holding the funds",
    "D": "Name of bank institution cashing the check",
    "answer": "A: Name of person or business receiving the funds",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following business trends affects HR management:?",
    "A": "Costs of business going down",
    "B": "Globalization",
    "C": "No restructuring",
    "D": "Lack of new technology",
    "answer": "B: Globalization",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When an employee is an expert in a certain job position, it can be important for others in the organization to access their knowledge through a knowledge management system. This influencing factor is known as?",
    "A": "innovation.",
    "B": "turnover.",
    "C": "specialization.",
    "D": "globalization.",
    "answer": "C: specialization.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary reason why employees might withhold their tacit knowledge from coworkers?",
    "A": "Negative work culture",
    "B": "Uncooperative vendors",
    "C": "Unsatisfactory credit rating",
    "D": "Poor customer service levels",
    "answer": "A: Negative work culture",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While performing her job, Kendra figured out how to solve a problem that has been affecting her department. Which of the following is the most efficient way for Kendra to share thi s knowledge with her coworkers:",
    "A": "Email",
    "B": "Company website",
    "C": "Relational database",
    "D": "Phone call",
    "answer": "A: Email",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an action that threatens a company's ability to maintain its trade secrets:?",
    "A": "Copyright reform initiatives",
    "B": "Reverse engineering",
    "C": "Process fragmentation",
    "D": "Systematic neutralizing",
    "answer": "B: Reverse engineering",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After knowledge has been captured and organized, it should be",
    "A": "deleted.",
    "B": "guarded.",
    "C": "shared.",
    "D": "sold.",
    "answer": "C: shared.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the link that connects producers and consumers so that both benefit?",
    "A": "Marketing",
    "B": "Handling",
    "C": "Shipping",
    "D": "Purchasing",
    "answer": "A: Marketing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maintaining comprehensive records about its customers' purchasing habits helps a company",
    "A": "plan future business activities.",
    "B": "increase brand loyalty.",
    "C": "obtain favorable credit ratings.",
    "D": "negotiate with competitors.",
    "answer": "A: plan future business activities.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One reason an existing business might develop a company website is to",
    "A": "create a new revenue source.",
    "B": "increase its product mix.",
    "C": "reduce marketing expenses.",
    "D": "lower tax rates.",
    "answer": "A: create a new revenue source.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one way that the trend toward protecting the environment has a negative effect on many businesses?",
    "A": "Reduces pollution",
    "B": "Promotes growth",
    "C": "Decreases prices",
    "D": "Increases costs",
    "answer": "D: Increases costs",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Todd needs to develop an overall plan for his business but does not know what type of information to include in the document. Todd logs onto a search engine to quickly locate the information he needs. Which of the following search terms is most likely to p rovide Todd with desired search results:",
    "A": "Develop planning document",
    "B": "Plan components",
    "C": "Business plan elements",
    "D": "Business document components",
    "answer": "C: Business plan elements",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to be a function of project management software:?",
    "A": "Creating visuals",
    "B": "Scheduling",
    "C": "Financial calculations",
    "D": "Storing client information",
    "answer": "B: Scheduling",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Daniela is in charge of moving company data into a new software system. Which of the following is a step she should take:",
    "A": "Avoid telling employees about the change until it is completed",
    "B": "Make sure all the data are saved in a backup location",
    "C": "Delete the old software system before installing the new one",
    "D": "Schedule the change to occur during a project deadline",
    "answer": "B: Make sure all the data are saved in a backup location",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions is most likely to contribute to the creation of a safe business environment:?",
    "A": "Keeping file drawers in high traffic areas open throughout the day",
    "B": "Running extension cords across main walkways in the business",
    "C": "Storing inventory in stairwells and in front of emergency exits",
    "D": "Salting icy patches on the sidewalk outside the business entrance",
    "answer": "D: Salting icy patches on the sidewalk outside the business entrance",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Henry works in a business's receiving room. While working, Henry was lifting and setting down heavy boxes when he experienced back and abdominal pain. What type of workplace injury did Henry receive?",
    "A": "Closed wound",
    "B": "Strain",
    "C": "Open wound",
    "D": "Sprain",
    "answer": "B: Strain",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of security problem does a business have if its employees routinely take pens and paper home for personal use?",
    "A": "Robbery",
    "B": "Shoplifting",
    "C": "Pilferage",
    "D": "Burglary",
    "answer": "C: Pilferage",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "David is meeting with a group of his employees to discuss what types of goods and services they need to successfully perform their jobs. This is often the first step in the __________ process.",
    "A": "marketing",
    "B": "receiving",
    "C": "buying",
    "D": "selling",
    "answer": "C: buying",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a tactic for protecting trade secrets, proprietary information, and sensitive data while also maintaining open lines of communication with a supplier:?",
    "A": "Testing supplier trustworthiness by providing provocative false information",
    "B": "Insisting that the supplier share all of its information first",
    "C": "Asking the supplier to sign nondisclosure agreements",
    "D": "Gathering damaging information on the suppl ier as leverage",
    "answer": "C: Asking the supplier to sign nondisclosure agreements",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the Frederick Company has space limitations in its warehouse, it needs to have a shelving unit custom-made. What type of order is the Frederick Company likely to place with the shelving manufacturer?",
    "A": "Open",
    "B": "Special",
    "C": "Reorder",
    "D": "Blanket",
    "answer": "B: Special",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following must occur for supply chain management to be successful:?",
    "A": "Goods and communication should flow both ways.",
    "B": "Few people should be involved in operations.",
    "C": "Producers should be in contact with final customers.",
    "D": "Emphasis should be placed on internal activities.",
    "answer": "A: Goods and communication should flow both ways.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is Claire doing when she reviews a report that compares the purchase transacti ons of the company's four largest customers?",
    "A": "Analyzing service performance",
    "B": "Preparing a purchasing forecast",
    "C": "Conducting a sales analysis",
    "D": "Organizing an inventory report",
    "answer": "C: Conducting a sales analysis",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are examples of raw materials that a business might keep on hand for production:?",
    "A": "Oil, grain, shoes, and household cleanser",
    "B": "Leather, bolts, stapler, and ore",
    "C": "Minerals, tables, leather, and paper",
    "D": "Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "answer": "D: Grain, minerals, leather, and oil",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a non-price issue that a business might negotiate with a vendor when purchasing expensive, complex equipment:?",
    "A": "Post-sale service",
    "B": "Compensation",
    "C": "Volume reductions",
    "D": "Payment terms",
    "answer": "A: Post-sale service",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Developing a business process typically results in a(n)",
    "A": "business process map.",
    "B": "third-party audit.",
    "C": "shareholder presentation.",
    "D": "organizational chart.",
    "answer": "A: business process map.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Shumaker Company recently altered its production process by adopting a new technology that can make finished goods three times faster than the old system. In other words, the company changed a business process to",
    "A": "reduce company debt.",
    "B": "improve performance.",
    "C": "increase company spending.",
    "D": "decrease employee wages.",
    "answer": "B: improve performance.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding the relationship between a business's supply chain management and its performance:?",
    "A": "Good supply ch ain management leads to unsustainable business practices.",
    "B": "Good supply chain management leads to decreased value for the customer.",
    "C": "Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction.",
    "D": "Poor supply chain management can result in customer satisfaction.",
    "answer": "C: Poor supply chain management can result in customer dissatisfaction.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Radio-frequency identification (RFID) technology is becoming more popular than barcodes in supply chain management because it does not require a direct line of sight, can be read at greater distances, and",
    "A": "has no chance of privacy problems.",
    "B": "can be read much faster.",
    "C": "is less expensive.",
    "D": "does not have reader collision concerns.",
    "answer": "B: can be read much faster.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a company hold employees accountable for protecting digital assets?",
    "A": "Encryption software",
    "B": "Project management software",
    "C": "Background checks",
    "D": "An effective laptop security policy",
    "answer": "D: An effective laptop security policy",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tanner is sending out an online customer satisfaction survey. What technique can he use to ensure he is protecting customer data?",
    "A": "House the data on portable drives",
    "B": "Only ask for the information he needs the most",
    "C": "Store the data for any future use",
    "D": "Refrain from sharing the nature of the survey",
    "answer": "B: Only ask for the information he needs the most",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where can you find information about the work, schedule, and resources for a project?",
    "A": "A marketing plan",
    "B": "A code of conduct",
    "C": "A project plan",
    "D": "A mission statement",
    "answer": "C: A project plan",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions would most likely be taken by an organized employee:?",
    "A": "Asking coworkers to complete work for them",
    "B": "Getting easily distracted",
    "C": "Planning work ahead of time",
    "D": "Thriving on tight deadlines",
    "answer": "C: Planning work ahead of time",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Creativity can be helpful when handling customers'",
    "A": "charge accounts.",
    "B": "inquiries.",
    "C": "credit applications.",
    "D": "objections.",
    "answer": "D: objections.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Professional selling belongs in what career area?",
    "A": "Business management",
    "B": "Marketing",
    "C": "Finance",
    "D": "Sports",
    "answer": "B: Marketing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of goal is designed to prevent or control internal organizational behavior?",
    "A": "Product",
    "B": "Short-term",
    "C": "Profit",
    "D": "Order",
    "answer": "D: Order",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"Business information management\" is a term sometimes used to refer to",
    "A": "supply chain management.",
    "B": "business analytics.",
    "C": "office management.",
    "D": "human resources management.",
    "answer": "B: business analytics.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Daniel is preparing to request approval for his project from senior management. What document does he need to develop and submit?",
    "A": "Project charter",
    "B": "Project management plan",
    "C": "Business case",
    "D": "Project statement of work",
    "answer": "A: Project charter",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary advantage of developing a work breakdown structure (WBS) to manage large projects?",
    "A": "Eliminates unexpected circumstances",
    "B": "Reduces the need to set project milestones",
    "C": "Decreases the need to manage each task",
    "D": "Prevents the duplication of work",
    "answer": "D: Prevents the duplication of work",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "So that team members can complete their specific tasks and responsibilities correctly, project managers must communicate",
    "A": "short-term incentives.",
    "B": "financial information.",
    "C": "performance standards.",
    "D": "marketing strategies.",
    "answer": "C: performance standards.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During the project-closure process group, which of the following should project teams do:",
    "A": "Approve deliverables and sign all project documents",
    "B": "Create issue logs for problems encountered during the project",
    "C": "Celebrate their successful project completion together",
    "D": "Develop a work breakdown structure to show all work completed",
    "answer": "C: Celebrate their successful project completion together",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kevin is planning to paint a house. He draws a simple graph that shows the sequence of tasks that will be done from beginning to end of the project. For example: 1) Buy supplies, 2) Prepare house for painting, 3) Paint house, and so on. This is an example of a",
    "A": "network diagram.",
    "B": "work breakdown structure.",
    "C": "project charter.",
    "D": "scope management plan.",
    "answer": "A: network diagram.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Quality management is a",
    "A": "philosophy.",
    "B": "technique.",
    "C": "six-step process.",
    "D": "tool.",
    "answer": "A: philosophy.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following quality management frameworks uses martial arts terminology to identify individuals necessary for its implementation:?",
    "A": "ITIL",
    "B": "Six Sigma",
    "C": "CMMI",
    "D": "Quality Max",
    "answer": "B: Six Sigma",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a checks and balances system that often helps companies manage their business risks and monitor the integrity of their organizations:?",
    "A": "Executive commission",
    "B": "Retribution board",
    "C": "Ethics committee",
    "D": "Human resources council",
    "answer": "C: Ethics committee",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of risk-management technology can track individual traders' risk limits and notify management immediately if any trader exceeds their preset limit?",
    "A": "Corporate governance",
    "B": "Automated oversight",
    "C": "Stress testing",
    "D": "Data aggregation",
    "answer": "B: Automated oversight",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the functions of managerial control involves comparing the results of various business activities with the",
    "A": "hiring procedures.",
    "B": "established goals.",
    "C": "purchasing methods.",
    "D": "safety regulations.",
    "answer": "B: established goals.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are characteristics of tactical planning:?",
    "A": "Short-range and specific",
    "B": "Long-term and vague",
    "C": "Long-term and specific",
    "D": "Short-range and vague",
    "answer": "A: Short-range and specific",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An organization with a wide span of control usually",
    "A": "has a lack of middle managers.",
    "B": "uses a divisional organizational structure.",
    "C": "does not give managers enough direct reports.",
    "D": "gives little control to the CEO.",
    "answer": "A: has a lack of middle managers.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What management function involves activities such as determining that two new employees need to be hired?",
    "A": "Organizing",
    "B": "Planning",
    "C": "Controlling",
    "D": "Staffing",
    "answer": "D: Staffing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a marketing manager goes on vacation, the marketing staff does not know what tasks to do and does not feel like it can work ahead on anything. This example illustrates that?",
    "A": "directing motivates employees.",
    "B": "directors must build group dynam ics.",
    "C": "directing is a continuous process.",
    "D": "directing is the starting point of action.",
    "answer": "D: directing is the starting point of action.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Change management strategies often fail because",
    "A": "low-level employees are given too much responsibility.",
    "B": "employees dedicate too much time to the change process.",
    "C": "competitors have implemented the changes already.",
    "D": "they don't include everyone in the change process.",
    "answer": "D: they don't include everyone in the change process.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following occurs during the process of change management:?",
    "A": "Decision-making by top managers without staff input",
    "B": "Top-down and bottom-up dialogue among all employees",
    "C": "Dialogue among upper management employees only",
    "D": "Dialogue among entry-level employees only",
    "answer": "B: Top-down and bottom-up dialogue among all employees",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about the directing function of management:?",
    "A": "It uses standardized communication.",
    "B": "It is results driven rather than performance driven.",
    "C": "It is a continuous process.",
    "D": "It primarily occurs at the lowest level of the organization.",
    "answer": "C: It is a continuous process.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Legal ownership of purchases does not pass to the purchaser until all payments have been made if the\npurchaser uses __________ credit.",
    "A": "regular",
    "B": "trade",
    "C": "installment",
    "D": "revolving",
    "answer": "C: installment",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Belinda is reviewing departmental reports to determine why the business's outputs have been decreasing\nsteadily over the last six weeks. Belinda is analyzing issues related to",
    "A": "human resources.",
    "B": "finance.",
    "C": "production.",
    "D": "distribution.",
    "answer": "C: production.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a trade secret:?",
    "A": "Legal document",
    "B": "Credit report",
    "C": "Trade journal",
    "D": "Customer list",
    "answer": "D: Customer list",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While opening a large box of office supplies, Kendall accidentally cut her finger with the box cutters she was\nusing. Another employee, Jorge, was helping Kendall at the time and witnessed the accident. What is the first\nthing that Jorge should do?",
    "A": "Fill out an accident report",
    "B": "Put the office supplies away",
    "C": "Call Kendall's doctor",
    "D": "Administer first aid",
    "answer": "D: Administer first aid",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Seeing a movie at a theater would be considered a(n) __________ want.",
    "A": "unlimited",
    "B": "limited",
    "C": "noneconomic",
    "D": "economic",
    "answer": "D: economic",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following positions oversees the recruitment, training, performance, and safety of employees:?",
    "A": "Office manager",
    "B": "Operations manager",
    "C": "Human resources manager",
    "D": "Project manager",
    "answer": "C: Human resources manager",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Supply chain network design improves service and reduces cost by aligning purchasing, production, warehousing, inventory, and",
    "A": "marketing.",
    "B": "transportation.",
    "C": "the sales force.",
    "D": "promotion.",
    "answer": "B: transportation.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Holly, Jamar, and Ricki are working on a project together, even though they are geographically far away from each other. They use the internet to work on documents together, share files, and communicate quickly and easily. What type of software are Holly, Jamar, and Ricki using?",
    "A": "Groupware",
    "B": "Spyware",
    "C": "Freeware",
    "D": "Shareware",
    "answer": "A: Groupware",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a business sells its customer list to other organizations without obtaining its customers' consent, the business is likely to",
    "A": "take legal action against the other organizations.",
    "B": "lose its customers' trust.",
    "C": "damage others' reputations.",
    "D": "offer deep discounts to gain back its customers' loyalty.",
    "answer": "B: lose its customers' trust.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lamont Enterprises is using a trademark that looks very similar to the Seward Company's trademark. To prevent Lamont from continuing to use the trademar k, Seward can take legal action by",
    "A": "obtaining an arrest warrant.",
    "B": "charging Lamont with obstruction of justice.",
    "C": "filing an infringement lawsuit against Lamont.",
    "D": "requiring Lamont to pay a licensing fee.",
    "answer": "C: filing an infringement lawsuit against Lamont.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lisa and Aaliyah are finishing a school project together. When Lisa asks Aaliyah what she thinks about her half of the project, Aaliyah tells her, \"That looks good, but let me show you what else you could have done.\" Aaliyah's comments are an example of",
    "A": "negative feedback.",
    "B": "constructive criticism.",
    "C": "internal feedback.",
    "D": "self-control.",
    "answer": "B: constructive criticism.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To maintain positive, ongoing relationships with vendors, a business should",
    "A": "adopt an indifferent outlook.",
    "B": "develop complex contracts.",
    "C": "focus on its own interests.",
    "D": "embrace a team-oriented mindset.",
    "answer": "D: embrace a team-oriented mindset.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Online shipment tracking is one example of __________ affecting supply chain management.",
    "A": "economic downturns",
    "B": "technology",
    "C": "globalization",
    "D": "production changes",
    "answer": "B: technology",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ethical quality management aims to benefit",
    "A": "the business and those outside it.",
    "B": "individuals in positions of power.",
    "C": "only those outside the business.",
    "D": "the business and its employees only.",
    "answer": "A: the business and those outside it.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason that organizations undertake knowledge management:?",
    "A": "They don't value an organizational culture of learning.",
    "B": "They know that new knowledge is only created o utside the organization.",
    "C": "They want to ensure that organizational knowledge isn't wasted.",
    "D": "They must follow the laws and regulations of their industries.",
    "answer": "C: They want to ensure that organizational knowledge isn't wasted.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Many countries have laws and regulations in place regarding workplace safety. In the United States, for example, businesses are required to keep their walkways and passageways free from obstruction and debris. This example best demonstrates how __________ affect(s) business __________.",
    "A": "legal considerations; operations",
    "B": "operations; accessibility",
    "C": "government; financial planning",
    "D": "the law; marketing research",
    "answer": "A: legal considerations; operations",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following tasks is a project manager typically responsible for:?",
    "A": "Determining and communicating the project objectives to clients",
    "B": "Telling project team members how to complete their activities",
    "C": "Providing direction and coordin ation to the project team work",
    "D": "Completing and documenting all of the necessary project work",
    "answer": "C: Providing direction and coordin ation to the project team work",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What function of management establishes a company's levels of authority?",
    "A": "Organizing",
    "B": "Evaluating",
    "C": "Controlling",
    "D": "Staffing",
    "answer": "A: Organizing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can management reduce the business's level of risk associated with ethics?",
    "A": "Advise employees that following business ethics depends on the situation",
    "B": "Assume employees know what constitutes ethical behavior",
    "C": "Allow employees to follow their own set of ethics",
    "D": "Train employees about expectations in relation to workplace ethics",
    "answer": "D: Train employees about expectations in relation to workplace ethics",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Managers need to be familiar with the latest technology, government regulations, innovations and trends within the industry, and competitors' activities. What category of resource is this?",
    "A": "Financial",
    "B": "Information",
    "C": "Material",
    "D": "Human",
    "answer": "B: Information",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should you do if a customer is being difficult or demanding?",
    "A": "Ignore them, and focus on another customer.",
    "B": "Continue to treat them with courtesy and respect.",
    "C": "Promise to give the customer a significant discount.",
    "D": "Tell the customer that their attitude is inappropriate.",
    "answer": "B: Continue to treat them with courtesy and respect.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The PVX automotive manufacturer keeps office supplies such as copy paper, pens, and notepads on hand at all times. These office supplies are part of the manufacturer's inventory of",
    "A": "finished products.",
    "B": "raw materials.",
    "C": "work-in-process.",
    "D": "MRO goods.",
    "answer": "D: MRO goods.",
    "topic": "Supply Chain Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you are able to respect and appreciate other people's unique viewpoints, you can?",
    "A": "work more efficiently at your job.",
    "B": "take on more responsibility at work.",
    "C": "have constructive dialogue with others.",
    "D": "expect people to take advantage of you.",
    "answer": "C: have constructive dialogue with others.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ethical stakeholder management includes",
    "A": "reaching key deliverables.",
    "B": "communicating honestly and openly.",
    "C": "using money wisely.",
    "D": "defining quality standards.",
    "answer": "B: communicating honestly and openly.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kara is preparing the work breakdown structure (WBS) for a new project. She has prepared five wor k packages. She has estimated the time to complete each package as follows: Package A-26 hours; Package B-50 hours; Package C-38 hours; Package D-6 hours; and Package E-15 hours. If Kara's estimates are accurate, has she followed the 8/80 rule?",
    "A": "Yes, the average time to complete each package is 27 hours, which meets the 8/80 criteria.",
    "B": "Yes, Kara has scheduled the packages so that each one does not exceed 80 hours.",
    "C": "No, package D does not meet the minimum requirement of taking eight hours to complete.",
    "D": "No, Kara has scheduled more than 80 hours of work for the entire project.",
    "answer": "C: No, package D does not meet the minimum requirement of taking eight hours to complete.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following helps individuals understand how their actions, needs, interests, values, and motives affect their personal behavior:?",
    "A": "Self-understanding",
    "B": "Self-fulfillment",
    "C": "Self-preservation",
    "D": "Self-esteem",
    "answer": "A: Self-understanding",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the primary purpose of word processing software programs:?",
    "A": "To store business records",
    "B": "To arrange numerical data",
    "C": "To maintain tables of data",
    "D": "To create text documents",
    "answer": "D: To create text documents",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The person who files a lawsuit is the",
    "A": "judge.",
    "B": "lawyer.",
    "C": "plaintiff.",
    "D": "defendant.",
    "answer": "C: plaintiff.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Knowledge management is important for business success, but it is often limited by __________ team members.",
    "A": "specialist",
    "B": "collaborative",
    "C": "gossipy",
    "D": "unmotivated",
    "answer": "D: unmotivated",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To continuously improve their quality processes, businesses need to",
    "A": "promote change.",
    "B": "implement flexible policies.",
    "C": "establish benchmarks.",
    "D": "solicit customers.",
    "answer": "C: establish benchmarks.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following measures of central tendency is the most influenced by outliers at the extremes of a data set:?",
    "A": "Mode",
    "B": "Mean",
    "C": "Median",
    "D": "Range",
    "answer": "B: Mean",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lakshna is buying a new car. There is a vehicle she likes at Dealership A, but before she makes her purchase, Lakshna visits three other dealerships to look at similar vehicles to make sure she is getting the best deal. This is an example of",
    "A": "curren cy speculation.",
    "B": "merchandising.",
    "C": "comparison shopping.",
    "D": "impulse spending.",
    "answer": "C: comparison shopping.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mr. Williams's small pharmacy has been in operation for 10 years. Recently, a few senior citizens have asked to be billed once a month for medicines and other medical supplies. Mr. Williams would like to accommodate the seniors but is not sure of the effec t these changes would have on his business. Which business activity would help Mr. Williams make a sound decision?",
    "A": "Strategic management",
    "B": "Marketing",
    "C": "Financial analysis",
    "D": "Production",
    "answer": "C: Financial analysis",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Having a \"rainy day\" fund equivalent to six months of living expenses is an important financial goal because",
    "A": "you can dip into you r emergency fund to pay for things like vacations and clothing.",
    "B": "emergency funds guarantee that you will be okay even if you never work again.",
    "C": "it will protect you during a catastrophe, such as a health emergency or unemployment.",
    "D": "you won't need to save for college or retirement if you have an emergency fund.",
    "answer": "C: it will protect you during a catastrophe, such as a health emergency or unemployment.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Individuals and businesses who are sued have a legal right to present evidence on their behalf before a court can impose a penalty. In other words, these individuals and businesses have a right to",
    "A": "procedural due process.",
    "B": "substantive due process.",
    "C": "the Takings Clause.",
    "D": "sovereign immunity.",
    "answer": "A: procedural due process.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does supply chain management increase customer satisfaction?",
    "A": "Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "B": "Integrates information throughout an organization",
    "C": "Improves cash flow",
    "D": "Enhances data quality",
    "answer": "A: Reduces the time it takes for goods to reach consumers",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During which phase of a project do project team members perform archiving procedures?",
    "A": "Controlling",
    "B": "Execution",
    "C": "Definition",
    "D": "Closing",
    "answer": "D: Closing",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the primary purpose of managerial planning?",
    "A": "To evaluate forecasts",
    "B": "To prepare for the future",
    "C": "To implement activities",
    "D": "To change processes",
    "answer": "B: To prepare for the future",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Corey wants a quality product that performs as it is supposed to. In other words, Corey is looking for an item that is",
    "A": "durable.",
    "B": "responsive.",
    "C": "reliable.",
    "D": "serviceable.",
    "answer": "C: reliable.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Silas is unsure how to dress appropriately for his payroll manager job interview. Which of the following is a guideline that might help him select the proper attire:",
    "A": "Clothing types should follow current trends.",
    "B": "Patterns and textures of cloth ing should be contrasting.",
    "C": "Business clothing usually should be conservative.",
    "D": "Articles of clothing should have several points of focus.",
    "answer": "C: Business clothing usually should be conservative.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the benefits of orderly and systematic behavior is that it should help you to achieve",
    "A": "your own goals.",
    "B": "immediate success.",
    "C": "financial security.",
    "D": "personal popularity.",
    "answer": "A: your own goals.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of businesses is most likely to have high liability insurance costs:?",
    "A": "A clothing boutique",
    "B": "A skydiving operation",
    "C": "A landscaping service",
    "D": "An ice cream parlor",
    "answer": "B: A skydiving operation",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is good to feel empathy, but empathy is more beneficial to others if you know how to __________ it.",
    "A": "demonstrate",
    "B": "demand",
    "C": "describe",
    "D": "define",
    "answer": "A: demonstrate",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important function of human resources management in business is",
    "A": "social media.",
    "B": "employee recruitment.",
    "C": "domain development.",
    "D": "capital investment.",
    "answer": "B: employee recruitment.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If the supply of a product decreases while demand remains the same, the price the consumer is charged for the product will probably",
    "A": "decrease.",
    "B": "stabilize.",
    "C": "remain the same.",
    "D": "increase.",
    "answer": "D: increase.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maverick is the new manager of the accounting department. He plans to meet with each employee individually and ask them for feedback about his performance so that he can improve his weaknesses. Which of the following approaches is most likely to result in honest feedback from his staff:",
    "A": "Maverick could admit a weakness that he is working on and ask if there are any other things he needs to improve.",
    "B": "Maverick could anticipate concerns his employees are likely to have about his management style and prepare possible explanations.",
    "C": "Maverick could simply ask employees if they believe he is effectively leading the accounting department.",
    "D": "Maveric k could ask his employees to compare his leadership with the leadership of the former department",
    "answer": "A: Maverick could admit a weakness that he is working on and ask if there are any other things he needs to improve.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you fail to assess the long-term value and impact of your actions on others, you are most likely to",
    "A": "damage other people's relati onships.",
    "B": "limit others' personal growth.",
    "C": "become a better observer of the world around you.",
    "D": "have a negative impact on society.",
    "answer": "D: have a negative impact on society.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the ILM Manufacturing Company orders large amounts of bolts and washers, the company's buyer asks its parts vendor for an additional 5% off the invoice total. This is an example of a business negotiating",
    "A": "delivery terms.",
    "B": "a cash rebate.",
    "C": "a quantity discount.",
    "D": "service terms.",
    "answer": "C: a quantity discount.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following data change activities is considered a best practice:?",
    "A": "Leaving an old system intact until its replacement is completely up and running",
    "B": "Only keeping one copy of all data and systems to reduce redundancy",
    "C": "Planning for data change processes to occur during normal business hours",
    "D": "Keeping data change processes hidden from employees until they are completed",
    "answer": "A: Leaving an old system intact until its replacement is completely up and running",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One possible downside to choosing overseas suppliers is",
    "A": "increased delivery times.",
    "B": "a simpler supply chain.",
    "C": "increased costs.",
    "D": "increased taxes.",
    "answer": "A: increased delivery times.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Andy presents his idea for restructuring his company to the board of directors. In which stage of the change-management lifecycle is Andy?",
    "A": "Implementation",
    "B": "Close",
    "C": "Review and authorize",
    "D": "Identify need for change",
    "answer": "C: Review and authorize",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What section of the statement of work (SOW) defines what the project will produce?",
    "A": "Schedule estimates",
    "B": "Purpose statement",
    "C": "Project deliverables",
    "D": "Benefits and risks",
    "answer": "C: Project deliverables",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the primary goals of supply chain management is to",
    "A": "set prices for products that maximize profits.",
    "B": "control customer perceptions of a business.",
    "C": "minimize overall value to the customer.",
    "D": "gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace.",
    "answer": "D: gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In Maria's community, the accumulation of wealth is a shared value that is often passed down from generation to generation. As a result, Maria is often attracted to luxury products. This is an example of a __________ influence on Maria's buying behavior.",
    "A": "psychological",
    "B": "situational",
    "C": "personal",
    "D": "cultural",
    "answer": "D: cultural",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Thomas is reviewing job applications to determine the five most qualified candidates to interview for a sales position. What management activity is Thomas performing?",
    "A": "Orienting",
    "B": "Training",
    "C": "Screening",
    "D": "Innovating",
    "answer": "C: Screening",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Effective headings in research reports are",
    "A": "vague.",
    "B": "lengthy.",
    "C": "non-parallel.",
    "D": "descriptive.",
    "answer": "D: descriptive.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of technology supporting a business's knowledge management processes:?",
    "A": "Using location-targeted digital advertisements",
    "B": "Tracking customer information in a customer relationship management system",
    "C": "Sendi ng digital coupons through a third-party advertising service",
    "D": "Monitoring interactions on a business social media account",
    "answer": "B: Tracking customer information in a customer relationship management system",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because the company's president was impressed with Ed's willingness to accept additional tasks and carry them out without a lot of direction, they promoted Ed to a management position. What personal trait does Ed possess that helped him advance in his care er?",
    "A": "Self-control",
    "B": "Initiative",
    "C": "Self-confidence",
    "D": "Courage",
    "answer": "B: Initiative",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are examples of digital assets a business could own:?",
    "A": "Logos, apps, and customer email lists",
    "B": "Websites, machinery, and subscriptions",
    "C": "Websites, photographs, and property",
    "D": "Cash, photographs, and machinery",
    "answer": "A: Logos, apps, and customer email lists",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a type of insurance company in which the policyholders retain the profits:?",
    "A": "Insurance underwriting association",
    "B": "Risk retention group",
    "C": "Insurance broker",
    "D": "Local insurance agency",
    "answer": "B: Risk retention group",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Effective change management has benefits on both the organizational and individual levels. A way in which it benefits an individual is that it helps",
    "A": "anticipate challenges and respond efficiently.",
    "B": "contain costs associated with change.",
    "C": "plan efficient communication strategies.",
    "D": "align existing resources within the company.",
    "answer": "C: plan efficient communication strategies.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monitoring a project makes sure people involved are d oing their part to make the project run smoothly. This is an example of how monitoring a project",
    "A": "saves time and resources.",
    "B": "creates accountability.",
    "C": "helps you learn from experience.",
    "D": "builds stronger relationships with stakeholders.",
    "answer": "B: creates accountability.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a good way to end a business phone call:?",
    "A": "Make small talk about the caller's day.",
    "B": "List all of the points made in the call.",
    "C": "Wait for the caller to speak before deciding the call is over.",
    "D": "Offer your email address if the caller needs additional information.",
    "answer": "D: Offer your email address if the caller needs additional information.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding employees' use of social media is true:?",
    "A": "When employees make negative comments about their company, it generates positive publicity.",
    "B": "Employees of large companies should never be allowed to have personal social media pages.",
    "C": "An employee's personal social media pages have no impact on the company.",
    "D": "An employee's social media \"brand\" can impact the company's overall image.",
    "answer": "D: An employee's social media \"brand\" can impact the company's overall image.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of intellectual capital:?",
    "A": "Office computers",
    "B": "Sales revenue",
    "C": "A company's stocks",
    "D": "An employee's product knowledge",
    "answer": "D: An employee's product knowledge",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Every task in a business process should have defined roles and responsibilities, which can be documented in an ARCI matrix. ARCI stands for accountable, responsible, __________, and informed.",
    "A": "constant",
    "B": "controlled",
    "C": "consulted",
    "D": "collaborative",
    "answer": "C: consulted",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses that are built on strong ethical principles are more likely to",
    "A": "avoid legal trouble.",
    "B": "go bankrupt.",
    "C": "face lawsuits.",
    "D": "drive away customers.",
    "answer": "A: avoid legal trouble.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a form of technology used to manage business risk in relation to online security:?",
    "A": "Meta tags",
    "B": "Frames",
    "C": "Site maps",
    "D": "Firewalls",
    "answer": "D: Firewalls",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way in which business profits benefit society:?",
    "A": "Profits indicate trends in consumer preferences.",
    "B": "Profits enable businesses to compete with other businesses.",
    "C": "Profits encourage business owners to conserve resources.",
    "D": "Profits provide an incentive to entrepreneurs.",
    "answer": "C: Profits encourage business owners to conserve resources.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The money that a company has left over after paying its operating expenses and capital expenditures is classified as",
    "A": "limited cash flow.",
    "B": "free cash flow.",
    "C": "dividends.",
    "D": "stock value.",
    "answer": "B: free cash flow.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a project manager fast-track a project?",
    "A": "Increase managerial oversight",
    "B": "Organize teams to run tasks concurrently",
    "C": "Refrain from making changes to stay on course",
    "D": "Add additional human resources",
    "answer": "B: Organize teams to run tasks concurrently",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Creativity is associated closely with the trait of",
    "A": "imagination.",
    "B": "orderliness.",
    "C": "dependability.",
    "D": "patience.",
    "answer": "A: imagination.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When developing persuasive business letters, it is most important for the writers to think about the readers'?",
    "A": "possible objections.",
    "B": "personal images.",
    "C": "decision-making styles.",
    "D": "nonverbal cues.",
    "answer": "A: possible objections.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After his manager instructs him to prepare an analytical report, JoJo conducts online research on consumer preferences and demographics to identify potential growth opportunities. Which of the following analytical reports is JoJo likely writing:",
    "A": "Market analysis",
    "B": "Trend analysis",
    "C": "Financial analysis",
    "D": "Operations analysis",
    "answer": "B: Trend analysis",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What attitude would be most likely to support long-term relationships between businesses and their suppliers?",
    "A": "Collaborative",
    "B": "Influential",
    "C": "Creative",
    "D": "Reflective",
    "answer": "A: Collaborative",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a country with a developing economy participates in free trade, it can expect to encounter",
    "A": "better relationships with other countries.",
    "B": "job loss.",
    "C": "fewer resources.",
    "D": "limited access to new markets.",
    "answer": "A: better relationships with other countries.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following business analysis techniques focuses on how to approach and achieve an organization's\ngoals:?",
    "A": "M.O.S.T.",
    "B": "Six Thinking Hats",
    "C": "S.W.O.T.",
    "D": "P.E.S.T.L.E.",
    "answer": "A: M.O.S.T.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Entrepreneurs protect the profitability of their businesses by developing which of the following skills:",
    "A": "Passive and technical",
    "B": "Language and operations",
    "C": "Domestic and team-building",
    "D": "Financial and problem-solving",
    "answer": "D: Financial and problem-solving",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An important aspect of managing the project team is",
    "A": "monitoring the work effort.",
    "B": "carrying out members' work tasks.",
    "C": "interpreting external data.",
    "D": "evaluating the stakeholders' interests.",
    "answer": "A: monitoring the work effort.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Knowledge management allows companies to",
    "A": "improve their technology.",
    "B": "spend less time on information management.",
    "C": "increase sales revenue.",
    "D": "better answer customer questions.",
    "answer": "D: better answer customer questions.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a major difference between the critical path method and the critical chain method for project management?",
    "A": "The critical path method considers uncertainty more than the critical chain method.",
    "B": "The critical path method includes buffers; the critical chain method does not.",
    "C": "The critical chain method considers resource constraints; the critical path method does not.",
    "D": "The critical chain method accounts for total float; the critical path method does not.",
    "answer": "C: The critical chain method considers resource constraints; the critical path method does not.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nonjudgmental, immediate, and nonthreatening are all characteristics of",
    "A": "internal feedback.",
    "B": "destructive criticism.",
    "C": "constructive criticism.",
    "D": "positive feedback.",
    "answer": "C: constructive criticism.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a technological tool that a business uses to store, update, and access various types of information:?",
    "A": "Newsletter",
    "B": "Instruction manual",
    "C": "Relational database",
    "D": "Microfilm",
    "answer": "C: Relational database",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When natural resources are used to produce a good or service, they become __________ resources.?",
    "A": "economic",
    "B": "monetary",
    "C": "financial",
    "D": "capital",
    "answer": "A: economic",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When prioritizing work, employees should place the most importance on work that involves?",
    "A": "interactive tasks.",
    "B": "tight deadlines.",
    "C": "interpersonal communication.",
    "D": "routine activities.",
    "answer": "B: tight deadlines.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason to apply knowledge management processes:?",
    "A": "To reduce innovation",
    "B": "To increase specialization",
    "C": "To manage information overload",
    "D": "To promote an affective culture",
    "answer": "C: To manage information overload",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As the size and power of United States businesses have increased over time, the federal government's involvement in the U.S. economy has",
    "A": "decreased.",
    "B": "stayed the same.",
    "C": "become unimportant.",
    "D": "increased.",
    "answer": "D: increased.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to the statement of cash flows in a company's annual report, its cash flow from operations last year was $5,260,300 and its capital expenditures were $980,200. What was the company's free cash flow?",
    "A": "$4,280,100",
    "B": "$5,397,164",
    "C": "$1,863,391",
    "D": "$6,240,500",
    "answer": "A: $4,280,100",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mara recently accepted a job with the Sweet Treat Cookie Company. Her new employer required her to sign a document stating that she will not reveal the ingredients in the company's cookie recipes to external sources. This is an example of a(n)",
    "A": "nondisclosure agreement.",
    "B": "indictment.",
    "C": "injunction.",
    "D": "noncompete provision.",
    "answer": "A: nondisclosure agreement.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The primary reason that people lose or leave their jobs is that they have",
    "A": "difficulty understanding their jobs.",
    "B": "difficulty getting along with others.",
    "C": "poor self-esteem.",
    "D": "poor job performance.",
    "answer": "B: difficulty getting along with others.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are results of properly using analytical reports:?",
    "A": "Better flexibility and damaged reputation",
    "B": "Improved adaptability and greater independency",
    "C": "Improved productivity and enhanced communication",
    "D": "Increased collaboration and decreased adaptability",
    "answer": "C: Improved productivity and enhanced communication",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most basic requirements of demonstrating honesty and integrity is to",
    "A": "report any dishonest behavior you hear about.",
    "B": "know how to avoid answering some questions.",
    "C": "learn from others' conversations.",
    "D": "tell the truth in all situations.",
    "answer": "D: tell the truth in all situations.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to occur as a result of a weak dollar in the United States:?",
    "A": "Americans will buy fewer imports.",
    "B": "Americans will experience higher unemployment rates.",
    "C": "Americans will pay higher interest rates.",
    "D": "Americans will sell fewer exports.",
    "answer": "A: Americans will buy fewer imports.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of law addresses issues that interfere with a firm's right to do business?",
    "A": "Criminal",
    "B": "Judiciary",
    "C": "Tort",
    "D": "Environmental",
    "answer": "C: Tort",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding the relationship between a business and its supply chain is true:?",
    "A": "If a business's supply chain is poorly managed, customer satisfaction is likely to suffer.",
    "B": "A business's supply chain has very little impact on the business's overall success.",
    "C": "Supply chains with organizational problems tend to boost members' overall success.",
    "D": "Effective supply chain management results in lower customer satisfaction.",
    "answer": "A: If a business's supply chain is poorly managed, customer satisfaction is likely to suffer.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ariel keeps all of her clients' information on her company's server. What method can Ariel use to ensure the information is unreadable to unauthorized users?",
    "A": "Installing antivirus software",
    "B": "Posting a security policy",
    "C": "Creating strong passwords",
    "D": "Encrypting the information",
    "answer": "D: Encrypting the information",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Maxwell Manufacturing Company regularly inspects its production equipment and conducts regular maintenance activities to ensure that the equipment works correctly and is not a danger to employees. By conducting these activities, Maxwell is complying wi th laws that relate to",
    "A": "workplace safety.",
    "B": "chemical emissions.",
    "C": "discrimination.",
    "D": "technical security.",
    "answer": "A: workplace safety.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of ethical behavior:?",
    "A": "Building relationships",
    "B": "Bending the rules",
    "C": "Honoring your promises",
    "D": "Imitating what others do",
    "answer": "C: Honoring your promises",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should you include in the conclusion section of a research report?",
    "A": "A detailed analysis of your argument",
    "B": "New information to make your argument stronger",
    "C": "Background information about your topic",
    "D": "Reasons why your research findings are significant",
    "answer": "D: Reasons why your research findings are significant",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What management function establishes a business's goals and objectives?",
    "A": "Directing",
    "B": "Organizing",
    "C": "Planning",
    "D": "Staffing",
    "answer": "C: Planning",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most important, fundamental keys to successful change management is",
    "A": "minimizing use of resources.",
    "B": "involving everyone in the organization.",
    "C": "ensuring changes do not impact competitiveness.",
    "D": "focusing on processes over people.",
    "answer": "B: involving everyone in the organization.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The use of sorting techniques to capture knowledge involves",
    "A": "obtaining and storing confidential information.",
    "B": "documenting relevant facts.",
    "C": "comparing and ordering concepts.",
    "D": "setting long-term objectives.",
    "answer": "C: comparing and ordering concepts.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes the relationship between innovation, learning, and change:?",
    "A": "Innovation triggers internal and external changes, leading to new learning.",
    "B": "Internal and external changes trigger new learning, leading to innovation.",
    "C": "Internal and external changes trigger innovation, leading to new learning.",
    "D": "New learning triggers innovation, leading to internal and external changes.",
    "answer": "B: Internal and external changes trigger new learning, leading to innovation.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel says to the audience, \"Now that you have some insight about the nature of the problem, I'll discuss the methodology that our firm used to conduct the research.\" This statement is an example of a(n)",
    "A": "gesture.",
    "B": "transition.",
    "C": "introduction.",
    "D": "conclusion.",
    "answer": "B: transition.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ability of an individual to influence the actions of other people is known as",
    "A": "charisma.",
    "B": "leadership.",
    "C": "authority.",
    "D": "power.",
    "answer": "D: power.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does having a customer-service mindset benefit a business's employees?",
    "A": "It creates a competitive work environment.",
    "B": "It increases the employees' efficiency levels.",
    "C": "It helps the business achieve its profit goals.",
    "D": "It helps employees advance in their careers.",
    "answer": "D: It helps employees advance in their careers.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step of the litigation process?",
    "A": "The defendant answers a complaint.",
    "B": "The defendant files a complaint.",
    "C": "The plaintiff answers a complaint.",
    "D": "The plaintiff files a complaint.",
    "answer": "D: The plaintiff files a complaint.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cameron knows that lying to clients is wrong, but his supervisor encourages it and acts like it is a necessary part of the project's success. Cameron is tempted to act unethically because of",
    "A": "the pressure to hit key deadlines.",
    "B": "his power and authority.",
    "C": "his lack of ethical principles.",
    "D": "the organizational culture.",
    "answer": "D: the organizational culture.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "By cleaning up their work areas at the end of each day, employees usually are able to",
    "A": "lead change.",
    "B": "complete work accurately.",
    "C": "cope with problems.",
    "D": "stay organized.",
    "answer": "D: stay organized.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jorge was hired by a company to establish a plan to protect its digital assets. What is the first thing Jorge should do in this process?",
    "A": "Purchase a cyber insurance policy",
    "B": "Back up all digital assets",
    "C": "Register for ownership of digital assets",
    "D": "List all of the company's digital assets",
    "answer": "D: List all of the company's digital assets",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a strategy to help manage risks in a global supply chain:?",
    "A": "Accept lower quality levels",
    "B": "Work only within the same time zone",
    "C": "Work with experienced partners abroad",
    "D": "Hire only local workers",
    "answer": "C: Work with experienced partners abroad",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To secure confidential financial data that are transmitted online, businesses often use",
    "A": "bots.",
    "B": "debuggers.",
    "C": "cross-platform technology.",
    "D": "encryption techniques.",
    "answer": "D: encryption techniques.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The main difference between arbitration and mediation is that",
    "A": "mediation involves a third party.",
    "B": "mediation applies to criminal cases.",
    "C": "arbitration is a nonbinding process.",
    "D": "arbitration involves a judgment.",
    "answer": "D: arbitration involves a judgment.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Operating costs that are fixed until the business reaches a certain level of production and then become variable are known as __________ expenses.",
    "A": "unfixed",
    "B": "fluctuating",
    "C": "semi-variable",
    "D": "capital",
    "answer": "C: semi-variable",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rita knows she will get a bonus if she pushes for her company to go through with a merger, but she also knows that in the long term, this merger might threaten her job. If Rita supports the merger, she is likely motivated by",
    "A": "sunk costs.",
    "B": "incrementalism.",
    "C": "short-term gratification.",
    "D": "overoptimism and overconfidence.",
    "answer": "C: short-term gratification.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One activity associated with the directing function of management is",
    "A": "interviewing applicants.",
    "B": "establishing goals.",
    "C": "instructing employees.",
    "D": "determining tasks.",
    "answer": "C: instructing employees.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The first step in the control process that management should follow to determine if the company is achieving planned annual sales and profits is to",
    "A": "take corrective action.",
    "B": "set monthly or quarterly sales and profit goals.",
    "C": "monitor sales and profit performance.",
    "D": "determine causes of lagging sales or profits.",
    "answer": "B: set monthly or quarterly sales and profit goals.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why would a business's stockholders be interested in the business's accounting records?",
    "A": "To find out whether the business plans changes",
    "B": "To know when to send in their next dividend",
    "C": "To know whether they have made a good investment",
    "D": "To find out what benefits employees receive",
    "answer": "C: To know whether they have made a good investment",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The final step of change management is to",
    "A": "create a vision.",
    "B": "undo the change.",
    "C": "implement the change.",
    "D": "analyze results.",
    "answer": "D: analyze results.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While a U.S. company conducts business in Chile, the value of the Chilean peso fluctuates and depreciates against the U.S. dollar. This is an example of which of the following types of risk:",
    "A": "Foreign exchange",
    "B": "Security and fraud",
    "C": "Geopolitical",
    "D": "Competition",
    "answer": "A: Foreign exchange",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following tools can be used to reduce information redundancy, control access to information, and share and back up data:?",
    "A": "Database management systems",
    "B": "Financial accounting software",
    "C": "Social networking websites",
    "D": "Cloud-based storage applications",
    "answer": "A: Database management systems",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The production manager of a company that produces wrenches, hammers, and electric drills would most likely report to the",
    "A": "operations assistant.",
    "B": "quality control line supervisor.",
    "C": "director of purchasing.",
    "D": "vice president of manufacturing.",
    "answer": "D: vice president of manufacturing.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Operations managers must work closely with managers and employees in",
    "A": "the marketing department only.",
    "B": "all other parts of the business.",
    "C": "foreign markets.",
    "D": "competing businesses.",
    "answer": "B: all other parts of the business.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To help ensure that its records will survive a large scale disaster such as a flood or hurricane, the ABC Company should store its records",
    "A": "in a remote location.",
    "B": "on desktop computers.",
    "C": "in a locked file room.",
    "D": "in digital formats",
    "answer": "A: in a remote location.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Department manager, small business manager, and regional manager are __________ positions.",
    "A": "supply chain management",
    "B": "general management",
    "C": "business analytics",
    "D": "operations management",
    "answer": "B: general management",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When the meeting leader asked the group participants if they had any suggestions for the new product catalog, Lily pulled out a list of notes that she had compiled and talked for the remaining 20 minutes of the hour-long meeting. In this situation, Lily?",
    "A": "followed parliamentary procedure.",
    "B": "monopolized the discussion.",
    "C": "expressed her opinions clearly.",
    "D": "provided positive feedback.",
    "answer": "B: monopolized the discussion.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To provide transparency for investors and customers, entrepreneurs should",
    "A": "separate their business and personal finances.",
    "B": "use personal money for business purposes.",
    "C": "open a joint bank account for all employees.",
    "D": "use business money for personal purposes.",
    "answer": "A: separate their business and personal finances.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mark works in the research and development department of a large snack food company. It is his job to develop products that consumers will buy and make changes to already existing products to benefit the company. What marketing function is Mark fulfilling?",
    "A": "Product/Service management",
    "B": "Marketing-information management",
    "C": "Pricing",
    "D": "Purchasing",
    "answer": "A: Product/Service management",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a question that should be answered when developing the lessons learned document:?",
    "A": "Who are our stakeholders?",
    "B": "What are the risks?",
    "C": "What equipment should we use?",
    "D": "How can we improve?",
    "answer": "D: How can we improve?",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ranga wants to save for retirement. Ideally, he would like a retirement plan that allows him to make tax-free withdrawals from his account during retirement. What retirement plan would be best for Ranga?",
    "A": "401(k) plan",
    "B": "Roth IRA",
    "C": "Traditional IRA",
    "D": "403(b) plan",
    "answer": "B: Roth IRA",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Filipe is a chef at a restaurant. When Filipe turns his ingredients into a complete meal, he's taking part in",
    "A": "mass production.",
    "B": "resource transformation.",
    "C": "dispatching.",
    "D": "the conversion process.",
    "answer": "D: the conversion process.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a common characteristic of an inspired individual:?",
    "A": "Open to new experiences",
    "B": "Less satisfied with their life",
    "C": "More extrinsically motivated",
    "D": "High levels of self-doubt",
    "answer": "A: Open to new experiences",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When businesses in a particular industry carry risks that commercial insurance companies typically do not cover, they often form __________ to __________ risk.?",
    "A": "independent life insurance agencies; minimize",
    "B": "insurance brokerage firms; assume",
    "C": "captive insurance companies; transfer",
    "D": "insurance rating companies; avoid",
    "answer": "C: captive insurance companies; transfer",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rather than doing them all himself, Sam asked a classmate to create a few of the slides for their group presentation. Sam recognized that he could not do everything himself and instead decided to",
    "A": "prioritize.",
    "B": "overcommit.",
    "C": "divulge.",
    "D": "delegate.",
    "answer": "D: delegate.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before a business begins negotiating with a vendor, it carefully plans the specific points or terms that it is willing to give up that will benefit the vendor. What is the business planning?",
    "A": "The vendor's purchasing power",
    "B": "Desired shipping terms",
    "C": "Targeted discount rates",
    "D": "Its concession strategy",
    "answer": "D: Its concession strategy",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of intangible inventory:?",
    "A": "The number of works-in-process in the company's warehouse",
    "B": "The amount of raw goods on hand according to the company's database",
    "C": "The total amount of finished goods currently waiting to be shipped",
    "D": "The quantity of finished goods currently in transit to distributors",
    "answer": "B: The amount of raw goods on hand according to the company's database",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a technique that companies can use to promote a work-life balance:?",
    "A": "Give all of the most stressful tasks to the most qualified person",
    "B": "Expect employees to reply to emails and phone calls promptly",
    "C": "Offer a generous amount of paid time off",
    "D": "Discourage telecommuting and working remotely",
    "answer": "C: Offer a generous amount of paid time off",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Economic activities can be impacted by __________ changes like droughts, floods, and blizzards.",
    "A": "political",
    "B": "climatic",
    "C": "psychological",
    "D": "demographic",
    "answer": "B: climatic",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After developing a plan for an advertising campaign, a manager is ready to delegate responsibilities to specific employees. Which management function should the manager focus on?",
    "A": "Controlling",
    "B": "Directing",
    "C": "Organizing",
    "D": "Planning",
    "answer": "C: Organizing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Harley is an excellent graphic designer, but she doesn't want to share her tips and tricks with her team members. She's afraid they'll become better designers than her. Harley's organization is being hindered by her",
    "A": "data privacy.",
    "B": "transparency.",
    "C": "self-interest.",
    "D": "intentionality.",
    "answer": "C: self-interest.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The usefulness of a product to consumers is referred to as product",
    "A": "allocation.",
    "B": "scarcity.",
    "C": "consumption.",
    "D": "utility.",
    "answer": "D: utility.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Assessing personal strengths and weaknesses is a(n) __________ process.",
    "A": "onetime",
    "B": "competitive",
    "C": "ongoing",
    "D": "easy",
    "answer": "C: ongoing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The primary ethical conflict in operations is to find ethical ways to cut costs and",
    "A": "keep employees safe.",
    "B": "maximize profits.",
    "C": "develop new products.",
    "D": "hire new employees.",
    "answer": "B: maximize profits.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ONT Company is a very large firm that handles many types of projects. What type of project-management software program would be the best choice for ONT to use?",
    "A": "Costing",
    "B": "Scheduling",
    "C": "Individual-level",
    "D": "Corporate-level",
    "answer": "D: Corporate-level",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kerry always obtains and saves receipts for her __________, which are a tax-deductible expense.",
    "A": "charitable gifts",
    "B": "lunch with coworkers",
    "C": "rent payments",
    "D": "political contributions",
    "answer": "A: charitable gifts",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an acceptable file name for a word-processing document:?",
    "A": "Office Calendar *3/30/2024*",
    "B": "Office Calendar: 3/30/2024",
    "C": "Office Calendar 3 30 2024",
    "D": "Office Calendar <3 30 2024>",
    "answer": "C: Office Calendar 3 30 2024",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When changing data, it is important to?",
    "A": "erase all previous data.",
    "B": "make changes quickly.",
    "C": "send a memo to all company employees.",
    "D": "make identical changes in all locations.",
    "answer": "D: make identical changes in all locations.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your teacher gives you a take-home test, and you're not supposed to use your book to find the answers. You didn't study very much, and now you are tempted to open your book. You know you'd never get caught for cheating. This is a(n) __________ dilemma.",
    "A": "social",
    "B": "ethical",
    "C": "legal",
    "D": "educational",
    "answer": "B: ethical",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which process group includes analyzing and measuring project performance?",
    "A": "Initiating",
    "B": "Executing",
    "C": "Closing",
    "D": "Monitoring and controlling",
    "answer": "D: Monitoring and controlling",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Reynolds Uniform Supplier agreed to sell 500 customized polo shirts to a fast-food restaurant chain at a price of $10 each. After receiving the shirts, however, the fast-food restaurant was surprised to find that the order was missing 100 shirts-and that the supplier charged them $12 per shirt instead of $10. Reynolds Uniform Supplier most likely violated __________ law.",
    "A": "tax",
    "B": "contract",
    "C": "sales",
    "D": "property",
    "answer": "B: contract",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does process thinking help organizations?",
    "A": "Enables them to find out who to blame for issues",
    "B": "Assists them in separating work between departments",
    "C": "Helps them avoid documenting workflow",
    "D": "Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "answer": "D: Lets them know why they succeeded or failed",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the safest and most responsible ways to determine whether an expensive item you're interested in is worth the money is by",
    "A": "contacting the company.",
    "B": "reading verified customer reviews.",
    "C": "searching for other advertisements.",
    "D": "buying the item to see for yourself.",
    "answer": "B: reading verified customer reviews.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does an accurate income statement often help a business identify?",
    "A": "Excessive income",
    "B": "Problem vendors",
    "C": "Trouble spots",
    "D": "Potential sales",
    "answer": "C: Trouble spots",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following focuses primarily on preventing defective products from being created:?",
    "A": "Quality control",
    "B": "Quality inspection",
    "C": "Quality management",
    "D": "Quality assurance",
    "answer": "D: Quality assurance",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does the use of GPS tracking and chipping impact supply chain management?",
    "A": "It hinders efficiency.",
    "B": "It complicates the process.",
    "C": "It helps with decision-making.",
    "D": "It increases spending.",
    "answer": "C: It helps with decision-making.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You ask your teacher, \"What did you mean when you said that promotion is an element of the marketing mix?\" This is a __________ question.",
    "A": "leading",
    "B": "hypothetical",
    "C": "clarifying",
    "D": "provocative",
    "answer": "C: clarifying",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an activity that falls under supply chain management:?",
    "A": "Creating advertising campaigns",
    "B": "Building relationships with vendors",
    "C": "Hiring new employees",
    "D": "Managing investments",
    "answer": "B: Building relationships with vendors",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to the Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI) model, the highest level of maturity that an organization can reach is",
    "A": "optimizing.",
    "B": "initial.",
    "C": "managed.",
    "D": "defined.",
    "answer": "A: optimizing.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following scenarios best represents a company trying to achieve aspirational quality with its products:?",
    "A": "It aims to meet stakeholder and sponsor expectations.",
    "B": "It aims to greatly exceed customer expectations.",
    "C": "It aims to meet standard levels so products can't be deemed failures.",
    "D": "It aims to do the bare minimum to meet standard levels.",
    "answer": "B: It aims to greatly exceed customer expectations.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a recipient-focused informational message:?",
    "A": "\"Everything in the store is on sale during the store's 50th anniversary sale!\"",
    "B": "\"You'll save at least 50% on everything in the store during this incredible sale!\"",
    "C": "\"We're holding a once-in-a-lifetime sale to celebrate our 50th year of business!\"",
    "D": "\"Webber Fashions has been in business for 50 years, so we're celebrating!\"",
    "answer": "B: \"You'll save at least 50% on everything in the store during this incredible sale!\"",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Human resources managers often walk a fine line between doing what is best for the organization and doing",
    "A": "what their family members want them to do.",
    "B": "the action that requires the least amount of work.",
    "C": "what other employees or managers want them to do.",
    "D": "the least profitable thing for the organization.",
    "answer": "C: what other employees or managers want them to do.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Without ethical standards, risk management activities can sometimes occur",
    "A": "illegally.",
    "B": "at the expense of other people.",
    "C": "too often.",
    "D": "without a strong leader in place.",
    "answer": "B: at the expense of other people.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Elaine, a buyer for a large retail chain, needs to order paper. She chooses Sheets Paper Company because Sheets has the best prices and can ship the order tomorrow. This is an example of a __________ order.",
    "A": "standard",
    "B": "contract",
    "C": "blanket",
    "D": "planned",
    "answer": "A: standard",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which component of the project's statement of work (SOW) would the following message most likely appear: \"Due to the limited amount of time allocated to complete the study, the survey sample size may need to be reduced.\"",
    "A": "Deliverables",
    "B": "Purpose",
    "C": "Constraints",
    "D": "Benefits",
    "answer": "C: Constraints",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its business processes is",
    "A": "desire for growth.",
    "B": "competition.",
    "C": "high operating costs.",
    "D": "low employee morale.",
    "answer": "B: competition.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Under which of the following circumstances is it appropriate for applicants to prepare interview follow-up letters:",
    "A": "After they have submitted application forms",
    "B": "Before they agree to pre-employment testing",
    "C": "In order to send information with r\u00e9sum\u00e9s",
    "D": "When they are no longer interested in the job",
    "answer": "D: When they are no longer interested in the job",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chloe recently took over the family business so that her parents could retire. While reorganizing her dad's desk so that she could use it, Chloe found several compact discs (CDs). She'd like to find out what is stored on each disc, but she doesn't have a c omputer with a CD drive. She can't access the data on the discs because CDs have become",
    "A": "destructive.",
    "B": "obsolete.",
    "C": "decentralized.",
    "D": "networked.",
    "answer": "B: obsolete.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a digital asset that a company might have:?",
    "A": "Social media posts",
    "B": "Company stock",
    "C": "Computer keyboards and monitors",
    "D": "Manufacturing equipment",
    "answer": "A: Social media posts",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following supply chain issues is primarily a result of globalization:?",
    "A": "Companies need to personalize products and packaging to appeal to multiple customer segments.",
    "B": "Supply chain networks are much smaller and less complex than they were in previous eras.",
    "C": "Members in a supply chain need to have a clear understanding of how the larger network operates.",
    "D": "It is easier than ever for companies to differentiate their products from the competition.",
    "answer": "A: Companies need to personalize products and packaging to appeal to multiple customer segments.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pooja is a financial analyst taking part in a group discussion about the operations of her company. Pooja stays quiet during most of the meeting but is very vocal when the discussion focuses on how to save on operating costs. Which of the following is Pooja doing to contribute to a successful group di scussion:",
    "A": "Adopting a laid-back attitude",
    "B": "Being rigid about others' ideas",
    "C": "Only speaking if knowledgeable on the topic",
    "D": "Controlling the entire discussion",
    "answer": "C: Only speaking if knowledgeable on the topic",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An individual who likes to keep track of information, such as facts and statistics, should consider an occupation that involves working with",
    "A": "people.",
    "B": "equipment.",
    "C": "things.",
    "D": "data.",
    "answer": "D: data.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Over the years, Malcolm has implemented strategies that help him perform and complete a work activity more efficiently. The department manager has asked Malcolm to write down the steps of the process so that the instructions will be available for coworkers and employees in the future. This is an example of",
    "A": "confidential information.",
    "B": "data procurement.",
    "C": "project management.",
    "D": "knowledge codification.",
    "answer": "D: knowledge codification.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of partnership arrangement might restrict a partner's liability?",
    "A": "\"S\"",
    "B": "Limited",
    "C": "Franchise",
    "D": "Close",
    "answer": "B: Limited",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Capital goods reflect the state of __________ that exists in society.",
    "A": "motivation",
    "B": "goodwill",
    "C": "technology",
    "D": "farmland",
    "answer": "C: technology",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "MOST, PESTLE, and SWOT are all types of",
    "A": "standards-setting organizations.",
    "B": "business analysis techniques.",
    "C": "international governing entities.",
    "D": "supply chain management approaches.",
    "answer": "B: business analysis techniques.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of an organization that has a positive culture:?",
    "A": "Limits recognition",
    "B": "Respects different ideas",
    "C": "Controls all activities",
    "D": "Demands agreement",
    "answer": "B: Respects different ideas",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Simone needs to update a customer's credit card information in the company's internal database. How should Simone obtain this information?",
    "A": "Email the customer and request that they respond with the information",
    "B": "Call the customer and ask them to verbalize the information",
    "C": "Text the customer to ask that they take a picture and text the information",
    "D": "Request the customer write down and mail the information",
    "answer": "B: Call the customer and ask them to verbalize the information",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you are implementing change on a wider scale, in which stage of the PDCA (Plan-Do-Check-Act) cycle are you?",
    "A": "Plan",
    "B": "Check",
    "C": "Act",
    "D": "Do",
    "answer": "C: Act",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is needed to maintain collaborative relationships with suppliers?",
    "A": "Complete disclosure of information",
    "B": "Different goals and objectives",
    "C": "A comprehensive request for proposal",
    "D": "Effective conflict-resolution skills",
    "answer": "D: Effective conflict-resolution skills",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Identifying and eliminating defects that cause variations in quality is the primary goal of",
    "A": "behavior modeling.",
    "B": "Six Sigma.",
    "C": "\"Big Q.\"",
    "D": "acceptance sampling.",
    "answer": "B: Six Sigma.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Consensus building creates high-quality solutions because",
    "A": "some people have more power than others.",
    "B": "only a few ideas are considered.",
    "C": "everyone has a unique perspective.",
    "D": "it is very time-consuming.",
    "answer": "C: everyone has a unique perspective.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does self-control help you think clearly?",
    "A": "By helping you be defensive",
    "B": "By helping you deal with criticism",
    "C": "By helping you keep a positive attitude",
    "D": "By helping you be objective",
    "answer": "D: By helping you be objective",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mediating conflict, resolving issues, and providing feedback are all components of",
    "A": "conducting a post-implementation review.",
    "B": "managing a project team.",
    "C": "documenting team progress.",
    "D": "completing a work breakdown structure.",
    "answer": "B: managing a project team.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way to break down a large work task into smaller easy-to-understand steps that, when completed, will result in the completion of the task:?",
    "A": "Entrepreneurial thinking",
    "B": "Process thinking",
    "C": "Creative thinking",
    "D": "Critical thinking",
    "answer": "B: Process thinking",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Reviewing activity status reports helps a project manager",
    "A": "develop specifications.",
    "B": "control the project.",
    "C": "determine project scope.",
    "D": "create barriers.",
    "answer": "B: control the project.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of accounting method is your company using if it records sales as they happen, even if no money changes hands then?",
    "A": "Income",
    "B": "Cash",
    "C": "Accrual",
    "D": "Credit",
    "answer": "C: Accrual",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements about data analytics is true:?",
    "A": "Prescriptive analytics recommend specific courses of action.",
    "B": "Descriptive analytics provide forecasts of the future.",
    "C": "Descriptive analytics recommend specific courses of action.",
    "D": "Predictive analytics provide descriptions of the past.",
    "answer": "A: Prescriptive analytics recommend specific courses of action.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nate was supposed to bring his report card back to school, signed by a parent. After forgetting 3 days in a row, his teacher gave him a detention. Nate doesn't complain about it because he knows he didn't follow the teacher's directions. Which of the follo wing steps for following directions does this situation illustrate:",
    "A": "Not rushing",
    "B": "Accepting responsibility",
    "C": "Noting key words",
    "D": "Knowing when to speak",
    "answer": "B: Accepting responsibility",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The recommendations section of a well-written research report should be based on",
    "A": "the research findings.",
    "B": "the researcher's values.",
    "C": "psychological theories.",
    "D": "customary opinions.",
    "answer": "A: the research findings.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tyrone, a new employee, had to attend daily training sessions for his first two weeks on the job. He learned a lot about the company and his new role, but he didn't retain much of it over time. This example demonstrates that",
    "A": "training sessions are useless for most employees.",
    "B": "learning and knowledge are the same thing.",
    "C": "learning doesn't always lead to knowledge.",
    "D": "knowledge is fleeting and hard to hold onto.",
    "answer": "C: learning doesn't always lead to knowledge.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following items would a clothing manufacturer classify as raw materials inventory:?",
    "A": "Thread, zippers, and sewing machines",
    "B": "Cloth, zippers, and shirts",
    "C": "Zippers, sewing machines, and cloth",
    "D": "Buttons, cloth, and thread",
    "answer": "D: Buttons, cloth, and thread",
    "topic": "Supply Chain Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a risk that is unique to international expansion:?",
    "A": "The relationship between the foreign government and business",
    "B": "The threat of digital security breaches",
    "C": "The potential to grow brand awareness",
    "D": "The potential for losing money on the investment",
    "answer": "A: The relationship between the foreign government and business",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit of project planning:?",
    "A": "Setting an appropriate time frame",
    "B": "Monitoring your project",
    "C": "Asking yourself important questions",
    "D": "Coordinating all of the parts of the project",
    "answer": "D: Coordinating all of the parts of the project",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Shawn is working on a project but finds himself overwhelmed with everything needed for the project to be successful. Before beginning work, Shawn wants to lay out all project milestones and deliverables. What should Shawn create?",
    "A": "A statement of work",
    "B": "An issue log",
    "C": "A work breakdown structure",
    "D": "A scope statement",
    "answer": "C: A work breakdown structure",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following directly results from a business with an efficient supply chain:?",
    "A": "Higher salaries",
    "B": "Higher customer demand",
    "C": "Lower overhead costs",
    "D": "Less inventory",
    "answer": "C: Lower overhead costs",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "PRD Manufacturing quickly realigned its production processes to meet a sudden rise in customer demand for its products. What characteristic of an adaptable organization did the manufacturing company exhibit?",
    "A": "Agility",
    "B": "Competitive aggression",
    "C": "Innovation",
    "D": "Cultural intelligence",
    "answer": "A: Agility",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason why businesses try to control expenses to purchase the most modern equipment:?",
    "A": "To offer good benefits",
    "B": "To spend excess cash",
    "C": "To remain competitive",
    "D": "To satisfy suppliers",
    "answer": "C: To remain competitive",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Zoe noticed that her coworker Tom has been performing a work activity incorrectly. Zoe hasn't corrected Tom because she wants her manager to think she is more competent than Tom. Can Zoe's behavior negatively impact her employer?",
    "A": "No. Zoe knows that Tom's errors do not affect customer relationships.",
    "B": "No. Zoe is not a manager and should not train Tom.",
    "C": "Yes. Zoe is violating a procedural law.",
    "D": "Yes. Tom's errors could be costly to the company.",
    "answer": "D: Yes. Tom's errors could be costly to the company.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Javier's company uses a knowledge-management system. Because of it, he knows that an important client would like to choose from a greater selection of products. He offers the client a new and bigger product selection, including some products with a greater profit margin for the company. This example illustrates which influencing factor in knowledge management:",
    "A": "Turnover",
    "B": "Enhanced value",
    "C": "Innovation",
    "D": "Globalization and competition",
    "answer": "B: Enhanced value",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the primary purpose of developing a post-implementation review during the closure phase of a project?",
    "A": "To determine if the deliverables achieved project goals",
    "B": "To document necessary changes for future projects",
    "C": "To formally release all resources from the project",
    "D": "To archive all project documentation",
    "answer": "A: To determine if the deliverables achieved project goals",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would probably result if a business reduced its marketing costs:?",
    "A": "Increased costs of production",
    "B": "Decreased need for customer contact with businesses",
    "C": "Increased consumer awareness of goods and services",
    "D": "Decreased variety of consumer goods",
    "answer": "D: Decreased variety of consumer goods",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When emailing large files or documents to coworkers or customers, a businessperson sends them?",
    "A": "as reply messages.",
    "B": "in text boxes.",
    "C": "as attachments.",
    "D": "in codes.",
    "answer": "C: as attachments.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hassan's business is committed to constantly seeking new ways to make its processes and products more efficient. Recently, the business adopted a new delivery system that helps customers receive their online orders in half of the time. This is an example of what aspect of quality management?",
    "A": "Quality control",
    "B": "Quality improvement",
    "C": "Quality assurance",
    "D": "Quality deterrent",
    "answer": "B: Quality improvement",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Tafoya Company has discovered that the Bremen Company illegally used Tafoya's trademark. To pursue a legal case for financial compensation, what should Tafoya's legal counsel do first?",
    "A": "File a formal complaint to the court alleging the Bremen Company's illegal use of the Tafoya trademark",
    "B": "Conduct an examination of discovery to interview all parties involved in the illegal use of the Tafoya trademark",
    "C": "Issue a summons requiring the Bremen Company to respond to allegations of misusing the trademark",
    "D": "Request that a pretrial conference date be set to clarify all the legal issues that will be discussed during the",
    "answer": "A: File a formal complaint to the court alleging the Bremen Company's illegal use of the Tafoya trademark",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You enjoy talking to people and have great public speaking skills. Which type of business management career should you consider:",
    "A": "Human resources",
    "B": "Business analytics",
    "C": "Supply chain",
    "D": "Operations",
    "answer": "A: Human resources",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of risk management:?",
    "A": "Treating others with respect",
    "B": "Following all the rules and procedures",
    "C": "Checking that a product works the way it is supposed to",
    "D": "Developing an alternative plan in case of technology failure",
    "answer": "D: Developing an alternative plan in case of technology failure",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage of a supply chain's ability to adjust internal inventory levels:?",
    "A": "It significantly reduces transportation costs.",
    "B": "It no longer needs to monitor inventory levels.",
    "C": "It develops better supplier relationships.",
    "D": "It can respond to changes in the marketplace.",
    "answer": "D: It can respond to changes in the marketplace.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The first step in the managerial control process is",
    "A": "measuring performance.",
    "B": "taking corrective action.",
    "C": "determining standards of excellence.",
    "D": "comparing performance with standards.",
    "answer": "C: determining standards of excellence.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Talia has been putting aside a portion of her paycheck each month. Now, she has enough saved to take a relaxing beach vacation. This is an example of how",
    "A": "spending money on unnecessary purchases is risky.",
    "B": "you can only save when you've reached a certain income level.",
    "C": "your emergency fund can be used in many ways.",
    "D": "saving money benefits your overall well-being.",
    "answer": "D: saving money benefits your overall well-being.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the drawbacks of communicating without words is that it is",
    "A": "sometimes misunderstood.",
    "B": "not effective.",
    "C": "hard to learn.",
    "D": "too precise.",
    "answer": "A: sometimes misunderstood.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following change management strategies should a company first implement if employees are intimidated by and afraid of change:?",
    "A": "Enable and sustain change",
    "B": "Reflect on change",
    "C": "Avoid making changes",
    "D": "Create a climate for change",
    "answer": "D: Create a climate for change",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Frankie used her business's most recent cash-flow statement to determine how much money the business had left over after subtracting its capital expenditures from its operating cash flow. What did Frankie calculate?",
    "A": "Amortization",
    "B": "Free cash flow",
    "C": "Working capital",
    "D": "Profit",
    "answer": "B: Free cash flow",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The desire for friendship belongs in which of the following categories:",
    "A": "Opportunity cost",
    "B": "Capital good",
    "C": "Noneconomic want",
    "D": "Service",
    "answer": "C: Noneconomic want",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage of weak currency:?",
    "A": "It makes buying imports cheaper.",
    "B": "It boosts exports.",
    "C": "It improves global perception of the domestic economy.",
    "D": "It inhibits business expansion into foreign markets.",
    "answer": "B: It boosts exports.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "High levels of apathy, low levels of creativity, and poor job performance are all characteristics of __________ conflict.",
    "A": "adaptable",
    "B": "positive",
    "C": "dysfunctional",
    "D": "functional",
    "answer": "C: dysfunctional",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To prevent security breaches by disgruntled employees, a business can",
    "A": "immediately terminate accounts that are no longer in use.",
    "B": "use strong passwords on all accounts.",
    "C": "install antivirus software.",
    "D": "make sure all employees are happy with the company.",
    "answer": "A: immediately terminate accounts that are no longer in use.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As employees go about their daily activities, their actions should be driven by whether they will",
    "A": "benefit the workforce.",
    "B": "result in customer satisfaction.",
    "C": "be witnessed by customers.",
    "D": "result in additional sales.",
    "answer": "B: result in customer satisfaction.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When traveling to certain countries for a long-term business assignment, you will need to have __________, which is an official document that temporarily authorizes you to be in that country.?",
    "A": "travel insurance",
    "B": "proof of citizenship",
    "C": "a permanent resident card",
    "D": "a visa",
    "answer": "D: a visa",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Human, regulatory, technological, and environmental factors are most likely to influence the design of",
    "A": "business processes.",
    "B": "office visitation guidelines.",
    "C": "project due dates.",
    "D": "employee leave policies.",
    "answer": "A: business processes.",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one way that employees can help their companies protect digital assets?",
    "A": "Send out emails to update everyone on security policy changes",
    "B": "Follow company policies about giving out personal information",
    "C": "Download documents from unevaluated websites",
    "D": "Share passwords with everyone in the company",
    "answer": "B: Follow company policies about giving out personal information",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kevin is planning to paint a house. He draws a simple graph that shows the sequence of tasks that will be done from beginning to end of the project. For example: 1) Buy supplies, 2) Prepare house for painting, 3) Paint house, and so on. This is an example of a",
    "A": "work breakdown structure.",
    "B": "project charter.",
    "C": "scope management plan.",
    "D": "network diagram.",
    "answer": "D: network diagram.",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "On what type of purchase order are you most likely to find the following information: This order covers the MRE Manufacturing Company's purchase of \u00bd\" rubber gaskets, Model # 62376 metal washers, and \"Y\" PVC piping beginning April 10, 2023 through March 31, 2025. The prices stated in your quotation dated January 31, 2021 are effective until March 31, 2025.",
    "A": "Blanket",
    "B": "Custom",
    "C": "Service",
    "D": "Referral",
    "answer": "A: Blanket",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Emma recently wrote an in-depth report on how her company can better reach millennial customers. Her report included an assessment of the company's current relationship with millennials as well as what steps the organization should take to improve the relationship. In other words, Emma wrote a(n) __________ report.",
    "A": "analytical",
    "B": "financial",
    "C": "data-based",
    "D": "informational",
    "answer": "A: analytical",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following situations is a settlement most likely to occur:",
    "A": "A defendant feels they have a strong chance of winning.",
    "B": "A struggling company wants to gain publicity.",
    "C": "A small company does not have the funds to go to court.",
    "D": "A complicated case involves multiple defendants.",
    "answer": "C: A small company does not have the funds to go to court.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The implementation of digital warehouse management systems is an example of how technology can impact __________ management.",
    "A": "financial",
    "B": "employee",
    "C": "human resource",
    "D": "supply chain",
    "answer": "D: supply chain",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the most important consideration in selecting a banking institution:?",
    "A": "The bank's ability to meet your current financial needs",
    "B": "The bank's ability to help plan your future financial needs",
    "C": "The bank's broad range of services",
    "D": "The bank's capacity to be financially profitable",
    "answer": "A: The bank's ability to meet your current financial needs",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An ethical purchasing department works with vendors that",
    "A": "encourage unpaid overtime.",
    "B": "provide safe working conditions.",
    "C": "use materials from endangered habitats.",
    "D": "prioritize speed over quality.",
    "answer": "B: provide safe working conditions.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following factors affecting personal appearance includes nutrition:?",
    "A": "Health",
    "B": "Grooming",
    "C": "Dress",
    "D": "Self-concept",
    "answer": "A: Health",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Serena is determining the specific activities needed to carry out a year-long advertising campaign. Serena is engaged in __________ planning.",
    "A": "strategic",
    "B": "long-term",
    "C": "contingency",
    "D": "tactical",
    "answer": "D: tactical",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a barrier to effective listening:?",
    "A": "Concentration",
    "B": "Open-mindedness",
    "C": "Distractions",
    "D": "Empathy",
    "answer": "C: Distractions",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do risk retention groups and captive insurers have in common?",
    "A": "They can both be headquartered anywhere in the world.",
    "B": "They are both forms of self-insurance.",
    "C": "They both only write liability coverage.",
    "D": "They both require a license in every state in which they operate.",
    "answer": "B: They are both forms of self-insurance.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of gathering information before making a decision:?",
    "A": "Asking questions",
    "B": "Watching movies",
    "C": "Writing letters",
    "D": "Reading novels",
    "answer": "A: Asking questions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gloves, computers, and office supplies are examples of",
    "A": "MRO goods.",
    "B": "transit inventory.",
    "C": "intangible inventory.",
    "D": "raw materials.",
    "answer": "A: MRO goods.",
    "topic": "Supply Chain Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesspeople are often unwilling to share tacit knowledge with coworkers when",
    "A": "economic conditions stabilize.",
    "B": "work relationships are interdependent.",
    "C": "job security is an issue.",
    "D": "management encourages collaboration.",
    "answer": "C: job security is an issue.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following are recorded chronologically when a change is made in a database and for any subsequent data changes:?",
    "A": "Timestamps",
    "B": "Queries",
    "C": "Changed data",
    "D": "Corrections",
    "answer": "A: Timestamps",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions can help a person develop empathy:?",
    "A": "Avoiding criticism",
    "B": "Eliminating stereotypes",
    "C": "Eliminating sympathy",
    "D": "Forming strong opinions",
    "answer": "B: Eliminating stereotypes",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you compliment someone's efforts even though the results weren't so good, you are likely to?",
    "A": "discourage them from trying again.",
    "B": "motivate them to keep working hard.",
    "C": "provide them with a false sense of success.",
    "D": "decrease their motivation to keep working hard.",
    "answer": "B: motivate them to keep working hard.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What technological tool can help businesses understand the types of knowledge that employees need to perform their jobs efficiently?",
    "A": "Systems register",
    "B": "Probability chart",
    "C": "Accountability matrix",
    "D": "Navigation log",
    "answer": "C: Accountability matrix",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When negotiating with a vendor, it is important to?",
    "A": "act as quickly as possible.",
    "B": "reject compliments.",
    "C": "prepare ahead of time.",
    "D": "use deception tactics.",
    "answer": "C: prepare ahead of time.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements about quality management is true:?",
    "A": "It deals solely with products and services.",
    "B": "It integrates quality into every aspect of a company.",
    "C": "It only applies to specific departments.",
    "D": "It isn't important to meet customer expectations.",
    "answer": "B: It integrates quality into every aspect of a company.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a possible consequence of having one's identity stolen:?",
    "A": "Unemployment",
    "B": "Need for new identity",
    "C": "Damage to credit history",
    "D": "Homelessness",
    "answer": "C: Damage to credit history",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When developing a personal budget, which of the following is typically a variable expense:?",
    "A": "Grocery bills",
    "B": "Car payments",
    "C": "Phone bills",
    "D": "Rent payments",
    "answer": "A: Grocery bills",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The judge based their legal decision by considering a similar decision made in another court. This is an example of which source of law?",
    "A": "Uniform",
    "B": "Constitutional",
    "C": "Statutory",
    "D": "Case",
    "answer": "D: Case",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mitchell is reviewing internal data and proposals from several agencies to determine the best course of action for implementing a major advertising campaign for his company. What is Mitchell analyzing?",
    "A": "Human resources",
    "B": "Operating schedule",
    "C": "Financial status",
    "D": "Promotional needs",
    "answer": "D: Promotional needs",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An unhappy customer wants to return some merchandise to the resort's gift shop. The salesperson listens well and is polite and courteous to the customer. As a result of this professional approach, the customer leaves the business satisfied. This is an example of",
    "A": "building positive customer relations.",
    "B": "increasing sales through suggestion selling.",
    "C": "providing quality products.",
    "D": "reducing employee turnover.",
    "answer": "A: building positive customer relations.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before implementing change, an important step in change management is",
    "A": "reviewing change.",
    "B": "embedding change.",
    "C": "creating a vision.",
    "D": "analyzing results.",
    "answer": "C: creating a vision.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following documents is it most appropriate to include an executive summary:",
    "A": "Complex research report",
    "B": "Six-page case study",
    "C": "Manuscript outline",
    "D": "Employee handbook",
    "answer": "A: Complex research report",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is risk modeling important?",
    "A": "It helps businesses proactively respond to potential risks.",
    "B": "It enables businesses to predict the future with complete certainty.",
    "C": "It guarantees businesses can mitigate all risks.",
    "D": "It replaces business expertise and management.",
    "answer": "A: It helps businesses proactively respond to potential risks.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a tool that can be used to evaluate project data:?",
    "A": "Competitive analysis",
    "B": "Feasibility analysis",
    "C": "Gap analysis",
    "D": "Environmental analysis",
    "answer": "C: Gap analysis",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During the risk management planning stage, companies should",
    "A": "reward ethical behavior.",
    "B": "focus on internal issues.",
    "C": "avoid discussing compliance.",
    "D": "assess their ethical needs.",
    "answer": "D: assess their ethical needs.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following most likely indicates that a manager needs to work on their directing abilities:?",
    "A": "Meeting goals",
    "B": "Adding new staff members",
    "C": "Missing deadlines",
    "D": "Communicating regularly",
    "answer": "C: Missing deadlines",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As a result of new privacy regulations, businesses that collect or process data have needed to change their processes. This is an example of how businesses often modify processes in response to changes in",
    "A": "technology.",
    "B": "legal requirements.",
    "C": "the marketplace.",
    "D": "customer demand.",
    "answer": "B: legal requirements.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which characteristic of a SMART goal does the following statement exemplify? Phase one of the project will be completed on May 10, 2025.?",
    "A": "Structured",
    "B": "Time-bound",
    "C": "Realistic",
    "D": "Motivational",
    "answer": "B: Time-bound",
    "topic": "Project Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Vincent's project team has a conflict in an emergency situation that must be dealt with immediately. Team members have many differing viewpoints that cannot all be accommodated. As project manager, which conflict resolution strategy should Vincent use?",
    "A": "Collaborate/Problem solve",
    "B": "Withdraw/Avoid",
    "C": "Force/Direct",
    "D": "Compromise/Reconcile",
    "answer": "C: Force/Direct",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Self-understanding is important because the better you understand yourself, the",
    "A": "more success you will have.",
    "B": "better you'll be at learning new skills.",
    "C": "more money you will make.",
    "D": "better prepared you'll be to cope with life.",
    "answer": "D: better prepared you'll be to cope with life.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is true of arbitration:?",
    "A": "It is a cooperative process.",
    "B": "It is an adversarial process.",
    "C": "It is more expensive than litigation.",
    "D": "It usually has a win-win outcome.",
    "answer": "B: It is an adversarial process.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an application of knowledge management in the workplace:?",
    "A": "A frontline employee doing day-to-day work",
    "B": "A researcher conducting surveys about an upcoming decision",
    "C": "A project team leader issuing memos with project updates",
    "D": "A manager creating a guide on performing a work task",
    "answer": "D: A manager creating a guide on performing a work task",
    "topic": "Knowledge Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of people using persuasion in business:?",
    "A": "Delivering or distributing goods to a customer on a timely basis",
    "B": "Presenting the company's annual financial statement to the board of directors",
    "C": "Requesting product specifications from a vendor or manufacturer",
    "D": "Distributing a report to company officers that recommends policy changes",
    "answer": "D: Distributing a report to company officers that recommends policy changes",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  }
]